[{"history_id":"1","user_id":"37","game_stage":"2","question":"85-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:46:42"},
{"history_id":"2","user_id":"37","game_stage":"2","question":"79+68","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":68}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":68}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:47:15"},
{"history_id":"3","user_id":"40","game_stage":"2","question":"62+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:47:52"},
{"history_id":"4","user_id":"37","game_stage":"2","question":"90-48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:48:36"},
{"history_id":"5","user_id":"40","game_stage":"2","question":"9+83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:49:13"},
{"history_id":"6","user_id":"38","game_stage":"2","question":"77+88","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:49:26"},
{"history_id":"7","user_id":"40","game_stage":"2","question":"71-41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:49:34"},
{"history_id":"8","user_id":"41","game_stage":"2","question":"46-27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:49:53"},
{"history_id":"9","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"15+99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:03"},
{"history_id":"10","user_id":"58","game_stage":"2","question":"83-40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:07"},
{"history_id":"11","user_id":"45","game_stage":"2","question":"73+49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:10"},
{"history_id":"12","user_id":"48","game_stage":"2","question":"70+70","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":70}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:18"},
{"history_id":"13","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"91-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:27"},
{"history_id":"14","user_id":"31","game_stage":"2","question":"55-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:34"},
{"history_id":"15","user_id":"56","game_stage":"2","question":"39+37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:36"},
{"history_id":"16","user_id":"35","game_stage":"2","question":"6+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:37"},
{"history_id":"17","user_id":"38","game_stage":"2","question":"55-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:48"},
{"history_id":"18","user_id":"37","game_stage":"2","question":"10+89","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:52"},
{"history_id":"19","user_id":"32","game_stage":"2","question":"63+90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:50:53"},
{"history_id":"20","user_id":"34","game_stage":"2","question":"86+83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:07"},
{"history_id":"21","user_id":"51","game_stage":"2","question":"74-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:08"},
{"history_id":"22","user_id":"32","game_stage":"2","question":"29+87","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":87}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":87}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:11"},
{"history_id":"23","user_id":"40","game_stage":"2","question":"23-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:17"},
{"history_id":"24","user_id":"32","game_stage":"2","question":"53-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:30"},
{"history_id":"25","user_id":"41","game_stage":"2","question":"38+90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:32"},
{"history_id":"26","user_id":"40","game_stage":"2","question":"66-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:50"},
{"history_id":"27","user_id":"35","game_stage":"2","question":"48-22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:53"},
{"history_id":"28","user_id":"43","game_stage":"2","question":"50-33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:53"},
{"history_id":"29","user_id":"45","game_stage":"2","question":"91-32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:51:55"},
{"history_id":"30","user_id":"48","game_stage":"2","question":"99-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:07"},
{"history_id":"31","user_id":"46","game_stage":"2","question":"23-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:07"},
{"history_id":"32","user_id":"58","game_stage":"2","question":"5+65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:20"},
{"history_id":"33","user_id":"37","game_stage":"3","question":"65÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:22"},
{"history_id":"34","user_id":"53","game_stage":"2","question":"70-44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:28"},
{"history_id":"35","user_id":"51","game_stage":"2","question":"42-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:29"},
{"history_id":"36","user_id":"56","game_stage":"2","question":"65-48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:31"},
{"history_id":"37","user_id":"39","game_stage":"2","question":"71-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:33"},
{"history_id":"38","user_id":"43","game_stage":"2","question":"12+98","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":98}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":98}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:35"},
{"history_id":"39","user_id":"57","game_stage":"2","question":"39+67","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:42"},
{"history_id":"40","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"63-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:48"},
{"history_id":"41","user_id":"34","game_stage":"2","question":"59-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:50"},
{"history_id":"42","user_id":"38","game_stage":"2","question":"84-35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:52:58"},
{"history_id":"43","user_id":"49","game_stage":"2","question":"6+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:09"},
{"history_id":"44","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"55+36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:10"},
{"history_id":"45","user_id":"37","game_stage":"3","question":"34x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:14"},
{"history_id":"46","user_id":"32","game_stage":"2","question":"76-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:18"},
{"history_id":"47","user_id":"46","game_stage":"2","question":"59-48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:35"},
{"history_id":"48","user_id":"55","game_stage":"2","question":"24-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:38"},
{"history_id":"49","user_id":"35","game_stage":"2","question":"69-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:47"},
{"history_id":"50","user_id":"48","game_stage":"2","question":"25-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:58"},
{"history_id":"51","user_id":"39","game_stage":"2","question":"76-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:59"},
{"history_id":"52","user_id":"37","game_stage":"3","question":"8x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:53:59"},
{"history_id":"53","user_id":"57","game_stage":"2","question":"65-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:01"},
{"history_id":"54","user_id":"53","game_stage":"2","question":"43-33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:03"},
{"history_id":"55","user_id":"46","game_stage":"2","question":"92-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:04"},
{"history_id":"56","user_id":"47","game_stage":"2","question":"58-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:12"},
{"history_id":"57","user_id":"43","game_stage":"2","question":"4+43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:17"},
{"history_id":"58","user_id":"36","game_stage":"2","question":"83+40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:21"},
{"history_id":"59","user_id":"41","game_stage":"2","question":"78+3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:23"},
{"history_id":"60","user_id":"51","game_stage":"2","question":"73-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:35"},
{"history_id":"61","user_id":"38","game_stage":"3","question":"14x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:35"},
{"history_id":"62","user_id":"49","game_stage":"2","question":"26-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:36"},
{"history_id":"63","user_id":"56","game_stage":"2","question":"59-32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:36"},
{"history_id":"64","user_id":"58","game_stage":"2","question":"26+11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:39"},
{"history_id":"65","user_id":"39","game_stage":"2","question":"53-14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:39"},
{"history_id":"66","user_id":"31","game_stage":"2","question":"43-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:55"},
{"history_id":"67","user_id":"40","game_stage":"3","question":"38x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":228,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":228,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:54:57"},
{"history_id":"68","user_id":"38","game_stage":"3","question":"1x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:00"},
{"history_id":"69","user_id":"32","game_stage":"2","question":"42-41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:04"},
{"history_id":"70","user_id":"44","game_stage":"2","question":"47-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:04"},
{"history_id":"71","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"98+82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:27"},
{"history_id":"72","user_id":"55","game_stage":"2","question":"81+46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":46}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:32"},
{"history_id":"73","user_id":"40","game_stage":"3","question":"20x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:32"},
{"history_id":"74","user_id":"45","game_stage":"2","question":"61-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:34"},
{"history_id":"75","user_id":"38","game_stage":"3","question":"27x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:34"},
{"history_id":"76","user_id":"47","game_stage":"2","question":"42-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:39"},
{"history_id":"77","user_id":"48","game_stage":"3","question":"12÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:43"},
{"history_id":"78","user_id":"37","game_stage":"4","question":"188+26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:45"},
{"history_id":"79","user_id":"53","game_stage":"2","question":"24+50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:56"},
{"history_id":"80","user_id":"51","game_stage":"3","question":"60÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:55:58"},
{"history_id":"81","user_id":"36","game_stage":"2","question":"99-42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:00"},
{"history_id":"82","user_id":"56","game_stage":"3","question":"13x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:10"},
{"history_id":"83","user_id":"40","game_stage":"3","question":"47x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:11"},
{"history_id":"84","user_id":"31","game_stage":"2","question":"75-42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:14"},
{"history_id":"85","user_id":"34","game_stage":"2","question":"68-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:15"},
{"history_id":"86","user_id":"41","game_stage":"3","question":"33÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:18"},
{"history_id":"87","user_id":"57","game_stage":"2","question":"39-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:20"},
{"history_id":"88","user_id":"47","game_stage":"2","question":"66+41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:22"},
{"history_id":"89","user_id":"37","game_stage":"4","question":"134+127","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":261,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":127}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":261,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":127}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:27"},
{"history_id":"90","user_id":"39","game_stage":"2","question":"61-47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:34"},
{"history_id":"91","user_id":"43","game_stage":"2","question":"72-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:34"},
{"history_id":"92","user_id":"31","game_stage":"2","question":"56-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:35"},
{"history_id":"93","user_id":"51","game_stage":"3","question":"12x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:37"},
{"history_id":"94","user_id":"36","game_stage":"2","question":"69-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:40"},
{"history_id":"95","user_id":"48","game_stage":"3","question":"92÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:41"},
{"history_id":"96","user_id":"42","game_stage":"2","question":"16+26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:42"},
{"history_id":"97","user_id":"35","game_stage":"3","question":"32x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":388,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:44"},
{"history_id":"98","user_id":"58","game_stage":"3","question":"38÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:45"},
{"history_id":"99","user_id":"44","game_stage":"2","question":"46+3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:49"},
{"history_id":"100","user_id":"49","game_stage":"2","question":"87+2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:56:55"},
{"history_id":"101","user_id":"37","game_stage":"4","question":"50÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:00"},
{"history_id":"102","user_id":"51","game_stage":"3","question":"28x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:01"},
{"history_id":"103","user_id":"35","game_stage":"3","question":"28÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:03"},
{"history_id":"104","user_id":"56","game_stage":"3","question":"16÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:06"},
{"history_id":"105","user_id":"45","game_stage":"3","question":"21x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:10"},
{"history_id":"106","user_id":"48","game_stage":"3","question":"72÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:19"},
{"history_id":"107","user_id":"58","game_stage":"3","question":"2x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:21"},
{"history_id":"108","user_id":"41","game_stage":"3","question":"85÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:22"},
{"history_id":"109","user_id":"51","game_stage":"3","question":"23x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:25"},
{"history_id":"110","user_id":"38","game_stage":"4","question":"68+114","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:26"},
{"history_id":"111","user_id":"32","game_stage":"3","question":"30x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:30"},
{"history_id":"112","user_id":"45","game_stage":"3","question":"14÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:30"},
{"history_id":"113","user_id":"56","game_stage":"3","question":"30x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:31"},
{"history_id":"114","user_id":"50","game_stage":"2","question":"89-45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:43"},
{"history_id":"115","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"90x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:44"},
{"history_id":"116","user_id":"38","game_stage":"4","question":"88x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:48"},
{"history_id":"117","user_id":"57","game_stage":"3","question":"1x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:49"},
{"history_id":"118","user_id":"54","game_stage":"2","question":"91-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:49"},
{"history_id":"119","user_id":"41","game_stage":"3","question":"46x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:53"},
{"history_id":"120","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"17+5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:55"},
{"history_id":"121","user_id":"35","game_stage":"3","question":"87÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:56"},
{"history_id":"122","user_id":"51","game_stage":"3","question":"48÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:57:58"},
{"history_id":"123","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"88x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:13"},
{"history_id":"124","user_id":"32","game_stage":"3","question":"37x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":222,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":222,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:13"},
{"history_id":"125","user_id":"43","game_stage":"3","question":"4x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:17"},
{"history_id":"126","user_id":"53","game_stage":"3","question":"62÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:18"},
{"history_id":"127","user_id":"46","game_stage":"2","question":"2-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:21"},
{"history_id":"128","user_id":"55","game_stage":"2","question":"68+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:21"},
{"history_id":"129","user_id":"41","game_stage":"3","question":"18x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:27"},
{"history_id":"130","user_id":"42","game_stage":"2","question":"80+65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:27"},
{"history_id":"131","user_id":"39","game_stage":"3","question":"31x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:29"},
{"history_id":"132","user_id":"52","game_stage":"2","question":"64+59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:36"},
{"history_id":"133","user_id":"37","game_stage":"6","question":"76+192+54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":192}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":322,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":192}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":322,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:39"},
{"history_id":"134","user_id":"44","game_stage":"2","question":"55-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:39"},
{"history_id":"135","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"75+66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:41"},
{"history_id":"136","user_id":"31","game_stage":"2","question":"8+33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:47"},
{"history_id":"137","user_id":"45","game_stage":"3","question":"93÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:48"},
{"history_id":"138","user_id":"35","game_stage":"3","question":"94÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:56"},
{"history_id":"139","user_id":"58","game_stage":"3","question":"78÷26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:59"},
{"history_id":"140","user_id":"47","game_stage":"2","question":"98-24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:58:59"},
{"history_id":"141","user_id":"38","game_stage":"6","question":"12+143-105","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":143}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":105}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":143}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":105}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:00"},
{"history_id":"142","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"92-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:03"},
{"history_id":"143","user_id":"32","game_stage":"3","question":"96÷48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:03"},
{"history_id":"144","user_id":"56","game_stage":"4","question":"67x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":670,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":670,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:10"},
{"history_id":"145","user_id":"34","game_stage":"3","question":"75÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:15"},
{"history_id":"146","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"53+60","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:18"},
{"history_id":"147","user_id":"48","game_stage":"4","question":"153+37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:20"},
{"history_id":"148","user_id":"54","game_stage":"2","question":"18+28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:21"},
{"history_id":"149","user_id":"36","game_stage":"2","question":"73-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:22"},
{"history_id":"150","user_id":"53","game_stage":"3","question":"42x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:31"},
{"history_id":"151","user_id":"39","game_stage":"3","question":"39÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:35"},
{"history_id":"152","user_id":"49","game_stage":"3","question":"55÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:37"},
{"history_id":"153","user_id":"56","game_stage":"4","question":"72x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:42"},
{"history_id":"154","user_id":"57","game_stage":"3","question":"91÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:44"},
{"history_id":"155","user_id":"37","game_stage":"6","question":"45÷5x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:48"},
{"history_id":"156","user_id":"46","game_stage":"2","question":"57+69","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":69}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":69}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:50"},
{"history_id":"157","user_id":"38","game_stage":"6","question":"183÷3x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:52"},
{"history_id":"158","user_id":"34","game_stage":"3","question":"1x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:52"},
{"history_id":"159","user_id":"54","game_stage":"2","question":"33+88","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 09:59:52"},
{"history_id":"160","user_id":"50","game_stage":"2","question":"32-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:11"},
{"history_id":"161","user_id":"43","game_stage":"3","question":"6÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:11"},
{"history_id":"162","user_id":"40","game_stage":"6","question":"111-75+189","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":189}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":189}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:13"},
{"history_id":"163","user_id":"49","game_stage":"3","question":"69÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:14"},
{"history_id":"164","user_id":"37","game_stage":"6","question":"188÷94x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:18"},
{"history_id":"165","user_id":"48","game_stage":"4","question":"195+125","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":125}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":125}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:21"},
{"history_id":"166","user_id":"41","game_stage":"4","question":"75x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:22"},
{"history_id":"167","user_id":"52","game_stage":"2","question":"38-33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:23"},
{"history_id":"168","user_id":"57","game_stage":"3","question":"88÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:27"},
{"history_id":"169","user_id":"53","game_stage":"3","question":"82÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:28"},
{"history_id":"170","user_id":"38","game_stage":"6","question":"196÷7÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:32"},
{"history_id":"171","user_id":"39","game_stage":"3","question":"60÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:40"},
{"history_id":"172","user_id":"42","game_stage":"2","question":"63-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:41"},
{"history_id":"173","user_id":"41","game_stage":"4","question":"4x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:47"},
{"history_id":"174","user_id":"58","game_stage":"4","question":"90+47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:49"},
{"history_id":"175","user_id":"47","game_stage":"3","question":"13x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:49"},
{"history_id":"176","user_id":"34","game_stage":"3","question":"34x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":306,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":306,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:52"},
{"history_id":"177","user_id":"56","game_stage":"6","question":"184-5+160","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":339,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":160}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":339,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":160}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:55"},
{"history_id":"178","user_id":"37","game_stage":"6","question":"142÷71x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:55"},
{"history_id":"179","user_id":"36","game_stage":"3","question":"63÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:00:57"},
{"history_id":"180","user_id":"43","game_stage":"3","question":"24x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:00"},
{"history_id":"181","user_id":"51","game_stage":"4","question":"5x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:00"},
{"history_id":"182","user_id":"49","game_stage":"3","question":"27÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:01"},
{"history_id":"183","user_id":"33","game_stage":"2","question":"73+30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:02"},
{"history_id":"184","user_id":"31","game_stage":"3","question":"27x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:10"},
{"history_id":"185","user_id":"40","game_stage":"6","question":"106÷2x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":477,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":504,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:13"},
{"history_id":"186","user_id":"35","game_stage":"4","question":"24÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:17"},
{"history_id":"187","user_id":"32","game_stage":"4","question":"81x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:17"},
{"history_id":"188","user_id":"38","game_stage":"6","question":"180-72-83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:23"},
{"history_id":"189","user_id":"47","game_stage":"3","question":"30x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:23"},
{"history_id":"190","user_id":"58","game_stage":"4","question":"155+190","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":345,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":190}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":345,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":190}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:32"},
{"history_id":"191","user_id":"31","game_stage":"3","question":"31x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:34"},
{"history_id":"192","user_id":"46","game_stage":"2","question":"50-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:38"},
{"history_id":"193","user_id":"56","game_stage":"6","question":"194÷2÷97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:41"},
{"history_id":"194","user_id":"51","game_stage":"4","question":"29+140","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":140}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":140}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:41"},
{"history_id":"195","user_id":"41","game_stage":"4","question":"129÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:43"},
{"history_id":"196","user_id":"35","game_stage":"4","question":"176-80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:48"},
{"history_id":"197","user_id":"36","game_stage":"3","question":"22x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:52"},
{"history_id":"198","user_id":"55","game_stage":"2","question":"87-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:55"},
{"history_id":"199","user_id":"58","game_stage":"4","question":"99÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:57"},
{"history_id":"200","user_id":"40","game_stage":"6","question":"172÷86x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:58"},
{"history_id":"201","user_id":"33","game_stage":"3","question":"32÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:01:58"},
{"history_id":"202","user_id":"54","game_stage":"2","question":"93-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:03"},
{"history_id":"203","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"81-39+75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:06"},
{"history_id":"204","user_id":"32","game_stage":"4","question":"187÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:09"},
{"history_id":"205","user_id":"34","game_stage":"3","question":"48x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":336,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":336,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:09"},
{"history_id":"206","user_id":"51","game_stage":"4","question":"91-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:11"},
{"history_id":"207","user_id":"47","game_stage":"3","question":"98÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:13"},
{"history_id":"208","user_id":"35","game_stage":"4","question":"62x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":558,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":558,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:13"},
{"history_id":"209","user_id":"44","game_stage":"3","question":"47x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:13"},
{"history_id":"210","user_id":"53","game_stage":"4","question":"66x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":792,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":792,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:16"},
{"history_id":"211","user_id":"57","game_stage":"4","question":"62-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:17"},
{"history_id":"212","user_id":"45","game_stage":"4","question":"133+10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:23"},
{"history_id":"213","user_id":"33","game_stage":"3","question":"55÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:25"},
{"history_id":"214","user_id":"31","game_stage":"3","question":"34x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":306,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":306,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:31"},
{"history_id":"215","user_id":"39","game_stage":"4","question":"148÷74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":74}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:31"},
{"history_id":"216","user_id":"51","game_stage":"4","question":"86÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:32"},
{"history_id":"217","user_id":"49","game_stage":"4","question":"15+20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:33"},
{"history_id":"218","user_id":"38","game_stage":"7","question":"101+113+287","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":501,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":287}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":501,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":287}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:33"},
{"history_id":"219","user_id":"32","game_stage":"4","question":"148-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:35"},
{"history_id":"220","user_id":"43","game_stage":"4","question":"77-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:39"},
{"history_id":"221","user_id":"34","game_stage":"3","question":"18x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:42"},
{"history_id":"222","user_id":"36","game_stage":"3","question":"48x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":882,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:42"},
{"history_id":"223","user_id":"40","game_stage":"6","question":"150÷2x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:43"},
{"history_id":"224","user_id":"52","game_stage":"2","question":"33-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:46"},
{"history_id":"225","user_id":"56","game_stage":"6","question":"85x10x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":850,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9350,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":850,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":850,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9350,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":850,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:51"},
{"history_id":"226","user_id":"53","game_stage":"4","question":"144-99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:52"},
{"history_id":"227","user_id":"57","game_stage":"4","question":"87+192","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":192}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":192}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:52"},
{"history_id":"228","user_id":"35","game_stage":"4","question":"135-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:55"},
{"history_id":"229","user_id":"45","game_stage":"4","question":"18x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:56"},
{"history_id":"230","user_id":"37","game_stage":"7","question":"187-106+243","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":243}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":243}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:57"},
{"history_id":"231","user_id":"33","game_stage":"3","question":"28÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:02:58"},
{"history_id":"232","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"96+17+153","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":153}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":153}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:02"},
{"history_id":"233","user_id":"32","game_stage":"4","question":"193+82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:03"},
{"history_id":"234","user_id":"39","game_stage":"4","question":"169-68","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":68}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":68}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:04"},
{"history_id":"235","user_id":"40","game_stage":"6","question":"58-26+1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:08"},
{"history_id":"236","user_id":"53","game_stage":"4","question":"3+146","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":146}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":146}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:10"},
{"history_id":"237","user_id":"43","game_stage":"4","question":"196+143","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":339,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":339,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":143}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:11"},
{"history_id":"238","user_id":"38","game_stage":"7","question":"164÷4÷41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:11"},
{"history_id":"239","user_id":"34","game_stage":"3","question":"10x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:14"},
{"history_id":"240","user_id":"57","game_stage":"4","question":"123-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:18"},
{"history_id":"241","user_id":"42","game_stage":"2","question":"95-21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:19"},
{"history_id":"242","user_id":"44","game_stage":"3","question":"40x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:19"},
{"history_id":"243","user_id":"58","game_stage":"6","question":"95+123-160","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":160}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":160}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:23"},
{"history_id":"244","user_id":"35","game_stage":"4","question":"87-61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:24"},
{"history_id":"245","user_id":"36","game_stage":"3","question":"93÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:24"},
{"history_id":"246","user_id":"56","game_stage":"6","question":"50x3x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:25"},
{"history_id":"247","user_id":"41","game_stage":"6","question":"170+46-129","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":129}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":129}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:27"},
{"history_id":"248","user_id":"55","game_stage":"2","question":"83+65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:28"},
{"history_id":"249","user_id":"43","game_stage":"4","question":"60-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:38"},
{"history_id":"250","user_id":"46","game_stage":"3","question":"95÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:41"},
{"history_id":"251","user_id":"52","game_stage":"2","question":"23-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:44"},
{"history_id":"252","user_id":"57","game_stage":"4","question":"6x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:45"},
{"history_id":"253","user_id":"49","game_stage":"4","question":"111-46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":46}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:46"},
{"history_id":"254","user_id":"38","game_stage":"7","question":"12÷2x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:47"},
{"history_id":"255","user_id":"37","game_stage":"7","question":"103x9÷309","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":927,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":927,\"numB\":309}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":927,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":927,\"numB\":309}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:49"},
{"history_id":"256","user_id":"51","game_stage":"6","question":"45-32-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":32}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":32}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:51"},
{"history_id":"257","user_id":"53","game_stage":"4","question":"155-97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:57"},
{"history_id":"258","user_id":"43","game_stage":"4","question":"163+120","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":283,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":120}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":283,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":120}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:03:58"},
{"history_id":"259","user_id":"44","game_stage":"3","question":"60÷30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:02"},
{"history_id":"260","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"67x10x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":670,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8040,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":670,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":670,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9040,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":670,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:03"},
{"history_id":"261","user_id":"41","game_stage":"6","question":"6÷2x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:04"},
{"history_id":"262","user_id":"40","game_stage":"7","question":"22-14+233","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":233}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":233}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:07"},
{"history_id":"263","user_id":"58","game_stage":"6","question":"129÷3÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:08"},
{"history_id":"264","user_id":"54","game_stage":"3","question":"58÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:12"},
{"history_id":"265","user_id":"49","game_stage":"4","question":"116+88","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:15"},
{"history_id":"266","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"42x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:16"},
{"history_id":"267","user_id":"46","game_stage":"3","question":"98÷49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:16"},
{"history_id":"268","user_id":"33","game_stage":"4","question":"141+188","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":188}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":188}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:19"},
{"history_id":"269","user_id":"47","game_stage":"4","question":"63+76","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":76}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":76}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:20"},
{"history_id":"270","user_id":"51","game_stage":"6","question":"50x1x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":550,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":550,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:22"},
{"history_id":"271","user_id":"39","game_stage":"6","question":"140+99-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":239,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":239,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:25"},
{"history_id":"272","user_id":"44","game_stage":"3","question":"26÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:26"},
{"history_id":"273","user_id":"32","game_stage":"6","question":"56+145+16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":145}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":161}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:29"},
{"history_id":"274","user_id":"37","game_stage":"7","question":"225+77+40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":302,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":302,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":302,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":302,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:33"},
{"history_id":"275","user_id":"45","game_stage":"6","question":"101+21-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:33"},
{"history_id":"276","user_id":"56","game_stage":"7","question":"230+139-134","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":369,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":369,\"numB\":134}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:37"},
{"history_id":"277","user_id":"50","game_stage":"2","question":"40+73","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":73}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":73}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:38"},
{"history_id":"278","user_id":"34","game_stage":"4","question":"15÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:41"},
{"history_id":"279","user_id":"49","game_stage":"4","question":"20÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:41"},
{"history_id":"280","user_id":"43","game_stage":"4","question":"132+107","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":239,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":107}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":239,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":107}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:42"},
{"history_id":"281","user_id":"33","game_stage":"4","question":"133+34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:42"},
{"history_id":"282","user_id":"41","game_stage":"6","question":"128÷8x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:43"},
{"history_id":"283","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"98+121","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":121}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":121}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:46"},
{"history_id":"284","user_id":"47","game_stage":"4","question":"29+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:51"},
{"history_id":"285","user_id":"58","game_stage":"6","question":"158÷2x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:57"},
{"history_id":"286","user_id":"40","game_stage":"7","question":"183-86-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:04:59"},
{"history_id":"287","user_id":"46","game_stage":"3","question":"14÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:03"},
{"history_id":"288","user_id":"54","game_stage":"3","question":"90÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:06"},
{"history_id":"289","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"85-18+35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:08"},
{"history_id":"290","user_id":"34","game_stage":"4","question":"93x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":930,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":930,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:10"},
{"history_id":"291","user_id":"51","game_stage":"6","question":"51÷17÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:11"},
{"history_id":"292","user_id":"33","game_stage":"4","question":"161-74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":74}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:12"},
{"history_id":"293","user_id":"38","game_stage":"8","question":"3+75÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:16"},
{"history_id":"294","user_id":"45","game_stage":"6","question":"62÷2x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:18"},
{"history_id":"295","user_id":"42","game_stage":"2","question":"16+32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:21"},
{"history_id":"296","user_id":"43","game_stage":"4","question":"89+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:22"},
{"history_id":"297","user_id":"55","game_stage":"2","question":"9+37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:22"},
{"history_id":"298","user_id":"50","game_stage":"2","question":"71+63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:22"},
{"history_id":"299","user_id":"35","game_stage":"6","question":"180-41+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:23"},
{"history_id":"300","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"146-75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:24"},
{"history_id":"301","user_id":"36","game_stage":"4","question":"92÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:25"},
{"history_id":"302","user_id":"39","game_stage":"6","question":"159÷3x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":636,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":636,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:31"},
{"history_id":"303","user_id":"52","game_stage":"3","question":"60÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:39"},
{"history_id":"304","user_id":"47","game_stage":"4","question":"67-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:39"},
{"history_id":"305","user_id":"53","game_stage":"6","question":"152-81-51","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":51}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":51}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:39"},
{"history_id":"306","user_id":"43","game_stage":"4","question":"1x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:42"},
{"history_id":"307","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"76÷2÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:44"},
{"history_id":"308","user_id":"33","game_stage":"4","question":"162-79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:49"},
{"history_id":"309","user_id":"37","game_stage":"8","question":"169+132÷33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:53"},
{"history_id":"310","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"66+144-87","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":87}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:54"},
{"history_id":"311","user_id":"32","game_stage":"6","question":"194÷97÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:05:59"},
{"history_id":"312","user_id":"40","game_stage":"7","question":"53x16x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":848,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":848,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":848,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":848,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:00"},
{"history_id":"313","user_id":"56","game_stage":"7","question":"74x13x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":962,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11544,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":962,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11544,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:03"},
{"history_id":"314","user_id":"51","game_stage":"6","question":"78÷26÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:04"},
{"history_id":"315","user_id":"38","game_stage":"8","question":"195+47x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":564,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":759,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":564}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":564,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":759,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":564}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:05"},
{"history_id":"316","user_id":"43","game_stage":"4","question":"55÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:06"},
{"history_id":"317","user_id":"58","game_stage":"7","question":"243+234-80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":477,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":234}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":397,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":477,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":477,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":234}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":397,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":477,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:09"},
{"history_id":"318","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"91+50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:09"},
{"history_id":"319","user_id":"34","game_stage":"4","question":"53x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":636,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":636,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:11"},
{"history_id":"320","user_id":"45","game_stage":"6","question":"85x10x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":850,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":850,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":850,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":850,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:16"},
{"history_id":"321","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"59x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":590,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":590,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:18"},
{"history_id":"322","user_id":"38","game_stage":"8","question":"12÷4-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:21"},
{"history_id":"323","user_id":"39","game_stage":"6","question":"117-46-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:22"},
{"history_id":"324","user_id":"36","game_stage":"4","question":"76÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:24"},
{"history_id":"325","user_id":"53","game_stage":"6","question":"39÷3÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:24"},
{"history_id":"326","user_id":"49","game_stage":"6","question":"93+179+100","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":179}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":100}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":179}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:32"},
{"history_id":"327","user_id":"32","game_stage":"6","question":"175÷25÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:37"},
{"history_id":"328","user_id":"37","game_stage":"8","question":"54-196÷49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:40"},
{"history_id":"329","user_id":"34","game_stage":"4","question":"43-35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:41"},
{"history_id":"330","user_id":"58","game_stage":"7","question":"156÷12÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:42"},
{"history_id":"331","user_id":"56","game_stage":"7","question":"215÷5÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":0}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:46"},
{"history_id":"332","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"108-33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:48"},
{"history_id":"333","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"120-87","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":87}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":87}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:48"},
{"history_id":"334","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"191-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:48"},
{"history_id":"335","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"36÷4x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:54"},
{"history_id":"336","user_id":"33","game_stage":"6","question":"144+64-117","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":117}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":117}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:56"},
{"history_id":"337","user_id":"47","game_stage":"4","question":"111-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:56"},
{"history_id":"338","user_id":"39","game_stage":"6","question":"192÷64÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:06:57"},
{"history_id":"339","user_id":"37","game_stage":"8","question":"126-25x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":100}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:00"},
{"history_id":"340","user_id":"35","game_stage":"6","question":"53x8÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":424,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":424,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":424,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":424,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:01"},
{"history_id":"341","user_id":"32","game_stage":"6","question":"22÷11÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:02"},
{"history_id":"342","user_id":"38","game_stage":"8","question":"118-172÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":86}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:05"},
{"history_id":"343","user_id":"40","game_stage":"7","question":"274+136-311","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":410,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":136}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":410,\"numB\":311}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":410,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":136}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":410,\"numB\":311}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:06"},
{"history_id":"344","user_id":"34","game_stage":"4","question":"30x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:08"},
{"history_id":"345","user_id":"36","game_stage":"4","question":"174+149","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":323,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":149}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":323,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":149}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:09"},
{"history_id":"346","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"131+140","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":271,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":140}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":271,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":140}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:10"},
{"history_id":"347","user_id":"53","game_stage":"6","question":"199-9-157","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":157}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":157}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:11"},
{"history_id":"348","user_id":"54","game_stage":"3","question":"6x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:16"},
{"history_id":"349","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"66x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:19"},
{"history_id":"350","user_id":"33","game_stage":"6","question":"1x7x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:20"},
{"history_id":"351","user_id":"47","game_stage":"4","question":"52+38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:21"},
{"history_id":"352","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"38÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:23"},
{"history_id":"353","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"8÷4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:28"},
{"history_id":"354","user_id":"42","game_stage":"2","question":"57-47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:29"},
{"history_id":"355","user_id":"41","game_stage":"7","question":"208-147+177","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":147}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":177}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":147}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":177}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:30"},
{"history_id":"356","user_id":"38","game_stage":"8","question":"94x1+20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:32"},
{"history_id":"357","user_id":"35","game_stage":"6","question":"176-96+100","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":100}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":100}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":196}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:36"},
{"history_id":"358","user_id":"52","game_stage":"3","question":"57÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:37"},
{"history_id":"359","user_id":"58","game_stage":"7","question":"278+290-529","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":290}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":568,\"numB\":529}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":290}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":568,\"numB\":529}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:37"},
{"history_id":"360","user_id":"51","game_stage":"7","question":"290-82+224","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":224}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":442,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":224}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:38"},
{"history_id":"361","user_id":"56","game_stage":"7","question":"117÷3x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:39"},
{"history_id":"362","user_id":"49","game_stage":"6","question":"57÷19x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:40"},
{"history_id":"363","user_id":"33","game_stage":"6","question":"45÷5x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:41"},
{"history_id":"364","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"126-40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:42"},
{"history_id":"365","user_id":"34","game_stage":"4","question":"164+152","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":152}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":152}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:43"},
{"history_id":"366","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"81x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":567,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":567,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:46"},
{"history_id":"367","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"195+173+114","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":368,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":173}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":482,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":368,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":173}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":382,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:48"},
{"history_id":"368","user_id":"45","game_stage":"7","question":"111+88+243","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":442,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":243}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":442,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":243}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:55"},
{"history_id":"369","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"129÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:55"},
{"history_id":"370","user_id":"32","game_stage":"6","question":"174+121-235","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":235}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":235}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:56"},
{"history_id":"371","user_id":"34","game_stage":"4","question":"51+10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:07:56"},
{"history_id":"372","user_id":"43","game_stage":"6","question":"145+118-170","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":263,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":118}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":170}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":118}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":170}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:07"},
{"history_id":"373","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"30x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:13"},
{"history_id":"374","user_id":"56","game_stage":"7","question":"58x6x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":348,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:15"},
{"history_id":"375","user_id":"40","game_stage":"8","question":"161÷7+145","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":145}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":145}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:16"},
{"history_id":"376","user_id":"32","game_stage":"6","question":"84÷2x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:20"},
{"history_id":"377","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"100÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:22"},
{"history_id":"378","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"86+19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:23"},
{"history_id":"379","user_id":"34","game_stage":"4","question":"83-71","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":71}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:23"},
{"history_id":"380","user_id":"51","game_stage":"7","question":"229-112+235","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":229,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":235}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":229,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":235}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:30"},
{"history_id":"381","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"69+135-61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":135}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":135}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:36"},
{"history_id":"382","user_id":"35","game_stage":"6","question":"5+161+177","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":343,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":177}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":343,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":177}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:36"},
{"history_id":"383","user_id":"41","game_stage":"7","question":"103x11÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1133,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1133,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:40"},
{"history_id":"384","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"68+101-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:40"},
{"history_id":"385","user_id":"43","game_stage":"6","question":"161-74+63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:41"},
{"history_id":"386","user_id":"33","game_stage":"7","question":"222+278+113","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":500,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":222,\"numB\":278}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":613,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":500,\"numB\":113}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":500,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":222,\"numB\":278}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":613,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":500,\"numB\":113}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:42"},
{"history_id":"387","user_id":"55","game_stage":"3","question":"87÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:42"},
{"history_id":"388","user_id":"49","game_stage":"6","question":"198+163-149","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":361,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":163}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":361,\"numB\":149}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":361,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":163}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":361,\"numB\":149}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:47"},
{"history_id":"389","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"150÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:49"},
{"history_id":"390","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"159-59-99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:54"},
{"history_id":"391","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"142-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:55"},
{"history_id":"392","user_id":"42","game_stage":"3","question":"64÷32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:08:59"},
{"history_id":"393","user_id":"58","game_stage":"7","question":"149-99+89","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:01"},
{"history_id":"394","user_id":"53","game_stage":"7","question":"176+194+268","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":638,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":268}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":638,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":268}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:03"},
{"history_id":"395","user_id":"36","game_stage":"6","question":"137-55+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:05"},
{"history_id":"396","user_id":"32","game_stage":"6","question":"143+58+191","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":191}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":191}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:05"},
{"history_id":"397","user_id":"40","game_stage":"8","question":"26x8-131","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":131}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":131}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:07"},
{"history_id":"398","user_id":"37","game_stage":"9","question":"151+134÷67","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:09"},
{"history_id":"399","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"24x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:12"},
{"history_id":"400","user_id":"51","game_stage":"7","question":"118÷2÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:13"},
{"history_id":"401","user_id":"54","game_stage":"4","question":"37+98","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":98}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":98}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:14"},
{"history_id":"402","user_id":"33","game_stage":"7","question":"153÷9÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:20"},
{"history_id":"403","user_id":"55","game_stage":"3","question":"34x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:21"},
{"history_id":"404","user_id":"45","game_stage":"7","question":"140x1÷35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:22"},
{"history_id":"405","user_id":"41","game_stage":"7","question":"78÷3x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:25"},
{"history_id":"406","user_id":"43","game_stage":"6","question":"32x4x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":640,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":640,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:33"},
{"history_id":"407","user_id":"40","game_stage":"8","question":"32-52÷26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:38"},
{"history_id":"408","user_id":"31","game_stage":"4","question":"198÷99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:39"},
{"history_id":"409","user_id":"38","game_stage":"9","question":"98x16+189","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1757,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1568,\"numB\":189}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1757,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1568,\"numB\":189}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:39"},
{"history_id":"410","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"223+278+42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":501,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":223,\"numB\":278}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":543,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":501,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":401,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":223,\"numB\":278}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":443,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":401,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:40"},
{"history_id":"411","user_id":"36","game_stage":"6","question":"30x8÷40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:44"},
{"history_id":"412","user_id":"37","game_stage":"9","question":"118-65x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:45"},
{"history_id":"413","user_id":"54","game_stage":"4","question":"181-90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:47"},
{"history_id":"414","user_id":"42","game_stage":"3","question":"7x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:50"},
{"history_id":"415","user_id":"33","game_stage":"7","question":"268-57+205","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":416,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":205}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":416,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":205}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:52"},
{"history_id":"416","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"126÷21x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":189}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:59"},
{"history_id":"417","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"49+196","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":196}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":196}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:09:59"},
{"history_id":"418","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"43+198+8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":198}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":198}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:04"},
{"history_id":"419","user_id":"55","game_stage":"3","question":"32x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:04"},
{"history_id":"420","user_id":"52","game_stage":"3","question":"51÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:04"},
{"history_id":"421","user_id":"58","game_stage":"7","question":"66x16x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1056,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1056,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1056,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1056,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:05"},
{"history_id":"422","user_id":"43","game_stage":"6","question":"22+107+114","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":107}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":107}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:10"},
{"history_id":"423","user_id":"54","game_stage":"4","question":"71+6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:16"},
{"history_id":"424","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"191-69-102","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":102}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":102}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:19"},
{"history_id":"425","user_id":"38","game_stage":"9","question":"96÷16-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:20"},
{"history_id":"426","user_id":"37","game_stage":"9","question":"10÷5+255","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":257,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":255}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":257,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":255}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:21"},
{"history_id":"427","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"56+85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:21"},
{"history_id":"428","user_id":"41","game_stage":"7","question":"241-113-54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:21"},
{"history_id":"429","user_id":"51","game_stage":"7","question":"127-38+12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:22"},
{"history_id":"430","user_id":"36","game_stage":"6","question":"56-12+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:32"},
{"history_id":"431","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"42+256-21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":256}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":277,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":256}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":319,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:35"},
{"history_id":"432","user_id":"42","game_stage":"3","question":"85÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:35"},
{"history_id":"433","user_id":"32","game_stage":"7","question":"221+83+151","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":304,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":304,\"numB\":151}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:36"},
{"history_id":"434","user_id":"45","game_stage":"7","question":"43x6x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2838,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":258,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2838,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":258,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:38"},
{"history_id":"435","user_id":"53","game_stage":"7","question":"98x16÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1568,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":390,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1568,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:41"},
{"history_id":"436","user_id":"55","game_stage":"3","question":"23x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:45"},
{"history_id":"437","user_id":"54","game_stage":"4","question":"44÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:45"},
{"history_id":"438","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"124÷31÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":168}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:50"},
{"history_id":"439","user_id":"31","game_stage":"6","question":"4+142+1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":142}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":142}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:51"},
{"history_id":"440","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"55x7÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":385,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":385,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":385,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":385,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:51"},
{"history_id":"441","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"59+168","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":227,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":168}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":227,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":168}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:10:57"},
{"history_id":"442","user_id":"33","game_stage":"8","question":"113+45÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:01"},
{"history_id":"443","user_id":"58","game_stage":"7","question":"28x13x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":364,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1456,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":364,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":364,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1456,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":364,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:09"},
{"history_id":"444","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"114x15÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1710,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1710,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1730,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1730,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:11"},
{"history_id":"445","user_id":"33","game_stage":"8","question":"45-111÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:23"},
{"history_id":"446","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"136+231-100","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":367,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":231}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":267,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":367,\"numB\":100}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":367,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":231}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":267,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":367,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:24"},
{"history_id":"447","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"193+177","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":177}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":177}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:27"},
{"history_id":"448","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"108÷54÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:28"},
{"history_id":"449","user_id":"52","game_stage":"3","question":"9÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:30"},
{"history_id":"450","user_id":"31","game_stage":"6","question":"6÷2÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:30"},
{"history_id":"451","user_id":"40","game_stage":"9","question":"185+146x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":584,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":769,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":584}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":146}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":330,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:35"},
{"history_id":"452","user_id":"37","game_stage":"10","question":"10x(104-95)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:38"},
{"history_id":"453","user_id":"32","game_stage":"7","question":"146x3÷146","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":438,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":438,\"numB\":146}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":438,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":438,\"numB\":146}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:41"},
{"history_id":"454","user_id":"38","game_stage":"9","question":"1417-127x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1397,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1417,\"numB\":1397}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1290,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1417,\"numB\":127}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1290,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:45"},
{"history_id":"455","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"14÷2x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:46"},
{"history_id":"456","user_id":"43","game_stage":"7","question":"288-110+104","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":110}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":104}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":110}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":104}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:49"},
{"history_id":"457","user_id":"33","game_stage":"8","question":"106+144÷72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:52"},
{"history_id":"458","user_id":"53","game_stage":"7","question":"114÷19x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:11:54"},
{"history_id":"459","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"10÷5x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:01"},
{"history_id":"460","user_id":"31","game_stage":"6","question":"77x10÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":770,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":770,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:05"},
{"history_id":"461","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"53x11÷53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":583,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":583,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":583,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":583,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:12"},
{"history_id":"462","user_id":"55","game_stage":"4","question":"59-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:20"},
{"history_id":"463","user_id":"37","game_stage":"10","question":"9x(160+125)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2565,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":285}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2765,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":285}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:21"},
{"history_id":"464","user_id":"32","game_stage":"7","question":"19+215+140","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":215}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":140}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":215}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":140}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:23"},
{"history_id":"465","user_id":"51","game_stage":"8","question":"137+16x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:25"},
{"history_id":"466","user_id":"38","game_stage":"9","question":"47x6+217","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":499,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":217}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":499,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":217}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:26"},
{"history_id":"467","user_id":"42","game_stage":"4","question":"93-67","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:27"},
{"history_id":"468","user_id":"36","game_stage":"7","question":"149-88-57","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:28"},
{"history_id":"469","user_id":"40","game_stage":"9","question":"81+22x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":323,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":242}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":323,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":242}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:30"},
{"history_id":"470","user_id":"31","game_stage":"6","question":"77÷7÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:30"},
{"history_id":"471","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"189÷63x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":63}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":63}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:40"},
{"history_id":"472","user_id":"52","game_stage":"3","question":"48x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":336,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:41"},
{"history_id":"473","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"195÷3÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:44"},
{"history_id":"474","user_id":"37","game_stage":"10","question":"20÷(8÷2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:45"},
{"history_id":"475","user_id":"55","game_stage":"4","question":"168+141","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":309,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":141}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":309,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":141}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:52"},
{"history_id":"476","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"156÷39x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":580,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":580}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:56"},
{"history_id":"477","user_id":"42","game_stage":"4","question":"37-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:56"},
{"history_id":"478","user_id":"43","game_stage":"7","question":"71x11x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":781,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3905,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":781,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":181,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":905,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:12:59"},
{"history_id":"479","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"108+78-143","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":143}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:02"},
{"history_id":"480","user_id":"37","game_stage":"10","question":"42÷(18÷3)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:12"},
{"history_id":"481","user_id":"58","game_stage":"8","question":"54x12+145","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":648,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":793,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":648,\"numB\":145}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":648,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":793,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":648,\"numB\":145}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:14"},
{"history_id":"482","user_id":"52","game_stage":"3","question":"64÷16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:17"},
{"history_id":"483","user_id":"55","game_stage":"4","question":"170-50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:17"},
{"history_id":"484","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"147-12+38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:22"},
{"history_id":"485","user_id":"51","game_stage":"8","question":"30x11-170","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":330,\"numB\":170}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":330,\"numB\":170}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:22"},
{"history_id":"486","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"54÷9÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:24"},
{"history_id":"487","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"167+215+291","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":382,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":215}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":673,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":382,\"numB\":291}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":383,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":215}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":674,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":383,\"numB\":291}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:25"},
{"history_id":"488","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"175÷35x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":455}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:25"},
{"history_id":"489","user_id":"33","game_stage":"9","question":"16+122÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":122}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:36"},
{"history_id":"490","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"118÷2x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":590,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:37"},
{"history_id":"491","user_id":"32","game_stage":"8","question":"38÷19+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:37"},
{"history_id":"492","user_id":"58","game_stage":"8","question":"24÷3-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:40"},
{"history_id":"493","user_id":"53","game_stage":"7","question":"235÷5÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:42"},
{"history_id":"494","user_id":"55","game_stage":"4","question":"129-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:44"},
{"history_id":"495","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"236+210-95","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":446,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":210}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":446,\"numB\":95}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":541,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":305}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:48"},
{"history_id":"496","user_id":"48","game_stage":"6","question":"44x4x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":880,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":880,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:50"},
{"history_id":"497","user_id":"40","game_stage":"9","question":"99x9-244","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":891,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":647,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":891,\"numB\":244}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":891,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":647,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":891,\"numB\":244}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:55"},
{"history_id":"498","user_id":"52","game_stage":"3","question":"31x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:13:59"},
{"history_id":"499","user_id":"51","game_stage":"8","question":"588-93x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":558,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":588,\"numB\":558}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":558,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":588,\"numB\":558}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:08"},
{"history_id":"500","user_id":"58","game_stage":"8","question":"52+161÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:10"},
{"history_id":"501","user_id":"57","game_stage":"6","question":"136-5-60","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:13"},
{"history_id":"502","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"58x11÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":638,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":638,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":638,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":638,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:26"},
{"history_id":"503","user_id":"52","game_stage":"3","question":"44x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":356,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:30"},
{"history_id":"504","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"116÷2x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":928,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9228,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:32"},
{"history_id":"505","user_id":"32","game_stage":"8","question":"88÷22-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:33"},
{"history_id":"506","user_id":"40","game_stage":"9","question":"99x1-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:38"},
{"history_id":"507","user_id":"32","game_stage":"8","question":"88÷44-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:51"},
{"history_id":"508","user_id":"36","game_stage":"7","question":"296÷2x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2072,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2762,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:53"},
{"history_id":"509","user_id":"33","game_stage":"9","question":"241+265÷53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":265,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":265,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:14:55"},
{"history_id":"510","user_id":"9","game_stage":"2","question":"22+81","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":81}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:43:40"},
{"history_id":"511","user_id":"29","game_stage":"2","question":"60+47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:44:26"},
{"history_id":"512","user_id":"25","game_stage":"2","question":"91+26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:44:41"},
{"history_id":"513","user_id":"9","game_stage":"2","question":"72-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:45:06"},
{"history_id":"514","user_id":"14","game_stage":"2","question":"27-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:45:17"},
{"history_id":"515","user_id":"5","game_stage":"2","question":"66+34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:45:36"},
{"history_id":"516","user_id":"15","game_stage":"2","question":"24-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:45:41"},
{"history_id":"517","user_id":"13","game_stage":"2","question":"52+30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:45:56"},
{"history_id":"518","user_id":"29","game_stage":"2","question":"73+29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:46:12"},
{"history_id":"519","user_id":"25","game_stage":"2","question":"83+58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:46:25"},
{"history_id":"520","user_id":"29","game_stage":"2","question":"18+38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:46:36"},
{"history_id":"521","user_id":"22","game_stage":"2","question":"36-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:46:39"},
{"history_id":"522","user_id":"26","game_stage":"2","question":"37-14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:46:47"},
{"history_id":"523","user_id":"21","game_stage":"2","question":"64+78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:46:50"},
{"history_id":"524","user_id":"23","game_stage":"2","question":"39-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:03"},
{"history_id":"525","user_id":"9","game_stage":"2","question":"56-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:03"},
{"history_id":"526","user_id":"15","game_stage":"2","question":"94-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:09"},
{"history_id":"527","user_id":"11","game_stage":"2","question":"76-22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:20"},
{"history_id":"528","user_id":"20","game_stage":"2","question":"87+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:21"},
{"history_id":"529","user_id":"30","game_stage":"2","question":"65+65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:22"},
{"history_id":"530","user_id":"8","game_stage":"2","question":"74-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:25"},
{"history_id":"531","user_id":"21","game_stage":"2","question":"59-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:25"},
{"history_id":"532","user_id":"13","game_stage":"2","question":"18+56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:27"},
{"history_id":"533","user_id":"12","game_stage":"2","question":"58+22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:28"},
{"history_id":"534","user_id":"28","game_stage":"2","question":"66+88","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:29"},
{"history_id":"535","user_id":"14","game_stage":"2","question":"76+91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:31"},
{"history_id":"536","user_id":"4","game_stage":"2","question":"19+17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:47:43"},
{"history_id":"537","user_id":"24","game_stage":"2","question":"71+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:12"},
{"history_id":"538","user_id":"26","game_stage":"2","question":"55+47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:15"},
{"history_id":"539","user_id":"16","game_stage":"2","question":"49+50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:16"},
{"history_id":"540","user_id":"9","game_stage":"3","question":"12÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:25"},
{"history_id":"541","user_id":"29","game_stage":"2","question":"98-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:29"},
{"history_id":"542","user_id":"22","game_stage":"2","question":"14+52","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":52}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":52}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:30"},
{"history_id":"543","user_id":"23","game_stage":"2","question":"55-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:33"},
{"history_id":"544","user_id":"25","game_stage":"2","question":"39-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:47"},
{"history_id":"545","user_id":"11","game_stage":"2","question":"47+97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:51"},
{"history_id":"546","user_id":"30","game_stage":"2","question":"69+80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:51"},
{"history_id":"547","user_id":"9","game_stage":"3","question":"24x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:57"},
{"history_id":"548","user_id":"6","game_stage":"2","question":"82-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:48:58"},
{"history_id":"549","user_id":"8","game_stage":"2","question":"73+69","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":69}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":69}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:11"},
{"history_id":"550","user_id":"21","game_stage":"2","question":"57+60","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:14"},
{"history_id":"551","user_id":"27","game_stage":"2","question":"70-45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:17"},
{"history_id":"552","user_id":"20","game_stage":"2","question":"33+96","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:18"},
{"history_id":"553","user_id":"7","game_stage":"2","question":"79+78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:24"},
{"history_id":"554","user_id":"9","game_stage":"3","question":"39x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:27"},
{"history_id":"555","user_id":"4","game_stage":"2","question":"37+10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:28"},
{"history_id":"556","user_id":"3","game_stage":"2","question":"6+79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:38"},
{"history_id":"557","user_id":"14","game_stage":"2","question":"2+75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:40"},
{"history_id":"558","user_id":"16","game_stage":"2","question":"75+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:44"},
{"history_id":"559","user_id":"24","game_stage":"2","question":"94-29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:45"},
{"history_id":"560","user_id":"13","game_stage":"2","question":"58-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:46"},
{"history_id":"561","user_id":"15","game_stage":"2","question":"80+18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:49:56"},
{"history_id":"562","user_id":"28","game_stage":"2","question":"15+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:09"},
{"history_id":"563","user_id":"12","game_stage":"2","question":"64+90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:13"},
{"history_id":"564","user_id":"26","game_stage":"2","question":"4+20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:23"},
{"history_id":"565","user_id":"25","game_stage":"3","question":"19x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:26"},
{"history_id":"566","user_id":"11","game_stage":"2","question":"23-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:30"},
{"history_id":"567","user_id":"6","game_stage":"2","question":"52-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:30"},
{"history_id":"568","user_id":"5","game_stage":"2","question":"81-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:34"},
{"history_id":"569","user_id":"27","game_stage":"2","question":"45+45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:41"},
{"history_id":"570","user_id":"30","game_stage":"2","question":"27+19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:42"},
{"history_id":"571","user_id":"23","game_stage":"2","question":"97+13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:45"},
{"history_id":"572","user_id":"7","game_stage":"2","question":"48-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:47"},
{"history_id":"573","user_id":"22","game_stage":"2","question":"43+90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:51"},
{"history_id":"574","user_id":"12","game_stage":"2","question":"82-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:50:54"},
{"history_id":"575","user_id":"3","game_stage":"2","question":"25-22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:08"},
{"history_id":"576","user_id":"11","game_stage":"2","question":"86-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:14"},
{"history_id":"577","user_id":"9","game_stage":"4","question":"92÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:16"},
{"history_id":"578","user_id":"25","game_stage":"3","question":"36x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:22"},
{"history_id":"579","user_id":"4","game_stage":"2","question":"74+57","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:27"},
{"history_id":"580","user_id":"21","game_stage":"2","question":"62-46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":46}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:27"},
{"history_id":"581","user_id":"29","game_stage":"3","question":"6x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:28"},
{"history_id":"582","user_id":"13","game_stage":"3","question":"16÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:33"},
{"history_id":"583","user_id":"16","game_stage":"2","question":"79-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:35"},
{"history_id":"584","user_id":"20","game_stage":"2","question":"74-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:38"},
{"history_id":"585","user_id":"14","game_stage":"3","question":"45x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:49"},
{"history_id":"586","user_id":"5","game_stage":"2","question":"12+15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:49"},
{"history_id":"587","user_id":"9","game_stage":"4","question":"94÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:51"},
{"history_id":"588","user_id":"8","game_stage":"2","question":"51-44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:51"},
{"history_id":"589","user_id":"29","game_stage":"3","question":"42x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:52"},
{"history_id":"590","user_id":"26","game_stage":"3","question":"10÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:51:56"},
{"history_id":"591","user_id":"30","game_stage":"3","question":"45÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:09"},
{"history_id":"592","user_id":"15","game_stage":"2","question":"76-43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:10"},
{"history_id":"593","user_id":"13","game_stage":"3","question":"15x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:21"},
{"history_id":"594","user_id":"29","game_stage":"3","question":"72÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:22"},
{"history_id":"595","user_id":"24","game_stage":"2","question":"89-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:22"},
{"history_id":"596","user_id":"25","game_stage":"3","question":"62÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:26"},
{"history_id":"597","user_id":"11","game_stage":"3","question":"26÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:33"},
{"history_id":"598","user_id":"7","game_stage":"2","question":"21-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:35"},
{"history_id":"599","user_id":"26","game_stage":"3","question":"9x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:37"},
{"history_id":"600","user_id":"14","game_stage":"3","question":"28x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":224,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":464,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:44"},
{"history_id":"601","user_id":"19","game_stage":"2","question":"43+85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:44"},
{"history_id":"602","user_id":"23","game_stage":"3","question":"91÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:44"},
{"history_id":"603","user_id":"27","game_stage":"2","question":"99-47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:49"},
{"history_id":"604","user_id":"12","game_stage":"2","question":"32+80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:49"},
{"history_id":"605","user_id":"22","game_stage":"3","question":"76÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:51"},
{"history_id":"606","user_id":"28","game_stage":"2","question":"67-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:51"},
{"history_id":"607","user_id":"21","game_stage":"3","question":"6x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:53"},
{"history_id":"608","user_id":"4","game_stage":"3","question":"12x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:52:56"},
{"history_id":"609","user_id":"6","game_stage":"2","question":"4-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:00"},
{"history_id":"610","user_id":"26","game_stage":"3","question":"46÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:07"},
{"history_id":"611","user_id":"9","game_stage":"6","question":"137-97+16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:12"},
{"history_id":"612","user_id":"30","game_stage":"3","question":"30x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:13"},
{"history_id":"613","user_id":"11","game_stage":"3","question":"98÷49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:16"},
{"history_id":"614","user_id":"3","game_stage":"2","question":"42-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:17"},
{"history_id":"615","user_id":"4","game_stage":"3","question":"16x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:27"},
{"history_id":"616","user_id":"5","game_stage":"2","question":"27+56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:27"},
{"history_id":"617","user_id":"8","game_stage":"3","question":"48x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:32"},
{"history_id":"618","user_id":"23","game_stage":"3","question":"91÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:35"},
{"history_id":"619","user_id":"13","game_stage":"3","question":"19x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:43"},
{"history_id":"620","user_id":"20","game_stage":"3","question":"55÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:44"},
{"history_id":"621","user_id":"29","game_stage":"4","question":"90-81","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":81}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:45"},
{"history_id":"622","user_id":"9","game_stage":"6","question":"50x4÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":0}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03mis04","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:45"},
{"history_id":"623","user_id":"14","game_stage":"3","question":"57÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:46"},
{"history_id":"624","user_id":"16","game_stage":"3","question":"94÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:46"},
{"history_id":"625","user_id":"21","game_stage":"3","question":"96÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:48"},
{"history_id":"626","user_id":"30","game_stage":"3","question":"14÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:48"},
{"history_id":"627","user_id":"4","game_stage":"3","question":"9x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:53"},
{"history_id":"628","user_id":"11","game_stage":"3","question":"57÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:53:54"},
{"history_id":"629","user_id":"7","game_stage":"3","question":"34÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:02"},
{"history_id":"630","user_id":"22","game_stage":"3","question":"85÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:08"},
{"history_id":"631","user_id":"19","game_stage":"2","question":"69-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:10"},
{"history_id":"632","user_id":"20","game_stage":"3","question":"44÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:12"},
{"history_id":"633","user_id":"10","game_stage":"2","question":"20+85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:13"},
{"history_id":"634","user_id":"15","game_stage":"2","question":"30-21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:16"},
{"history_id":"635","user_id":"25","game_stage":"4","question":"34x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":340,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":340,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:17"},
{"history_id":"636","user_id":"23","game_stage":"3","question":"25x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:28"},
{"history_id":"637","user_id":"7","game_stage":"3","question":"86÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:29"},
{"history_id":"638","user_id":"29","game_stage":"4","question":"175÷35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:29"},
{"history_id":"639","user_id":"16","game_stage":"3","question":"40x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:32"},
{"history_id":"640","user_id":"9","game_stage":"6","question":"176-7+64","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:33"},
{"history_id":"641","user_id":"14","game_stage":"3","question":"96÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:38"},
{"history_id":"642","user_id":"28","game_stage":"3","question":"26÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:44"},
{"history_id":"643","user_id":"21","game_stage":"3","question":"21x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:51"},
{"history_id":"644","user_id":"25","game_stage":"4","question":"128-96","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:54:55"},
{"history_id":"645","user_id":"8","game_stage":"3","question":"42x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:00"},
{"history_id":"646","user_id":"22","game_stage":"3","question":"34x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:02"},
{"history_id":"647","user_id":"29","game_stage":"4","question":"186÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:04"},
{"history_id":"648","user_id":"12","game_stage":"3","question":"70÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:05"},
{"history_id":"649","user_id":"7","game_stage":"3","question":"68÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:06"},
{"history_id":"650","user_id":"3","game_stage":"3","question":"4x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:08"},
{"history_id":"651","user_id":"5","game_stage":"3","question":"57÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:21"},
{"history_id":"652","user_id":"13","game_stage":"4","question":"135-77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:22"},
{"history_id":"653","user_id":"4","game_stage":"4","question":"97-84","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":84}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":84}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:22"},
{"history_id":"654","user_id":"26","game_stage":"4","question":"181-43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:26"},
{"history_id":"655","user_id":"9","game_stage":"7","question":"178-117-47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":117}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":117}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:34"},
{"history_id":"656","user_id":"24","game_stage":"2","question":"57-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:34"},
{"history_id":"657","user_id":"11","game_stage":"4","question":"161-81","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":81}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:36"},
{"history_id":"658","user_id":"30","game_stage":"4","question":"85-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:36"},
{"history_id":"659","user_id":"8","game_stage":"3","question":"41x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:36"},
{"history_id":"660","user_id":"25","game_stage":"4","question":"23+126","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":126}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":126}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:42"},
{"history_id":"661","user_id":"12","game_stage":"3","question":"62÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:44"},
{"history_id":"662","user_id":"10","game_stage":"2","question":"56-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:47"},
{"history_id":"663","user_id":"16","game_stage":"3","question":"57÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:48"},
{"history_id":"664","user_id":"23","game_stage":"4","question":"4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:51"},
{"history_id":"665","user_id":"26","game_stage":"4","question":"35÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:53"},
{"history_id":"666","user_id":"13","game_stage":"4","question":"159÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:55"},
{"history_id":"667","user_id":"4","game_stage":"4","question":"78x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":624,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":624,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:56"},
{"history_id":"668","user_id":"3","game_stage":"3","question":"94÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:55:58"},
{"history_id":"669","user_id":"20","game_stage":"3","question":"20x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:01"},
{"history_id":"670","user_id":"6","game_stage":"3","question":"5x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:04"},
{"history_id":"671","user_id":"27","game_stage":"3","question":"46÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:04"},
{"history_id":"672","user_id":"15","game_stage":"2","question":"21-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:05"},
{"history_id":"673","user_id":"5","game_stage":"3","question":"34x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":306,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":306,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:06"},
{"history_id":"674","user_id":"9","game_stage":"7","question":"3x8÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:08"},
{"history_id":"675","user_id":"29","game_stage":"6","question":"50+165-100","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":165}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":100}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":165}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:11"},
{"history_id":"676","user_id":"12","game_stage":"3","question":"33÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:12"},
{"history_id":"677","user_id":"11","game_stage":"4","question":"67x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":737,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":737,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:13"},
{"history_id":"678","user_id":"28","game_stage":"3","question":"51÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:18"},
{"history_id":"679","user_id":"19","game_stage":"2","question":"22+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:20"},
{"history_id":"680","user_id":"13","game_stage":"4","question":"27÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:21"},
{"history_id":"681","user_id":"4","game_stage":"4","question":"11+36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:23"},
{"history_id":"682","user_id":"26","game_stage":"4","question":"61x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":793,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":793,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:28"},
{"history_id":"683","user_id":"21","game_stage":"4","question":"113+149","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":262,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":149}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":262,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":149}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:29"},
{"history_id":"684","user_id":"5","game_stage":"3","question":"72÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:38"},
{"history_id":"685","user_id":"3","game_stage":"3","question":"10÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:41"},
{"history_id":"686","user_id":"7","game_stage":"4","question":"51x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:43"},
{"history_id":"687","user_id":"22","game_stage":"4","question":"120-75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:46"},
{"history_id":"688","user_id":"24","game_stage":"2","question":"49-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:50"},
{"history_id":"689","user_id":"29","game_stage":"6","question":"25x8÷25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:51"},
{"history_id":"690","user_id":"27","game_stage":"3","question":"85÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:57"},
{"history_id":"691","user_id":"23","game_stage":"4","question":"124-63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:56:57"},
{"history_id":"692","user_id":"21","game_stage":"4","question":"53x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":371,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":371,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:00"},
{"history_id":"693","user_id":"14","game_stage":"4","question":"44-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:04"},
{"history_id":"694","user_id":"18","game_stage":"2","question":"46+21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:09"},
{"history_id":"695","user_id":"30","game_stage":"4","question":"42x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:10"},
{"history_id":"696","user_id":"6","game_stage":"3","question":"20÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:10"},
{"history_id":"697","user_id":"16","game_stage":"4","question":"38÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:13"},
{"history_id":"698","user_id":"28","game_stage":"3","question":"48x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:16"},
{"history_id":"699","user_id":"22","game_stage":"4","question":"80+50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:21"},
{"history_id":"700","user_id":"7","game_stage":"4","question":"47x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":423,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":423,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:21"},
{"history_id":"701","user_id":"29","game_stage":"6","question":"42÷14÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:27"},
{"history_id":"702","user_id":"21","game_stage":"4","question":"29-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:28"},
{"history_id":"703","user_id":"23","game_stage":"4","question":"74÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:29"},
{"history_id":"704","user_id":"9","game_stage":"7","question":"132+141+83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":273,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":356,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":273,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":356,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:31"},
{"history_id":"705","user_id":"25","game_stage":"6","question":"147+176+23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":323,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":176}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":346,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":323,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":323,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":176}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":346,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":323,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:31"},
{"history_id":"706","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"159+20-73","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":73}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":73}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:32"},
{"history_id":"707","user_id":"30","game_stage":"4","question":"62-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:33"},
{"history_id":"708","user_id":"20","game_stage":"4","question":"11+144","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":144}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":144}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:35"},
{"history_id":"709","user_id":"8","game_stage":"4","question":"89x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":801,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":801,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:35"},
{"history_id":"710","user_id":"14","game_stage":"4","question":"39x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:39"},
{"history_id":"711","user_id":"4","game_stage":"6","question":"23+114-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":114}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":114}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:41"},
{"history_id":"712","user_id":"27","game_stage":"3","question":"29x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:42"},
{"history_id":"713","user_id":"16","game_stage":"4","question":"4-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:44"},
{"history_id":"714","user_id":"15","game_stage":"3","question":"21x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:44"},
{"history_id":"715","user_id":"5","game_stage":"3","question":"30x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:45"},
{"history_id":"716","user_id":"6","game_stage":"3","question":"42x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":378,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":378,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:49"},
{"history_id":"717","user_id":"22","game_stage":"4","question":"51÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:53"},
{"history_id":"718","user_id":"13","game_stage":"6","question":"198+129+62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":327,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":389,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":327,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":327,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":389,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":327,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:55"},
{"history_id":"719","user_id":"30","game_stage":"4","question":"148+141","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":141}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":141}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:57:57"},
{"history_id":"720","user_id":"12","game_stage":"4","question":"32x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:04"},
{"history_id":"721","user_id":"14","game_stage":"4","question":"86x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":946,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":860,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:05"},
{"history_id":"722","user_id":"5","game_stage":"3","question":"11x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:07"},
{"history_id":"723","user_id":"8","game_stage":"4","question":"147+168","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":168}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":168}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:09"},
{"history_id":"724","user_id":"10","game_stage":"2","question":"70-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:10"},
{"history_id":"725","user_id":"16","game_stage":"4","question":"115÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:11"},
{"history_id":"726","user_id":"20","game_stage":"4","question":"175+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:17"},
{"history_id":"727","user_id":"25","game_stage":"6","question":"165÷15x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:17"},
{"history_id":"728","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"36÷4÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:19"},
{"history_id":"729","user_id":"4","game_stage":"6","question":"154÷14x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:19"},
{"history_id":"730","user_id":"15","game_stage":"3","question":"5x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:25"},
{"history_id":"731","user_id":"14","game_stage":"4","question":"78÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:29"},
{"history_id":"732","user_id":"19","game_stage":"3","question":"19x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:30"},
{"history_id":"733","user_id":"5","game_stage":"3","question":"22÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:31"},
{"history_id":"734","user_id":"3","game_stage":"4","question":"77+165","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":165}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":165}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:32"},
{"history_id":"735","user_id":"30","game_stage":"4","question":"153÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:36"},
{"history_id":"736","user_id":"13","game_stage":"6","question":"44x6x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1584,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1584,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:40"},
{"history_id":"737","user_id":"18","game_stage":"2","question":"76-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:42"},
{"history_id":"738","user_id":"29","game_stage":"7","question":"210-43+127","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":127}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":127}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:47"},
{"history_id":"739","user_id":"8","game_stage":"4","question":"191+122","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":122}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":122}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:47"},
{"history_id":"740","user_id":"24","game_stage":"2","question":"91-45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:47"},
{"history_id":"741","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"85÷5+61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:50"},
{"history_id":"742","user_id":"12","game_stage":"4","question":"53x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:51"},
{"history_id":"743","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"196-53-90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:52"},
{"history_id":"744","user_id":"4","game_stage":"6","question":"68+186+178","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":254,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":178}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":254,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":463,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":178}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:53"},
{"history_id":"745","user_id":"25","game_stage":"6","question":"88÷11÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:54"},
{"history_id":"746","user_id":"14","game_stage":"4","question":"106÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:58:54"},
{"history_id":"747","user_id":"3","game_stage":"4","question":"107-52","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":52}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":52}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:03"},
{"history_id":"748","user_id":"13","game_stage":"6","question":"85-43-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:06"},
{"history_id":"749","user_id":"4","game_stage":"6","question":"20x4÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:12"},
{"history_id":"750","user_id":"15","game_stage":"3","question":"46x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:13"},
{"history_id":"751","user_id":"30","game_stage":"4","question":"76x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:15"},
{"history_id":"752","user_id":"25","game_stage":"6","question":"20÷4÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:17"},
{"history_id":"753","user_id":"26","game_stage":"6","question":"41-12+113","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":113}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":142}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:18"},
{"history_id":"754","user_id":"12","game_stage":"4","question":"138÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:23"},
{"history_id":"755","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"27÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:28"},
{"history_id":"756","user_id":"3","game_stage":"4","question":"48-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:35"},
{"history_id":"757","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"195-87x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:37"},
{"history_id":"758","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"191-48-94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:38"},
{"history_id":"759","user_id":"29","game_stage":"7","question":"117÷13x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:40"},
{"history_id":"760","user_id":"6","game_stage":"4","question":"108-81","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":81}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:41"},
{"history_id":"761","user_id":"16","game_stage":"6","question":"44+122+186","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":122}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":186}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":122}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":186}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:48"},
{"history_id":"762","user_id":"22","game_stage":"6","question":"131+30+5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":30}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":30}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:52"},
{"history_id":"763","user_id":"20","game_stage":"6","question":"163+56+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":56}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":56}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 10:59:54"},
{"history_id":"764","user_id":"5","game_stage":"4","question":"29-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:01"},
{"history_id":"765","user_id":"19","game_stage":"3","question":"88÷44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:06"},
{"history_id":"766","user_id":"26","game_stage":"6","question":"60+90-74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":90}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":74}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":76}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:10"},
{"history_id":"767","user_id":"3","game_stage":"4","question":"166÷83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:11"},
{"history_id":"768","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"328-95x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":328,\"numB\":285}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":328,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":699,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:11"},
{"history_id":"769","user_id":"7","game_stage":"6","question":"69+16+82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:13"},
{"history_id":"770","user_id":"28","game_stage":"4","question":"6+189","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":189}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":189}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:16"},
{"history_id":"771","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"38÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:16"},
{"history_id":"772","user_id":"23","game_stage":"6","question":"169-66-91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:17"},
{"history_id":"773","user_id":"16","game_stage":"6","question":"22÷11x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:18"},
{"history_id":"774","user_id":"14","game_stage":"6","question":"159-45-81","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":81}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:22"},
{"history_id":"775","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"104-45-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:25"},
{"history_id":"776","user_id":"8","game_stage":"6","question":"69-53-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:27"},
{"history_id":"777","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"177-7+95","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":265,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":95}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:28"},
{"history_id":"778","user_id":"29","game_stage":"7","question":"14x14x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:28"},
{"history_id":"779","user_id":"6","game_stage":"4","question":"194-99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:30"},
{"history_id":"780","user_id":"17","game_stage":"2","question":"91-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:31"},
{"history_id":"781","user_id":"5","game_stage":"4","question":"146-50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:34"},
{"history_id":"782","user_id":"4","game_stage":"7","question":"55+174+124","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":174}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":353,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":229,\"numB\":124}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":174}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":353,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":229,\"numB\":124}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:35"},
{"history_id":"783","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"51+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:41"},
{"history_id":"784","user_id":"30","game_stage":"6","question":"168-38-58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:44"},
{"history_id":"785","user_id":"19","game_stage":"3","question":"15x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:44"},
{"history_id":"786","user_id":"25","game_stage":"7","question":"267+4-115","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":271,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":271,\"numB\":115}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":271,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":271,\"numB\":115}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:45"},
{"history_id":"787","user_id":"3","game_stage":"4","question":"67x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:47"},
{"history_id":"788","user_id":"24","game_stage":"3","question":"93÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:50"},
{"history_id":"789","user_id":"22","game_stage":"6","question":"91÷13x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:50"},
{"history_id":"790","user_id":"7","game_stage":"6","question":"58x3x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:51"},
{"history_id":"791","user_id":"13","game_stage":"7","question":"256-81-113","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":113}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":113}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:56"},
{"history_id":"792","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"140÷7÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:56"},
{"history_id":"793","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"905-80x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":880,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":905,\"numB\":880}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":825,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":905,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9075,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":825,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:00:56"},
{"history_id":"794","user_id":"4","game_stage":"7","question":"24÷4x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:00"},
{"history_id":"795","user_id":"28","game_stage":"4","question":"95÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:00"},
{"history_id":"796","user_id":"5","game_stage":"4","question":"32+10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:01"},
{"history_id":"797","user_id":"15","game_stage":"4","question":"123-24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:04"},
{"history_id":"798","user_id":"6","game_stage":"4","question":"116+26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:04"},
{"history_id":"799","user_id":"16","game_stage":"6","question":"58x11x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":638,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4466,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":638,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4466,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:05"},
{"history_id":"800","user_id":"23","game_stage":"6","question":"64x8x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":512,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":512,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:09"},
{"history_id":"801","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"115-83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:10"},
{"history_id":"802","user_id":"20","game_stage":"6","question":"58x4÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:11"},
{"history_id":"803","user_id":"14","game_stage":"6","question":"134+76-144","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":76}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":144}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":76}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":144}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:12"},
{"history_id":"804","user_id":"7","game_stage":"6","question":"81÷9x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:16"},
{"history_id":"805","user_id":"10","game_stage":"2","question":"96-33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:17"},
{"history_id":"806","user_id":"30","game_stage":"6","question":"56÷4x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:17"},
{"history_id":"807","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"170+37-96","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":207,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":207,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:20"},
{"history_id":"808","user_id":"26","game_stage":"6","question":"39-37+161","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":161}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":198}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:25"},
{"history_id":"809","user_id":"18","game_stage":"2","question":"48+67","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:32"},
{"history_id":"810","user_id":"15","game_stage":"4","question":"57+20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:33"},
{"history_id":"811","user_id":"12","game_stage":"7","question":"285-57+99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":228,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":327,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:34"},
{"history_id":"812","user_id":"24","game_stage":"3","question":"92÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:36"},
{"history_id":"813","user_id":"8","game_stage":"6","question":"96÷4x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:39"},
{"history_id":"814","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"46+80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:44"},
{"history_id":"815","user_id":"22","game_stage":"6","question":"78x2÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:48"},
{"history_id":"816","user_id":"28","game_stage":"4","question":"76x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:51"},
{"history_id":"817","user_id":"6","game_stage":"4","question":"86x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":860,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:53"},
{"history_id":"818","user_id":"13","game_stage":"7","question":"144÷24÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:58"},
{"history_id":"819","user_id":"14","game_stage":"6","question":"33+181+91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":181}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":181}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:58"},
{"history_id":"820","user_id":"23","game_stage":"6","question":"186+173+158","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":359,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":173}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":517,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":359,\"numB\":158}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":359,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":173}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":517,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":359,\"numB\":158}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:01:59"},
{"history_id":"821","user_id":"4","game_stage":"7","question":"33x15x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":495,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7425,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":495,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":495,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7425,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":495,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:01"},
{"history_id":"822","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"95x11÷209","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1045,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1045,\"numB\":209}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":209}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:02"},
{"history_id":"823","user_id":"29","game_stage":"8","question":"40x4+76","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":76}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":76}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:06"},
{"history_id":"824","user_id":"26","game_stage":"6","question":"56+144-131","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":131}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":131}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:12"},
{"history_id":"825","user_id":"15","game_stage":"4","question":"168-54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:12"},
{"history_id":"826","user_id":"12","game_stage":"7","question":"267-106-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:12"},
{"history_id":"827","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"156+24-158","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":158}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":158}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:16"},
{"history_id":"828","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"165-85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:17"},
{"history_id":"829","user_id":"16","game_stage":"7","question":"221+54-199","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":275,\"numB\":199}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":275,\"numB\":199}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:18"},
{"history_id":"830","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"160+188+12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":188}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":348,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":188}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":348,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:23"},
{"history_id":"831","user_id":"25","game_stage":"7","question":"69x16÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1104,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1104,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:26"},
{"history_id":"832","user_id":"30","game_stage":"6","question":"44+198-177","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":198}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":242,\"numB\":177}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":198}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":242,\"numB\":177}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:28"},
{"history_id":"833","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"100+26x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":334,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":234}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:28"},
{"history_id":"834","user_id":"6","game_stage":"4","question":"190+169","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":359,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":169}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":359,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":169}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:29"},
{"history_id":"835","user_id":"3","game_stage":"6","question":"183+136-211","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":319,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":136}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":319,\"numB\":211}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":322,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":136}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":322,\"numB\":211}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:30"},
{"history_id":"836","user_id":"29","game_stage":"8","question":"29-4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:32"},
{"history_id":"837","user_id":"24","game_stage":"3","question":"24x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:36"},
{"history_id":"838","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"195+5+59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":259,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":259,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:38"},
{"history_id":"839","user_id":"7","game_stage":"7","question":"170-141-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":122}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:47"},
{"history_id":"840","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"46÷2x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:49"},
{"history_id":"841","user_id":"17","game_stage":"2","question":"69+9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:52"},
{"history_id":"842","user_id":"13","game_stage":"7","question":"291÷3÷97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":291,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":291,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:54"},
{"history_id":"843","user_id":"8","game_stage":"6","question":"198÷66x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:02:58"},
{"history_id":"844","user_id":"16","game_stage":"7","question":"81÷3÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:02"},
{"history_id":"845","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"118+8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:02"},
{"history_id":"846","user_id":"26","game_stage":"6","question":"37x11÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":407,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":407,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":407,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":407,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:03"},
{"history_id":"847","user_id":"14","game_stage":"6","question":"63x12÷54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":756,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":756,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":756,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":756,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:06"},
{"history_id":"848","user_id":"3","game_stage":"6","question":"150+2+116","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":116}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":116}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:06"},
{"history_id":"849","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"120÷2x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:07"},
{"history_id":"850","user_id":"29","game_stage":"8","question":"128÷2+61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:08"},
{"history_id":"851","user_id":"6","game_stage":"4","question":"108-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:10"},
{"history_id":"852","user_id":"12","game_stage":"7","question":"176-39-25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:12"},
{"history_id":"853","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"68x9+129","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":612,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":741,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":612,\"numB\":129}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":612,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":741,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":612,\"numB\":129}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:15"},
{"history_id":"854","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"42÷14÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:15"},
{"history_id":"855","user_id":"23","game_stage":"7","question":"41-22-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:20"},
{"history_id":"856","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"9+19x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":76}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:21"},
{"history_id":"857","user_id":"7","game_stage":"7","question":"275-11+48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":275,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":275,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:23"},
{"history_id":"858","user_id":"25","game_stage":"7","question":"195-140-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":140}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":140}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:26"},
{"history_id":"859","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"131+172","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":303,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":303,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:35"},
{"history_id":"860","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"27x5-124","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":124}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":124}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:41"},
{"history_id":"861","user_id":"26","game_stage":"6","question":"58x12÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":696,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:44"},
{"history_id":"862","user_id":"16","game_stage":"7","question":"53x9÷159","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":477,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":477,\"numB\":159}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":477,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":477,\"numB\":159}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:47"},
{"history_id":"863","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"134÷2x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:48"},
{"history_id":"864","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"171÷3÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:03:51"},
{"history_id":"865","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"143+175÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:02"},
{"history_id":"866","user_id":"22","game_stage":"7","question":"173+281+62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":454,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":281}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":516,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":454,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":454,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":281}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":516,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":454,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:02"},
{"history_id":"867","user_id":"27","game_stage":"4","question":"154÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:02"},
{"history_id":"868","user_id":"24","game_stage":"4","question":"142+198","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":340,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":198}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":340,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":198}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:10"},
{"history_id":"869","user_id":"23","game_stage":"7","question":"285÷5x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":570,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":570,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:13"},
{"history_id":"870","user_id":"15","game_stage":"6","question":"177+16-72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":121}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:14"},
{"history_id":"871","user_id":"11","game_stage":"6","question":"119+3+89","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:22"},
{"history_id":"872","user_id":"7","game_stage":"7","question":"263-133-86","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":133}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:24"},
{"history_id":"873","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"48-123÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:25"},
{"history_id":"874","user_id":"10","game_stage":"3","question":"35÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:35"},
{"history_id":"875","user_id":"24","game_stage":"4","question":"37x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:41"},
{"history_id":"876","user_id":"3","game_stage":"6","question":"55x8÷55","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":440,\"numB\":55}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":440,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:42"},
{"history_id":"877","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"52÷4-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:04:46"},
{"history_id":"878","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"72-5+130","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":197,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":130}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":197,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:00"},
{"history_id":"879","user_id":"10","game_stage":"3","question":"28x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:04"},
{"history_id":"880","user_id":"24","game_stage":"4","question":"9x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:04"},
{"history_id":"881","user_id":"23","game_stage":"7","question":"27+133+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":133}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":133}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:07"},
{"history_id":"882","user_id":"15","game_stage":"6","question":"178-70-68","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":68}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:12"},
{"history_id":"883","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"129÷43+130","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":130}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:15"},
{"history_id":"884","user_id":"14","game_stage":"6","question":"40+14+9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:23"},
{"history_id":"885","user_id":"3","game_stage":"6","question":"105÷21x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:30"},
{"history_id":"886","user_id":"12","game_stage":"7","question":"70-31-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:31"},
{"history_id":"887","user_id":"27","game_stage":"6","question":"33-21-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:38"},
{"history_id":"888","user_id":"11","game_stage":"7","question":"263-135-25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":135}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":135}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:47"},
{"history_id":"889","user_id":"29","game_stage":"9","question":"103+93x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":465,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":465}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":465,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":465}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:50"},
{"history_id":"890","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"173+184+79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":357,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":436,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":357,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":357,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":436,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":357,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:05:54"},
{"history_id":"891","user_id":"20","game_stage":"6","question":"144-58+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":135}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:03"},
{"history_id":"892","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"155+165÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:05"},
{"history_id":"893","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"89x10÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":890,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":890,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":890,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":890,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:15"},
{"history_id":"894","user_id":"17","game_stage":"2","question":"10+58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:16"},
{"history_id":"895","user_id":"14","game_stage":"6","question":"44x12x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":528,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":528,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":528,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3694,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":528,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:18"},
{"history_id":"896","user_id":"10","game_stage":"3","question":"75÷25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:21"},
{"history_id":"897","user_id":"27","game_stage":"6","question":"41-23-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:25"},
{"history_id":"898","user_id":"20","game_stage":"6","question":"20+42+118","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:29"},
{"history_id":"899","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"16x5+104","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":104}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":104}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:29"},
{"history_id":"900","user_id":"15","game_stage":"6","question":"188-48+124","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":124}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":124}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:39"},
{"history_id":"901","user_id":"25","game_stage":"8","question":"85+140÷35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":140}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:49"},
{"history_id":"902","user_id":"14","game_stage":"6","question":"108÷9x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:50"},
{"history_id":"903","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"26-51÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:50"},
{"history_id":"904","user_id":"11","game_stage":"7","question":"7x12x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:06:55"},
{"history_id":"905","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"112÷2x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:07:04"},
{"history_id":"906","user_id":"4","game_stage":"8","question":"818-90x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":810,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":818,\"numB\":810}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":810,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":818,\"numB\":810}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:07:15"},
{"history_id":"907","user_id":"14","game_stage":"6","question":"148÷74x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:07:17"},
{"history_id":"908","user_id":"25","game_stage":"8","question":"9x13+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:07:21"},
{"history_id":"909","user_id":"15","game_stage":"6","question":"24x3x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:07:25"},
{"history_id":"910","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"28÷14÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:07:26"},
{"history_id":"911","user_id":"11","game_stage":"7","question":"274+243-392","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":517,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":243}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":517,\"numB\":392}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":517,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":243}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":517,\"numB\":392}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:07:52"},
{"history_id":"912","user_id":"15","game_stage":"6","question":"72÷2÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:07:57"},
{"history_id":"913","user_id":"10","game_stage":"4","question":"18x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:08:24"},
{"history_id":"914","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"62x13x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":806,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8866,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":806,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":886,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":143}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:08:25"},
{"history_id":"915","user_id":"22","game_stage":"7","question":"133x13÷247","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1729,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1729,\"numB\":247}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1729,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1729,\"numB\":247}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:08:39"},
{"history_id":"916","user_id":"10","game_stage":"4","question":"15x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:08:45"},
{"history_id":"917","user_id":"4","game_stage":"9","question":"68+12x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":132}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":880,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-19 11:09:06"},
{"history_id":"918","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8def\u4e0a\u6709\u4e00\u5806\u77f3\u982d\u64cb\u4f4f\u53bb\u8def\uff0c\u9700\u8981\u5c07\u77f3\u982d\u79fb\u958b\u624d\u80fd\u884c\u8d70\uff0c\u5df2\u77e5\u7e3d\u5171\u670941\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u67099\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u4e00\u6b21\u6700\u591a\u53ea\u80fd\u642c\u904b123\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u7e3d\u5171\u8981\u642c\u904b\u5e7e\u6b21\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"41x9÷123","userAns_obj":"41x9÷123","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 01:55:13"},
{"history_id":"919","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u6dd8\u6c70\u8c6c\u8cb7\u4e8664\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u56de\u4f86\uff0c\u6bcf4\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u6210\u4e00\u5305\uff0c\u8c6c\u72d7\u72d7\u770b\u5230\u9905\u4e7e\u60f3\u5403\uff0c\u65bc\u662f\u5077\u5077\u62ff\u8d70\u4e864\u5305\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6dd8\u6c70\u8c6c\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"64÷4-4","userAns_obj":"64÷4-4","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 01:55:58"},
{"history_id":"920","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u5abd\u5abd\u5230\u9eb5\u5305\u5e97\u8cb7\u4e8681\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff0c\u7559\u4e0b41\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\u653e\u5bb6\u4e2d\uff0c\u5176\u4ed6\u5e73\u5206\u7d665\u500b\u5de6\u53f3\u9130\u5c45\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u500b\u9130\u5c45\u6703\u62ff\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"(81-41)÷5","userAns_obj":"(81-41)÷5","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 01:56:13"},
{"history_id":"924","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"15÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 07:56:05"},
{"history_id":"925","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"24x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 07:56:33"},
{"history_id":"926","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"36x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-19 07:57:00"},
{"history_id":"927","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"74+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:38:29"},
{"history_id":"928","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"78+35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:39:41"},
{"history_id":"929","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"69-35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:40:01"},
{"history_id":"930","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"11+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:40:12"},
{"history_id":"931","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"96-40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:42:40"},
{"history_id":"932","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"33÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:46:47"},
{"history_id":"933","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"10÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:47:00"},
{"history_id":"934","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"99÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:47:49"},
{"history_id":"935","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"32÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:48:26"},
{"history_id":"936","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"37x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:49:33"},
{"history_id":"937","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"26x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 02:50:33"},
{"history_id":"938","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"19x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:07:03"},
{"history_id":"939","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"1+120","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":120}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":120}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:09:22"},
{"history_id":"940","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"75x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:09:46"},
{"history_id":"941","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"155-41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:10:11"},
{"history_id":"942","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"194-75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:11:00"},
{"history_id":"943","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"104-59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:11:26"},
{"history_id":"944","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"171+174","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":345,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":345,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:11:48"},
{"history_id":"945","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"138-77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:12:29"},
{"history_id":"946","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"135+179","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":314,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":179}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":179}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:12:44"},
{"history_id":"947","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"98-48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:13:00"},
{"history_id":"948","user_id":"1","game_stage":"4","question":"159÷53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:13:18"},
{"history_id":"949","user_id":"1","game_stage":"6","question":"137+100+66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":100}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":303,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":100}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":303,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:14:58"},
{"history_id":"950","user_id":"1","game_stage":"6","question":"188÷2x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":846,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":842,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:15:21"},
{"history_id":"951","user_id":"1","game_stage":"6","question":"16x7x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1456,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:31:21"},
{"history_id":"952","user_id":"1","game_stage":"6","question":"161÷7÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:31:43"},
{"history_id":"953","user_id":"1","game_stage":"6","question":"68+184+140","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":140}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":140}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:32:05"},
{"history_id":"954","user_id":"1","game_stage":"7","question":"290-44-227","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":246,\"numB\":227}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":227}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:33:04"},
{"history_id":"955","user_id":"1","game_stage":"7","question":"185+185-217","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":185}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":217}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":185}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":217}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:33:40"},
{"history_id":"956","user_id":"1","game_stage":"7","question":"152÷2÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:34:05"},
{"history_id":"957","user_id":"1","game_stage":"7","question":"71x12÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":852,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":284,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":852,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":852,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":852,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:35:45"},
{"history_id":"958","user_id":"1","game_stage":"7","question":"191-84-106","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":106}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":106}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:37:30"},
{"history_id":"959","user_id":"1","game_stage":"7","question":"40x13x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6760,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":520,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6760,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":520,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:38:02"},
{"history_id":"960","user_id":"1","game_stage":"7","question":"232÷4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:38:31"},
{"history_id":"961","user_id":"1","game_stage":"7","question":"251-121-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:40:11"},
{"history_id":"962","user_id":"1","game_stage":"8","question":"172+83x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:43:51"},
{"history_id":"963","user_id":"1","game_stage":"8","question":"264-18x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":216}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":216}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:44:28"},
{"history_id":"964","user_id":"1","game_stage":"8","question":"512-38x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":494,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":512,\"numB\":494}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":494,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":512,\"numB\":494}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:45:03"},
{"history_id":"965","user_id":"1","game_stage":"9","question":"193+90÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:52:15"},
{"history_id":"966","user_id":"1","game_stage":"9","question":"238÷34+214","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":214}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":214}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:59:12"},
{"history_id":"967","user_id":"1","game_stage":"9","question":"160-125x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":125}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":125}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 03:59:47"},
{"history_id":"968","user_id":"1","game_stage":"9","question":"68÷34-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:00:13"},
{"history_id":"969","user_id":"1","game_stage":"10","question":"2040÷(36+168)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":168}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2040,\"numB\":204}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":168}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2040,\"numB\":204}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:01:03"},
{"history_id":"970","user_id":"1","game_stage":"10","question":"98-(151-57)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:01:26"},
{"history_id":"971","user_id":"1","game_stage":"10","question":"(77+149)x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1808,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1808,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:02:05"},
{"history_id":"972","user_id":"1","game_stage":"10","question":"(141-79)x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":806,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":806,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:02:28"},
{"history_id":"973","user_id":"1","game_stage":"11","question":"3x(17+240)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":257,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":240}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":771,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":257}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":257,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":240}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":771,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":257}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:03:31"},
{"history_id":"974","user_id":"1","game_stage":"11","question":"(78-36)-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:04:06"},
{"history_id":"975","user_id":"1","game_stage":"11","question":"6x(33+144)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1062,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":177}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1062,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":177}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:04:46"},
{"history_id":"976","user_id":"1","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u62103\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u5806180\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u580649\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"3x(180+49)","userAns_obj":"(180+49)x3","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:06:12"},
{"history_id":"977","user_id":"1","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86138\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86151\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e862\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"2x(138+151)","userAns_obj":"(138+151)x2","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:21:48"},
{"history_id":"978","user_id":"1","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u4e8c\u54e5\u84cb\u623f\u5b50\u6642\u4f7f\u7528\u4e8611\u6839\u6728\u982d\uff0c\u5f8c\u4f86\u767c\u73fe\u6728\u982d\u4e0d\u5920\uff0c\u53c8\u53bb\u8490\u96c6\u4e8633\u6839\u6728\u982d\uff0c\u84cb\u597d\u623f\u5b50\u5f8c\u767c\u73fe\u670916\u6839\u6728\u982d\u6c92\u6709\u7528\u5230\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u4e8c\u54e5\u84cb\u623f\u5b50\u4f7f\u7528\u4e86\u591a\u5c11\u6839\u6728\u982d\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"11+33-16","userAns_obj":"11+33-16","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:22:24"},
{"history_id":"979","user_id":"1","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5c0f\u5f1f\u60f3\u8981\u8a08\u7b97\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u78da\u982d\u6578\u91cf\uff0c\u4ed6\u5c0740\u500b\u78da\u982d\u5206\u70ba\u4e00\u7d44\uff0c\u5171\u670913\u7d44\uff0c\u53e6\u5916\u9084\u670960\u500b\u78da\u982d\uff0c\u8acb\u5e6b\u8c6c\u5c0f\u5f1f\u8a08\u7b97\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u78da\u982d\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"60+40x13","userAns_obj":"40x13+60","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:23:01"},
{"history_id":"980","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\ufeff\u5730\u4e0a\u7684\u77f3\u982d\u5171\u670944\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u67092\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u73fe\u5728\u60f3\u5168\u90e8\u6df7\u5728\u4e00\u8d77\u4e26\u4e14\u5e73\u5206\u621022\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u5e73\u5206\u904e\u5f8c\u6bcf\u5806\u88e1\u9762\u6709\u5e7e\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"44x2÷22","userAns_obj":"44÷22x2","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:55:03"},
{"history_id":"981","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\u5230\u8c6c\u8c6c\u8d85\u5e02\u8cb7\u4e8657\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\uff0c\u56de\u5bb6\u5f8c\u5c0719\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u4e00\u5305\uff0c\u9001\u7d66\u8c6c\u963f\u5b242\u5305\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"57÷19-2","userAns_obj":"57÷19-2","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:55:29"},
{"history_id":"982","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u5abd\u5abd\u5230\u9eb5\u5305\u5e97\u8cb7\u4e8637\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff0c\u7559\u4e0b20\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\u653e\u5bb6\u4e2d\uff0c\u5176\u4ed6\u5e73\u5206\u7d6617\u500b\u5de6\u53f3\u9130\u5c45\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u500b\u9130\u5c45\u6703\u62ff\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"(37-20)÷17","userAns_obj":"(37-20)÷17","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-20 04:55:56"},
{"history_id":"983","user_id":"60","game_stage":"2","question":"63+94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:38:50"},
{"history_id":"984","user_id":"61","game_stage":"2","question":"51-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:39:46"},
{"history_id":"985","user_id":"60","game_stage":"2","question":"30+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:40:06"},
{"history_id":"986","user_id":"65","game_stage":"2","question":"45-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:41:09"},
{"history_id":"987","user_id":"61","game_stage":"2","question":"34+9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:41:09"},
{"history_id":"988","user_id":"64","game_stage":"2","question":"3+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:41:11"},
{"history_id":"989","user_id":"63","game_stage":"2","question":"78+22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:41:14"},
{"history_id":"990","user_id":"68","game_stage":"2","question":"51+73","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":73}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":73}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:41:25"},
{"history_id":"991","user_id":"72","game_stage":"2","question":"91-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:41:36"},
{"history_id":"992","user_id":"62","game_stage":"2","question":"47-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:41:49"},
{"history_id":"993","user_id":"60","game_stage":"2","question":"39-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:05"},
{"history_id":"994","user_id":"82","game_stage":"2","question":"67+4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:19"},
{"history_id":"995","user_id":"69","game_stage":"2","question":"9+36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:33"},
{"history_id":"996","user_id":"85","game_stage":"2","question":"80-46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":46}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:37"},
{"history_id":"997","user_id":"74","game_stage":"2","question":"93-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:37"},
{"history_id":"998","user_id":"72","game_stage":"2","question":"78+39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:38"},
{"history_id":"999","user_id":"68","game_stage":"2","question":"99+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:43"},
{"history_id":"1000","user_id":"63","game_stage":"2","question":"54+96","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:44"},
{"history_id":"1001","user_id":"64","game_stage":"2","question":"51+66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:42:48"},
{"history_id":"1002","user_id":"61","game_stage":"2","question":"55-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:04"},
{"history_id":"1003","user_id":"84","game_stage":"2","question":"64+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:11"},
{"history_id":"1004","user_id":"80","game_stage":"2","question":"88-40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:14"},
{"history_id":"1005","user_id":"83","game_stage":"2","question":"70-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:17"},
{"history_id":"1006","user_id":"62","game_stage":"2","question":"96-32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:33"},
{"history_id":"1007","user_id":"60","game_stage":"3","question":"17x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis07","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:39"},
{"history_id":"1008","user_id":"59","game_stage":"2","question":"55-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:42"},
{"history_id":"1009","user_id":"80","game_stage":"2","question":"52-22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:43"},
{"history_id":"1010","user_id":"82","game_stage":"2","question":"60+11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:47"},
{"history_id":"1011","user_id":"60","game_stage":"3","question":"44÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:43:52"},
{"history_id":"1012","user_id":"67","game_stage":"2","question":"76-48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:02"},
{"history_id":"1013","user_id":"72","game_stage":"2","question":"74-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:06"},
{"history_id":"1014","user_id":"69","game_stage":"2","question":"79+91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:09"},
{"history_id":"1015","user_id":"59","game_stage":"2","question":"38-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:12"},
{"history_id":"1016","user_id":"60","game_stage":"3","question":"39x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:16"},
{"history_id":"1017","user_id":"85","game_stage":"2","question":"59-42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:37"},
{"history_id":"1018","user_id":"70","game_stage":"2","question":"86+32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:38"},
{"history_id":"1019","user_id":"68","game_stage":"2","question":"82-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:39"},
{"history_id":"1020","user_id":"60","game_stage":"3","question":"62÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:41"},
{"history_id":"1021","user_id":"64","game_stage":"2","question":"24+1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:43"},
{"history_id":"1022","user_id":"74","game_stage":"2","question":"93-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:46"},
{"history_id":"1023","user_id":"83","game_stage":"2","question":"77-41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:44:49"},
{"history_id":"1024","user_id":"84","game_stage":"2","question":"39+93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:05"},
{"history_id":"1025","user_id":"68","game_stage":"2","question":"81+17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:07"},
{"history_id":"1026","user_id":"83","game_stage":"2","question":"67+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:13"},
{"history_id":"1027","user_id":"61","game_stage":"3","question":"74÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:14"},
{"history_id":"1028","user_id":"73","game_stage":"2","question":"42+71","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":71}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:17"},
{"history_id":"1029","user_id":"63","game_stage":"2","question":"99+78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:25"},
{"history_id":"1030","user_id":"66","game_stage":"2","question":"6+95","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":95}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":95}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:26"},
{"history_id":"1031","user_id":"78","game_stage":"2","question":"91-43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:30"},
{"history_id":"1032","user_id":"65","game_stage":"2","question":"99+89","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:33"},
{"history_id":"1033","user_id":"62","game_stage":"2","question":"74-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:34"},
{"history_id":"1034","user_id":"67","game_stage":"2","question":"98-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:50"},
{"history_id":"1035","user_id":"80","game_stage":"2","question":"3+37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:53"},
{"history_id":"1036","user_id":"61","game_stage":"3","question":"3x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:45:54"},
{"history_id":"1037","user_id":"71","game_stage":"2","question":"19-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:01"},
{"history_id":"1038","user_id":"86","game_stage":"2","question":"91-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:08"},
{"history_id":"1039","user_id":"59","game_stage":"2","question":"37+86","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":86}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:11"},
{"history_id":"1040","user_id":"82","game_stage":"2","question":"45+3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:19"},
{"history_id":"1041","user_id":"69","game_stage":"2","question":"15+74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":74}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:19"},
{"history_id":"1042","user_id":"60","game_stage":"4","question":"121-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:31"},
{"history_id":"1043","user_id":"70","game_stage":"2","question":"38-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:35"},
{"history_id":"1044","user_id":"72","game_stage":"2","question":"33-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:39"},
{"history_id":"1045","user_id":"66","game_stage":"2","question":"93-43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:40"},
{"history_id":"1046","user_id":"78","game_stage":"2","question":"34+15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:43"},
{"history_id":"1047","user_id":"61","game_stage":"3","question":"24x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:46"},
{"history_id":"1048","user_id":"85","game_stage":"2","question":"85-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:53"},
{"history_id":"1049","user_id":"65","game_stage":"2","question":"82-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:56"},
{"history_id":"1050","user_id":"64","game_stage":"3","question":"90÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:57"},
{"history_id":"1051","user_id":"68","game_stage":"3","question":"87÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:57"},
{"history_id":"1052","user_id":"60","game_stage":"4","question":"77÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:46:58"},
{"history_id":"1053","user_id":"74","game_stage":"2","question":"43-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:11"},
{"history_id":"1054","user_id":"62","game_stage":"2","question":"26-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:13"},
{"history_id":"1055","user_id":"60","game_stage":"4","question":"105-82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:24"},
{"history_id":"1056","user_id":"83","game_stage":"2","question":"62+63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:27"},
{"history_id":"1057","user_id":"71","game_stage":"2","question":"22-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:27"},
{"history_id":"1058","user_id":"61","game_stage":"3","question":"87÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:31"},
{"history_id":"1059","user_id":"86","game_stage":"2","question":"56-43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:32"},
{"history_id":"1060","user_id":"68","game_stage":"3","question":"47x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:38"},
{"history_id":"1061","user_id":"84","game_stage":"2","question":"22+99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:39"},
{"history_id":"1062","user_id":"63","game_stage":"3","question":"24x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:42"},
{"history_id":"1063","user_id":"73","game_stage":"2","question":"58-44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:45"},
{"history_id":"1064","user_id":"76","game_stage":"2","question":"36+99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:54"},
{"history_id":"1065","user_id":"62","game_stage":"2","question":"41+97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:47:59"},
{"history_id":"1066","user_id":"64","game_stage":"3","question":"8x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:00"},
{"history_id":"1067","user_id":"75","game_stage":"2","question":"78-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:02"},
{"history_id":"1068","user_id":"82","game_stage":"3","question":"30÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:02"},
{"history_id":"1069","user_id":"67","game_stage":"2","question":"66-35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:06"},
{"history_id":"1070","user_id":"68","game_stage":"3","question":"48÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:11"},
{"history_id":"1071","user_id":"63","game_stage":"3","question":"31x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:21"},
{"history_id":"1072","user_id":"59","game_stage":"2","question":"86-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:27"},
{"history_id":"1073","user_id":"79","game_stage":"2","question":"96+21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:35"},
{"history_id":"1074","user_id":"80","game_stage":"2","question":"78-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:36"},
{"history_id":"1075","user_id":"81","game_stage":"2","question":"86-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:45"},
{"history_id":"1076","user_id":"66","game_stage":"2","question":"43-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:47"},
{"history_id":"1077","user_id":"70","game_stage":"2","question":"99-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:48"},
{"history_id":"1078","user_id":"63","game_stage":"3","question":"91÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:53"},
{"history_id":"1079","user_id":"65","game_stage":"2","question":"16+6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:54"},
{"history_id":"1080","user_id":"60","game_stage":"6","question":"16+74+56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:58"},
{"history_id":"1081","user_id":"64","game_stage":"3","question":"46x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":813,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:48:59"},
{"history_id":"1082","user_id":"87","game_stage":"2","question":"43-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:00"},
{"history_id":"1083","user_id":"74","game_stage":"3","question":"31x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:01"},
{"history_id":"1084","user_id":"78","game_stage":"2","question":"4+38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:06"},
{"history_id":"1085","user_id":"76","game_stage":"2","question":"27-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:14"},
{"history_id":"1086","user_id":"61","game_stage":"4","question":"56x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:20"},
{"history_id":"1087","user_id":"60","game_stage":"6","question":"55÷11÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:26"},
{"history_id":"1088","user_id":"82","game_stage":"3","question":"48x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:33"},
{"history_id":"1089","user_id":"76","game_stage":"2","question":"68-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:40"},
{"history_id":"1090","user_id":"75","game_stage":"2","question":"49+98","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":98}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":98}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:40"},
{"history_id":"1091","user_id":"68","game_stage":"4","question":"34÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:42"},
{"history_id":"1092","user_id":"64","game_stage":"3","question":"28x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:43"},
{"history_id":"1093","user_id":"83","game_stage":"3","question":"45x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:45"},
{"history_id":"1094","user_id":"84","game_stage":"3","question":"42÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:46"},
{"history_id":"1095","user_id":"59","game_stage":"3","question":"17x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:56"},
{"history_id":"1096","user_id":"74","game_stage":"3","question":"22x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:49:57"},
{"history_id":"1097","user_id":"67","game_stage":"3","question":"27÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:04"},
{"history_id":"1098","user_id":"85","game_stage":"3","question":"51÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:04"},
{"history_id":"1099","user_id":"61","game_stage":"4","question":"52x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":676,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:05"},
{"history_id":"1100","user_id":"80","game_stage":"3","question":"36x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:08"},
{"history_id":"1101","user_id":"82","game_stage":"3","question":"2x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:08"},
{"history_id":"1102","user_id":"86","game_stage":"2","question":"44-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:10"},
{"history_id":"1103","user_id":"68","game_stage":"4","question":"86-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:12"},
{"history_id":"1104","user_id":"81","game_stage":"2","question":"85-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:12"},
{"history_id":"1105","user_id":"72","game_stage":"3","question":"38÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:12"},
{"history_id":"1106","user_id":"71","game_stage":"2","question":"86+35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:16"},
{"history_id":"1107","user_id":"60","game_stage":"6","question":"86x13x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1118,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1118,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:20"},
{"history_id":"1108","user_id":"66","game_stage":"3","question":"4x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:20"},
{"history_id":"1109","user_id":"63","game_stage":"4","question":"194-62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:26"},
{"history_id":"1110","user_id":"77","game_stage":"2","question":"39+82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:30"},
{"history_id":"1111","user_id":"61","game_stage":"4","question":"135-29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:32"},
{"history_id":"1112","user_id":"85","game_stage":"3","question":"28÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:33"},
{"history_id":"1113","user_id":"83","game_stage":"3","question":"78÷39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:34"},
{"history_id":"1114","user_id":"65","game_stage":"3","question":"75÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:34"},
{"history_id":"1115","user_id":"68","game_stage":"4","question":"54÷18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:37"},
{"history_id":"1116","user_id":"78","game_stage":"3","question":"7x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:38"},
{"history_id":"1117","user_id":"62","game_stage":"3","question":"87÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:43"},
{"history_id":"1118","user_id":"72","game_stage":"3","question":"5x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:45"},
{"history_id":"1119","user_id":"87","game_stage":"2","question":"62+82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:47"},
{"history_id":"1120","user_id":"84","game_stage":"3","question":"5x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:48"},
{"history_id":"1121","user_id":"66","game_stage":"3","question":"72÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:55"},
{"history_id":"1122","user_id":"61","game_stage":"4","question":"39x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:56"},
{"history_id":"1123","user_id":"63","game_stage":"4","question":"155÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:56"},
{"history_id":"1124","user_id":"83","game_stage":"3","question":"28x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:58"},
{"history_id":"1125","user_id":"74","game_stage":"3","question":"44÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:59"},
{"history_id":"1126","user_id":"59","game_stage":"3","question":"56÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:50:59"},
{"history_id":"1127","user_id":"78","game_stage":"3","question":"27x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:00"},
{"history_id":"1128","user_id":"65","game_stage":"3","question":"36x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:04"},
{"history_id":"1129","user_id":"68","game_stage":"4","question":"119÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:04"},
{"history_id":"1130","user_id":"80","game_stage":"3","question":"92÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:05"},
{"history_id":"1131","user_id":"79","game_stage":"2","question":"47+90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:08"},
{"history_id":"1132","user_id":"73","game_stage":"2","question":"7-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:08"},
{"history_id":"1133","user_id":"62","game_stage":"3","question":"46x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:10"},
{"history_id":"1134","user_id":"59","game_stage":"3","question":"74÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:20"},
{"history_id":"1135","user_id":"63","game_stage":"4","question":"118-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:23"},
{"history_id":"1136","user_id":"85","game_stage":"3","question":"92÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:24"},
{"history_id":"1137","user_id":"75","game_stage":"2","question":"79-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:28"},
{"history_id":"1138","user_id":"83","game_stage":"3","question":"27x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:29"},
{"history_id":"1139","user_id":"76","game_stage":"2","question":"85-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:31"},
{"history_id":"1140","user_id":"78","game_stage":"3","question":"27x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:32"},
{"history_id":"1141","user_id":"68","game_stage":"4","question":"117÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:32"},
{"history_id":"1142","user_id":"60","game_stage":"7","question":"25+186+96","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":307,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":307,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:35"},
{"history_id":"1143","user_id":"66","game_stage":"3","question":"96÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:36"},
{"history_id":"1144","user_id":"72","game_stage":"3","question":"92÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:37"},
{"history_id":"1145","user_id":"64","game_stage":"4","question":"110-97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:39"},
{"history_id":"1146","user_id":"82","game_stage":"4","question":"14÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:42"},
{"history_id":"1147","user_id":"62","game_stage":"3","question":"64÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:44"},
{"history_id":"1148","user_id":"84","game_stage":"3","question":"29x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:47"},
{"history_id":"1149","user_id":"65","game_stage":"3","question":"14x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:47"},
{"history_id":"1150","user_id":"67","game_stage":"3","question":"65÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:50"},
{"history_id":"1151","user_id":"86","game_stage":"3","question":"33x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:52"},
{"history_id":"1152","user_id":"59","game_stage":"3","question":"90÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:51:55"},
{"history_id":"1153","user_id":"77","game_stage":"2","question":"54-25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:00"},
{"history_id":"1154","user_id":"87","game_stage":"2","question":"98-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:06"},
{"history_id":"1155","user_id":"78","game_stage":"3","question":"40x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:09"},
{"history_id":"1156","user_id":"61","game_stage":"6","question":"66+112+71","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":183}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:11"},
{"history_id":"1157","user_id":"80","game_stage":"3","question":"44x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":308,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":308,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:16"},
{"history_id":"1158","user_id":"64","game_stage":"4","question":"169-72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:17"},
{"history_id":"1159","user_id":"82","game_stage":"4","question":"60+177","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":177}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":177}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:18"},
{"history_id":"1160","user_id":"85","game_stage":"3","question":"93÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:24"},
{"history_id":"1161","user_id":"86","game_stage":"3","question":"26÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:27"},
{"history_id":"1162","user_id":"60","game_stage":"7","question":"210÷6x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":425,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:27"},
{"history_id":"1163","user_id":"70","game_stage":"3","question":"76÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:30"},
{"history_id":"1164","user_id":"84","game_stage":"3","question":"12x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:41"},
{"history_id":"1165","user_id":"64","game_stage":"4","question":"37x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:44"},
{"history_id":"1166","user_id":"74","game_stage":"4","question":"3x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:45"},
{"history_id":"1167","user_id":"71","game_stage":"3","question":"33÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:48"},
{"history_id":"1168","user_id":"82","game_stage":"4","question":"110+139","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:48"},
{"history_id":"1169","user_id":"70","game_stage":"3","question":"9÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:48"},
{"history_id":"1170","user_id":"67","game_stage":"3","question":"6x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:52"},
{"history_id":"1171","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"151-23+61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:54"},
{"history_id":"1172","user_id":"73","game_stage":"3","question":"4x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:54"},
{"history_id":"1173","user_id":"85","game_stage":"3","question":"24÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:52:55"},
{"history_id":"1174","user_id":"81","game_stage":"2","question":"41+62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:03"},
{"history_id":"1175","user_id":"86","game_stage":"3","question":"1x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:05"},
{"history_id":"1176","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"39+43+105","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":105}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":105}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":148}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:05"},
{"history_id":"1177","user_id":"76","game_stage":"3","question":"45x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:09"},
{"history_id":"1178","user_id":"83","game_stage":"4","question":"92-51","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":51}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":51}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:11"},
{"history_id":"1179","user_id":"62","game_stage":"4","question":"80+139","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:18"},
{"history_id":"1180","user_id":"74","game_stage":"4","question":"168÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:18"},
{"history_id":"1181","user_id":"82","game_stage":"4","question":"67x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:20"},
{"history_id":"1182","user_id":"65","game_stage":"4","question":"150-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:22"},
{"history_id":"1183","user_id":"72","game_stage":"4","question":"85+140","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":140}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":140}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:23"},
{"history_id":"1184","user_id":"64","game_stage":"4","question":"185÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:23"},
{"history_id":"1185","user_id":"73","game_stage":"3","question":"14÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:26"},
{"history_id":"1186","user_id":"75","game_stage":"3","question":"44÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:32"},
{"history_id":"1187","user_id":"61","game_stage":"6","question":"72x2÷18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:35"},
{"history_id":"1188","user_id":"79","game_stage":"2","question":"82-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:35"},
{"history_id":"1189","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"38x13x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":494,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3952,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":494,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9181,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":104}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:35"},
{"history_id":"1190","user_id":"70","game_stage":"3","question":"14÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:41"},
{"history_id":"1191","user_id":"64","game_stage":"4","question":"45÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:43"},
{"history_id":"1192","user_id":"78","game_stage":"4","question":"82-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:43"},
{"history_id":"1193","user_id":"69","game_stage":"3","question":"35x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:44"},
{"history_id":"1194","user_id":"66","game_stage":"4","question":"30÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:47"},
{"history_id":"1195","user_id":"80","game_stage":"4","question":"129-89","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:47"},
{"history_id":"1196","user_id":"62","game_stage":"4","question":"18+43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:48"},
{"history_id":"1197","user_id":"83","game_stage":"4","question":"36x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":468,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:49"},
{"history_id":"1198","user_id":"77","game_stage":"2","question":"95-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:52"},
{"history_id":"1199","user_id":"65","game_stage":"4","question":"112÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:53"},
{"history_id":"1200","user_id":"76","game_stage":"3","question":"2x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:55"},
{"history_id":"1201","user_id":"75","game_stage":"3","question":"93÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:53:57"},
{"history_id":"1202","user_id":"74","game_stage":"4","question":"105÷15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:03"},
{"history_id":"1203","user_id":"71","game_stage":"3","question":"4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:06"},
{"history_id":"1204","user_id":"59","game_stage":"4","question":"194-42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:09"},
{"history_id":"1205","user_id":"83","game_stage":"4","question":"184÷46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":46}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:09"},
{"history_id":"1206","user_id":"66","game_stage":"4","question":"50÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:11"},
{"history_id":"1207","user_id":"72","game_stage":"4","question":"38x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:15"},
{"history_id":"1208","user_id":"73","game_stage":"3","question":"24x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:18"},
{"history_id":"1209","user_id":"80","game_stage":"4","question":"179-77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:18"},
{"history_id":"1210","user_id":"78","game_stage":"4","question":"183÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:19"},
{"history_id":"1211","user_id":"60","game_stage":"7","question":"135x13÷45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1755,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1755,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1755,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1755,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:21"},
{"history_id":"1212","user_id":"83","game_stage":"4","question":"45-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:30"},
{"history_id":"1213","user_id":"59","game_stage":"4","question":"188÷94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:32"},
{"history_id":"1214","user_id":"62","game_stage":"4","question":"144÷72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:36"},
{"history_id":"1215","user_id":"67","game_stage":"4","question":"30+5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:39"},
{"history_id":"1216","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"185÷5x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:39"},
{"history_id":"1217","user_id":"66","game_stage":"4","question":"73x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:41"},
{"history_id":"1218","user_id":"64","game_stage":"4","question":"190÷38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:42"},
{"history_id":"1219","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"86x12x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1032,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1032,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":132}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:50"},
{"history_id":"1220","user_id":"80","game_stage":"4","question":"97x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":873,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":873,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:51"},
{"history_id":"1221","user_id":"78","game_stage":"4","question":"39x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:51"},
{"history_id":"1222","user_id":"75","game_stage":"3","question":"51÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:52"},
{"history_id":"1223","user_id":"76","game_stage":"3","question":"80÷16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:54"},
{"history_id":"1224","user_id":"81","game_stage":"3","question":"21x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:54:55"},
{"history_id":"1225","user_id":"67","game_stage":"4","question":"117÷39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:06"},
{"history_id":"1226","user_id":"83","game_stage":"4","question":"130+7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:07"},
{"history_id":"1227","user_id":"77","game_stage":"3","question":"20x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:14"},
{"history_id":"1228","user_id":"80","game_stage":"4","question":"38÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:15"},
{"history_id":"1229","user_id":"59","game_stage":"4","question":"160+96","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:16"},
{"history_id":"1230","user_id":"85","game_stage":"4","question":"85+90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:18"},
{"history_id":"1231","user_id":"72","game_stage":"4","question":"111-69","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":69}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":69}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:21"},
{"history_id":"1232","user_id":"84","game_stage":"4","question":"179-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:22"},
{"history_id":"1233","user_id":"65","game_stage":"6","question":"152+138-105","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":290,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":138}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":185,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":105}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":290,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":138}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":185,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":105}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:24"},
{"history_id":"1234","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"168÷4x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:25"},
{"history_id":"1235","user_id":"86","game_stage":"4","question":"80÷40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:25"},
{"history_id":"1236","user_id":"70","game_stage":"3","question":"65÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:27"},
{"history_id":"1237","user_id":"71","game_stage":"3","question":"43x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:28"},
{"history_id":"1238","user_id":"87","game_stage":"2","question":"15+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:33"},
{"history_id":"1239","user_id":"69","game_stage":"3","question":"57÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:35"},
{"history_id":"1240","user_id":"67","game_stage":"4","question":"78÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:38"},
{"history_id":"1241","user_id":"80","game_stage":"4","question":"134÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:41"},
{"history_id":"1242","user_id":"77","game_stage":"3","question":"87÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:42"},
{"history_id":"1243","user_id":"85","game_stage":"4","question":"98x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:45"},
{"history_id":"1244","user_id":"60","game_stage":"7","question":"138x16÷184","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2208,\"numB\":184}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2208,\"numB\":184}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:46"},
{"history_id":"1245","user_id":"59","game_stage":"4","question":"126+146","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":146}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":146}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:47"},
{"history_id":"1246","user_id":"75","game_stage":"3","question":"50÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:51"},
{"history_id":"1247","user_id":"66","game_stage":"6","question":"58+130-168","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":130}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":168}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":130}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":168}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:53"},
{"history_id":"1248","user_id":"73","game_stage":"4","question":"70+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:57"},
{"history_id":"1249","user_id":"74","game_stage":"6","question":"5+125-51","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":51}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":51}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:55:57"},
{"history_id":"1250","user_id":"81","game_stage":"3","question":"86÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:01"},
{"history_id":"1251","user_id":"84","game_stage":"4","question":"165÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:02"},
{"history_id":"1252","user_id":"65","game_stage":"6","question":"50÷25x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:03"},
{"history_id":"1253","user_id":"67","game_stage":"4","question":"144+134","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":278,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":134}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":278,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":134}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:04"},
{"history_id":"1254","user_id":"77","game_stage":"3","question":"48÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:04"},
{"history_id":"1255","user_id":"82","game_stage":"6","question":"96-40-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:12"},
{"history_id":"1256","user_id":"78","game_stage":"6","question":"77+41+91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:12"},
{"history_id":"1257","user_id":"87","game_stage":"2","question":"50-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:13"},
{"history_id":"1258","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"16+68-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:19"},
{"history_id":"1259","user_id":"61","game_stage":"6","question":"66÷2x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:20"},
{"history_id":"1260","user_id":"69","game_stage":"3","question":"44x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:22"},
{"history_id":"1261","user_id":"64","game_stage":"6","question":"78+159+152","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":159}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":389,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":152}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":159}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":389,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":152}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:24"},
{"history_id":"1262","user_id":"76","game_stage":"4","question":"37x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:24"},
{"history_id":"1263","user_id":"79","game_stage":"3","question":"25÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:25"},
{"history_id":"1264","user_id":"77","game_stage":"3","question":"41x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:35"},
{"history_id":"1265","user_id":"83","game_stage":"6","question":"96+26+123","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":123}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":123}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:36"},
{"history_id":"1266","user_id":"66","game_stage":"6","question":"121÷11x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:39"},
{"history_id":"1267","user_id":"84","game_stage":"4","question":"46÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:42"},
{"history_id":"1268","user_id":"86","game_stage":"4","question":"70x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:43"},
{"history_id":"1269","user_id":"72","game_stage":"6","question":"48+33+130","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":130}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":130}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":163}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:44"},
{"history_id":"1270","user_id":"73","game_stage":"4","question":"185÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:47"},
{"history_id":"1271","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"129÷43÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:50"},
{"history_id":"1272","user_id":"65","game_stage":"6","question":"76x6x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":456,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":456,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":456,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":456,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:51"},
{"history_id":"1273","user_id":"76","game_stage":"4","question":"59x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":590,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":590,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:51"},
{"history_id":"1274","user_id":"81","game_stage":"3","question":"21÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:54"},
{"history_id":"1275","user_id":"78","game_stage":"6","question":"11x4x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:55"},
{"history_id":"1276","user_id":"64","game_stage":"6","question":"12x10x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:56"},
{"history_id":"1277","user_id":"71","game_stage":"3","question":"30x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:56"},
{"history_id":"1278","user_id":"74","game_stage":"6","question":"192÷16÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:56:58"},
{"history_id":"1279","user_id":"86","game_stage":"4","question":"90x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:09"},
{"history_id":"1280","user_id":"73","game_stage":"4","question":"53x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:12"},
{"history_id":"1281","user_id":"59","game_stage":"6","question":"120-96-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:16"},
{"history_id":"1282","user_id":"76","game_stage":"4","question":"40-33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:16"},
{"history_id":"1283","user_id":"60","game_stage":"7","question":"201+120+75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":321,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":321,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":321,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":321,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:16"},
{"history_id":"1284","user_id":"72","game_stage":"6","question":"124-14+68","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":68}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":68}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:17"},
{"history_id":"1285","user_id":"66","game_stage":"6","question":"196-68-106","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":106}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":106}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:19"},
{"history_id":"1286","user_id":"79","game_stage":"3","question":"47x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:19"},
{"history_id":"1287","user_id":"84","game_stage":"4","question":"161-48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:20"},
{"history_id":"1288","user_id":"75","game_stage":"4","question":"41+149","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":149}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":149}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:25"},
{"history_id":"1289","user_id":"81","game_stage":"3","question":"99÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:26"},
{"history_id":"1290","user_id":"78","game_stage":"6","question":"36÷2÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:26"},
{"history_id":"1291","user_id":"62","game_stage":"7","question":"74+215-250","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":215}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":289,\"numB\":250}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":250}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:30"},
{"history_id":"1292","user_id":"83","game_stage":"6","question":"84÷6x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:33"},
{"history_id":"1293","user_id":"74","game_stage":"6","question":"145÷5÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:36"},
{"history_id":"1294","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"130-93-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":93}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":84}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:37"},
{"history_id":"1295","user_id":"80","game_stage":"6","question":"3+83+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:39"},
{"history_id":"1296","user_id":"73","game_stage":"4","question":"83+45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:42"},
{"history_id":"1297","user_id":"70","game_stage":"4","question":"96-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:53"},
{"history_id":"1298","user_id":"59","game_stage":"6","question":"10x6x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:53"},
{"history_id":"1299","user_id":"75","game_stage":"4","question":"57x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":513,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":513,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:54"},
{"history_id":"1300","user_id":"85","game_stage":"6","question":"152+161-205","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":313,\"numB\":205}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":313,\"numB\":205}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:56"},
{"history_id":"1301","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"139-90+10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":90}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:57:56"},
{"history_id":"1302","user_id":"64","game_stage":"6","question":"196÷14÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:00"},
{"history_id":"1303","user_id":"65","game_stage":"7","question":"295-82-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":213,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":213,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:11"},
{"history_id":"1304","user_id":"83","game_stage":"6","question":"158-43-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:15"},
{"history_id":"1305","user_id":"72","game_stage":"6","question":"8x3x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:16"},
{"history_id":"1306","user_id":"62","game_stage":"7","question":"28+41-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:17"},
{"history_id":"1307","user_id":"77","game_stage":"4","question":"84x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1008,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":948,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:18"},
{"history_id":"1308","user_id":"75","game_stage":"4","question":"6x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:18"},
{"history_id":"1309","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"135-96+6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":102}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:20"},
{"history_id":"1310","user_id":"69","game_stage":"4","question":"118÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:21"},
{"history_id":"1311","user_id":"87","game_stage":"3","question":"17x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:21"},
{"history_id":"1312","user_id":"79","game_stage":"3","question":"18x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:23"},
{"history_id":"1313","user_id":"82","game_stage":"6","question":"114÷19÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:26"},
{"history_id":"1314","user_id":"78","game_stage":"7","question":"236-137-62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:30"},
{"history_id":"1315","user_id":"85","game_stage":"6","question":"77÷7x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:31"},
{"history_id":"1316","user_id":"59","game_stage":"6","question":"33+167-177","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":167}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":177}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":167}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":177}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:31"},
{"history_id":"1317","user_id":"80","game_stage":"6","question":"83x5x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":415,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2490,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":415,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":415,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2490,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":415,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:34"},
{"history_id":"1318","user_id":"77","game_stage":"4","question":"109-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:38"},
{"history_id":"1319","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"186-49-63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:39"},
{"history_id":"1320","user_id":"72","game_stage":"6","question":"55÷5÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:43"},
{"history_id":"1321","user_id":"69","game_stage":"4","question":"40x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:43"},
{"history_id":"1322","user_id":"76","game_stage":"6","question":"102+56-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":56}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":56}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:47"},
{"history_id":"1323","user_id":"70","game_stage":"4","question":"95+77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:50"},
{"history_id":"1324","user_id":"87","game_stage":"3","question":"44÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:50"},
{"history_id":"1325","user_id":"83","game_stage":"6","question":"128÷16x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:52"},
{"history_id":"1326","user_id":"65","game_stage":"7","question":"201÷67x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:54"},
{"history_id":"1327","user_id":"82","game_stage":"6","question":"2x5x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:56"},
{"history_id":"1328","user_id":"71","game_stage":"4","question":"181-87","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":87}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":87}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:56"},
{"history_id":"1329","user_id":"66","game_stage":"7","question":"264+71-162","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":335,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":335,\"numB\":162}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":335,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":335,\"numB\":162}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:58:59"},
{"history_id":"1330","user_id":"77","game_stage":"4","question":"35÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:01"},
{"history_id":"1331","user_id":"61","game_stage":"6","question":"135-26-108","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":109,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":108}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":109,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":108}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:01"},
{"history_id":"1332","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"108÷54x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:02"},
{"history_id":"1333","user_id":"87","game_stage":"3","question":"6÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:05"},
{"history_id":"1334","user_id":"85","game_stage":"6","question":"92÷4÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:06"},
{"history_id":"1335","user_id":"67","game_stage":"6","question":"88-34+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:06"},
{"history_id":"1336","user_id":"69","game_stage":"4","question":"42÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:11"},
{"history_id":"1337","user_id":"78","game_stage":"7","question":"96÷24÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:14"},
{"history_id":"1338","user_id":"80","game_stage":"6","question":"193+12+1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:15"},
{"history_id":"1339","user_id":"74","game_stage":"7","question":"282-39+220","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":463,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":220}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":463,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":220}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:18"},
{"history_id":"1340","user_id":"76","game_stage":"6","question":"127-48-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:21"},
{"history_id":"1341","user_id":"81","game_stage":"4","question":"76x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":532,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":532,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:23"},
{"history_id":"1342","user_id":"70","game_stage":"4","question":"80x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":400,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":400,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:25"},
{"history_id":"1343","user_id":"66","game_stage":"7","question":"33÷11x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:33"},
{"history_id":"1344","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"92+107+88","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":107}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":287,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":107}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":278,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:34"},
{"history_id":"1345","user_id":"61","game_stage":"6","question":"92x3x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":828,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":276,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":828,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:35"},
{"history_id":"1346","user_id":"69","game_stage":"4","question":"23x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:38"},
{"history_id":"1347","user_id":"75","game_stage":"6","question":"117-77+128","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":128}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":128}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:38"},
{"history_id":"1348","user_id":"77","game_stage":"4","question":"64+187","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":187}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":187}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:39"},
{"history_id":"1349","user_id":"87","game_stage":"3","question":"28x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:41"},
{"history_id":"1350","user_id":"65","game_stage":"7","question":"51x2÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:44"},
{"history_id":"1351","user_id":"60","game_stage":"8","question":"41+118÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":118}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:45"},
{"history_id":"1352","user_id":"62","game_stage":"7","question":"129÷3x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:46"},
{"history_id":"1353","user_id":"67","game_stage":"6","question":"141+128-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":128}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":269,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":128}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":269,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:47"},
{"history_id":"1354","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"272-98-56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:52"},
{"history_id":"1355","user_id":"71","game_stage":"4","question":"51÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:53"},
{"history_id":"1356","user_id":"70","game_stage":"4","question":"79-62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:53"},
{"history_id":"1357","user_id":"76","game_stage":"6","question":"32-1-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:54"},
{"history_id":"1358","user_id":"78","game_stage":"7","question":"260+114-156","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":114}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":374,\"numB\":156}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":114}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":374,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:57"},
{"history_id":"1359","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"72-6-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 10:59:58"},
{"history_id":"1360","user_id":"81","game_stage":"4","question":"109-48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:02"},
{"history_id":"1361","user_id":"61","game_stage":"6","question":"184+141+1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":325,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":326,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":325,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":325,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":326,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":325,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:03"},
{"history_id":"1362","user_id":"66","game_stage":"7","question":"130-102-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":102}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":102}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:10"},
{"history_id":"1363","user_id":"72","game_stage":"7","question":"261+8-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":261,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":269,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":261,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":269,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:11"},
{"history_id":"1364","user_id":"68","game_stage":"6","question":"120-55-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:14"},
{"history_id":"1365","user_id":"67","game_stage":"6","question":"40÷20÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:17"},
{"history_id":"1366","user_id":"83","game_stage":"7","question":"97+183+48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":183}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":183}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:17"},
{"history_id":"1367","user_id":"81","game_stage":"4","question":"64÷32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:20"},
{"history_id":"1368","user_id":"74","game_stage":"7","question":"113x5x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":565,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":565,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":565,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":565,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:21"},
{"history_id":"1369","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"175-34-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:21"},
{"history_id":"1370","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"115+70+106","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":185,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":291,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":106}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":106}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:23"},
{"history_id":"1371","user_id":"75","game_stage":"6","question":"12÷2÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:25"},
{"history_id":"1372","user_id":"76","game_stage":"6","question":"171÷57÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:29"},
{"history_id":"1373","user_id":"79","game_stage":"4","question":"185÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:30"},
{"history_id":"1374","user_id":"62","game_stage":"7","question":"135-134+139","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:30"},
{"history_id":"1375","user_id":"85","game_stage":"7","question":"40+129+182","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":182}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":182}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:31"},
{"history_id":"1376","user_id":"73","game_stage":"4","question":"6+121","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":121}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":121}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:31"},
{"history_id":"1377","user_id":"86","game_stage":"6","question":"44x10x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":440,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":440,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:33"},
{"history_id":"1378","user_id":"71","game_stage":"4","question":"52+91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:34"},
{"history_id":"1379","user_id":"87","game_stage":"3","question":"24x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:41"},
{"history_id":"1380","user_id":"60","game_stage":"8","question":"42+79x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":395,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":437,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":395}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":395,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":437,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":395}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:45"},
{"history_id":"1381","user_id":"81","game_stage":"4","question":"46x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:45"},
{"history_id":"1382","user_id":"75","game_stage":"6","question":"23+192-136","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":192}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":136}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":192}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":136}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:47"},
{"history_id":"1383","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"82-10+38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:48"},
{"history_id":"1384","user_id":"69","game_stage":"6","question":"12-11-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:56"},
{"history_id":"1385","user_id":"72","game_stage":"7","question":"226÷113÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:56"},
{"history_id":"1386","user_id":"79","game_stage":"4","question":"188-42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:58"},
{"history_id":"1387","user_id":"82","game_stage":"6","question":"84x3÷42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:59"},
{"history_id":"1388","user_id":"74","game_stage":"7","question":"14÷2÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:00:59"},
{"history_id":"1389","user_id":"76","game_stage":"6","question":"159÷3÷53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:04"},
{"history_id":"1390","user_id":"87","game_stage":"3","question":"20÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:04"},
{"history_id":"1391","user_id":"77","game_stage":"6","question":"197-76+32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":76}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":76}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:05"},
{"history_id":"1392","user_id":"80","game_stage":"7","question":"51+149-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:06"},
{"history_id":"1393","user_id":"65","game_stage":"8","question":"168÷28+166","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":166}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":166}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:12"},
{"history_id":"1394","user_id":"73","game_stage":"4","question":"49x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":441,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":441,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:15"},
{"history_id":"1395","user_id":"60","game_stage":"8","question":"67-75÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:19"},
{"history_id":"1396","user_id":"78","game_stage":"8","question":"70x5+192","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":350,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":542,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":350,\"numB\":192}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":350,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":542,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":350,\"numB\":192}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:24"},
{"history_id":"1397","user_id":"86","game_stage":"6","question":"160÷10x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:25"},
{"history_id":"1398","user_id":"79","game_stage":"4","question":"81÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:25"},
{"history_id":"1399","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"278-110-156","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":110}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":156}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":156}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:30"},
{"history_id":"1400","user_id":"65","game_stage":"8","question":"22-8÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:37"},
{"history_id":"1401","user_id":"61","game_stage":"7","question":"272-123+78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":227,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":227,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:40"},
{"history_id":"1402","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"125÷5x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:41"},
{"history_id":"1403","user_id":"66","game_stage":"8","question":"30+45x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":180}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:41"},
{"history_id":"1404","user_id":"68","game_stage":"7","question":"285+285+255","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":570,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":285}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":825,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":570,\"numB\":255}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":570,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":285}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":825,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":570,\"numB\":255}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:43"},
{"history_id":"1405","user_id":"84","game_stage":"6","question":"81+91-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:44"},
{"history_id":"1406","user_id":"83","game_stage":"7","question":"43x9x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":387,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5418,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":387,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":387,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5414,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":387,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:45"},
{"history_id":"1407","user_id":"77","game_stage":"6","question":"114÷2÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:47"},
{"history_id":"1408","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"39x3÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:50"},
{"history_id":"1409","user_id":"75","game_stage":"7","question":"46+36+272","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":272}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":272}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:53"},
{"history_id":"1410","user_id":"85","game_stage":"7","question":"185÷5÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:53"},
{"history_id":"1411","user_id":"69","game_stage":"6","question":"156÷13x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:57"},
{"history_id":"1412","user_id":"79","game_stage":"4","question":"167-56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:01:57"},
{"history_id":"1413","user_id":"72","game_stage":"7","question":"169+234-25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":403,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":234}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":378,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":403,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":403,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":234}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":378,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":403,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:06"},
{"history_id":"1414","user_id":"60","game_stage":"8","question":"86x10-462","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":860,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":398,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":860,\"numB\":462}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":860,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":398,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":860,\"numB\":462}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:07"},
{"history_id":"1415","user_id":"63","game_stage":"6","question":"91x6x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":546,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":546,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":546,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":546,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":546,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":546,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:08"},
{"history_id":"1416","user_id":"65","game_stage":"8","question":"188÷4-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:11"},
{"history_id":"1417","user_id":"66","game_stage":"8","question":"81x13+87","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1053,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1053,\"numB\":87}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:12"},
{"history_id":"1418","user_id":"76","game_stage":"7","question":"161-125+259","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":259}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":259}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":223,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":384}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:14"},
{"history_id":"1419","user_id":"68","game_stage":"7","question":"221÷13x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:18"},
{"history_id":"1420","user_id":"87","game_stage":"3","question":"48x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:21"},
{"history_id":"1421","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"119+145+269","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":145}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":533,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":269}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":414,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":269}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":533,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":414}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:22"},
{"history_id":"1422","user_id":"65","game_stage":"8","question":"2x7-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:28"},
{"history_id":"1423","user_id":"69","game_stage":"6","question":"165÷5x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:28"},
{"history_id":"1424","user_id":"82","game_stage":"6","question":"134-34+194","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":194}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":194}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:28"},
{"history_id":"1425","user_id":"62","game_stage":"8","question":"171÷9+137","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":137}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":137}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:29"},
{"history_id":"1426","user_id":"75","game_stage":"7","question":"89x1x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1424,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1424,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:32"},
{"history_id":"1427","user_id":"77","game_stage":"6","question":"4x5x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:35"},
{"history_id":"1428","user_id":"78","game_stage":"8","question":"164÷82-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:37"},
{"history_id":"1429","user_id":"70","game_stage":"6","question":"119-96+125","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":125}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":125}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:39"},
{"history_id":"1430","user_id":"61","game_stage":"7","question":"14x12÷21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:43"},
{"history_id":"1431","user_id":"80","game_stage":"7","question":"68x14x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":952,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7616,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":952,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":952,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7610,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":952,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:44"},
{"history_id":"1432","user_id":"84","game_stage":"6","question":"118÷2÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:45"},
{"history_id":"1433","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"44÷11x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:49"},
{"history_id":"1434","user_id":"73","game_stage":"6","question":"126+123+110","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":359,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":359,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":110}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:50"},
{"history_id":"1435","user_id":"65","game_stage":"8","question":"55÷5-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:51"},
{"history_id":"1436","user_id":"76","game_stage":"7","question":"255-4+239","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":490,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":239}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":239}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":243}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:56"},
{"history_id":"1437","user_id":"85","game_stage":"7","question":"237÷3x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":869,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":869,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:02:57"},
{"history_id":"1438","user_id":"83","game_stage":"7","question":"96x4x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5376,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":384,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5376,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":384,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:00"},
{"history_id":"1439","user_id":"71","game_stage":"6","question":"153-82-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:04"},
{"history_id":"1440","user_id":"82","game_stage":"6","question":"50x2x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:05"},
{"history_id":"1441","user_id":"69","game_stage":"6","question":"80x12x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":960,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":960,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:06"},
{"history_id":"1442","user_id":"66","game_stage":"8","question":"28+88÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:06"},
{"history_id":"1443","user_id":"75","game_stage":"7","question":"124+4-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:11"},
{"history_id":"1444","user_id":"86","game_stage":"7","question":"243-73-130","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":130}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:19"},
{"history_id":"1445","user_id":"72","game_stage":"8","question":"80÷40+2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:19"},
{"history_id":"1446","user_id":"78","game_stage":"8","question":"194÷2+156","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":156}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:23"},
{"history_id":"1447","user_id":"61","game_stage":"7","question":"199+31-97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:23"},
{"history_id":"1448","user_id":"74","game_stage":"8","question":"182÷14+81","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":95}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:27"},
{"history_id":"1449","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"139-47-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:27"},
{"history_id":"1450","user_id":"73","game_stage":"6","question":"30÷15x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:31"},
{"history_id":"1451","user_id":"62","game_stage":"8","question":"65-141÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:34"},
{"history_id":"1452","user_id":"68","game_stage":"7","question":"35x15x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":525,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4725,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":525,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":525,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4725,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":525,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:36"},
{"history_id":"1453","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"145x5÷145","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":725,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":725,\"numB\":145}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":145}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:36"},
{"history_id":"1454","user_id":"76","game_stage":"7","question":"221-48+194","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":367,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":194}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":173}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:37"},
{"history_id":"1455","user_id":"83","game_stage":"7","question":"10÷5x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:37"},
{"history_id":"1456","user_id":"80","game_stage":"7","question":"52x8÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":416,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":416,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":416,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":416,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:38"},
{"history_id":"1457","user_id":"84","game_stage":"6","question":"98÷14x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:39"},
{"history_id":"1458","user_id":"82","game_stage":"6","question":"140+167+105","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":307,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":167}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":412,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":307,\"numB\":105}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":167}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":405,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":300,\"numB\":105}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:45"},
{"history_id":"1459","user_id":"63","game_stage":"7","question":"278+240+187","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":518,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":240}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":705,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":518,\"numB\":187}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":427,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":187}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":711,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":427}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:51"},
{"history_id":"1460","user_id":"67","game_stage":"6","question":"132+134+179","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":445,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":179}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":445,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":179}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:03:58"},
{"history_id":"1461","user_id":"60","game_stage":"9","question":"198÷6+295","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":295}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":295}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:01"},
{"history_id":"1462","user_id":"70","game_stage":"6","question":"1x11÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:01"},
{"history_id":"1463","user_id":"74","game_stage":"8","question":"95÷19+123","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":123}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":123}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:01"},
{"history_id":"1464","user_id":"86","game_stage":"7","question":"143÷13x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:02"},
{"history_id":"1465","user_id":"77","game_stage":"7","question":"206-106-79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:07"},
{"history_id":"1466","user_id":"71","game_stage":"6","question":"17+105+174","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":105}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":105}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:09"},
{"history_id":"1467","user_id":"87","game_stage":"4","question":"54+11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:11"},
{"history_id":"1468","user_id":"72","game_stage":"8","question":"148÷2-14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:15"},
{"history_id":"1469","user_id":"65","game_stage":"9","question":"141+134x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1347,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":1206}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2475,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":275,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:17"},
{"history_id":"1470","user_id":"82","game_stage":"6","question":"82÷2x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:20"},
{"history_id":"1471","user_id":"76","game_stage":"7","question":"231-59-121","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":121}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":121}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:23"},
{"history_id":"1472","user_id":"66","game_stage":"8","question":"113+23x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":412,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":299}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1768,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:27"},
{"history_id":"1473","user_id":"68","game_stage":"7","question":"141x5÷141","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":705,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":705,\"numB\":141}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":705,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":705,\"numB\":141}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:29"},
{"history_id":"1474","user_id":"62","game_stage":"8","question":"117-9x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:30"},
{"history_id":"1475","user_id":"81","game_stage":"6","question":"180+125+53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":358,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":305,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":358,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":305,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:32"},
{"history_id":"1476","user_id":"63","game_stage":"7","question":"210-139+33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:38"},
{"history_id":"1477","user_id":"69","game_stage":"7","question":"14+174-138","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":174}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":138}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":174}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":138}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:44"},
{"history_id":"1478","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"72÷2x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:44"},
{"history_id":"1479","user_id":"87","game_stage":"4","question":"24x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:46"},
{"history_id":"1480","user_id":"74","game_stage":"8","question":"63+186÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:49"},
{"history_id":"1481","user_id":"66","game_stage":"8","question":"103+40÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:50"},
{"history_id":"1482","user_id":"73","game_stage":"6","question":"59x7÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":413,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":413,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":385,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":385,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:51"},
{"history_id":"1483","user_id":"80","game_stage":"7","question":"285+113+89","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":398,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":487,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":398,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":398,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":487,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":398,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:52"},
{"history_id":"1484","user_id":"62","game_stage":"8","question":"106÷53-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":52}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:54"},
{"history_id":"1485","user_id":"70","game_stage":"6","question":"23+112+47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:55"},
{"history_id":"1486","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"77+76÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":76}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:56"},
{"history_id":"1487","user_id":"60","game_stage":"9","question":"79x4-213","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":316,\"numB\":213}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":316,\"numB\":213}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:56"},
{"history_id":"1488","user_id":"77","game_stage":"7","question":"299-34-242","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":265,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":265,\"numB\":242}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":265,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":265,\"numB\":242}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:04:57"},
{"history_id":"1489","user_id":"67","game_stage":"6","question":"186÷2x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":558,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:04"},
{"history_id":"1490","user_id":"63","game_stage":"7","question":"237÷79x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:08"},
{"history_id":"1491","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"87÷3+99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:09"},
{"history_id":"1492","user_id":"66","game_stage":"8","question":"46÷23-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:14"},
{"history_id":"1493","user_id":"86","game_stage":"7","question":"195÷65÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:15"},
{"history_id":"1494","user_id":"76","game_stage":"7","question":"175÷5x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":350,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":350,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:16"},
{"history_id":"1495","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"237÷3+257","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":336,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":257}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":336,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":257}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:16"},
{"history_id":"1496","user_id":"73","game_stage":"6","question":"80÷10x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:17"},
{"history_id":"1497","user_id":"87","game_stage":"4","question":"46÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:18"},
{"history_id":"1498","user_id":"65","game_stage":"9","question":"119x9+277","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1071,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1071,\"numB\":277}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1071,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1071,\"numB\":277}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:19"},
{"history_id":"1499","user_id":"71","game_stage":"6","question":"49x9x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":441,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3528,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":441,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3528,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:20"},
{"history_id":"1500","user_id":"82","game_stage":"7","question":"176-3+192","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":365,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":192}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":365,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":192}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:29"},
{"history_id":"1501","user_id":"72","game_stage":"8","question":"53x12+110","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":636,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":746,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":636,\"numB\":110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":110}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":112}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:30"},
{"history_id":"1502","user_id":"67","game_stage":"6","question":"14÷2x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:31"},
{"history_id":"1503","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"246-38-79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":246,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":246,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:32"},
{"history_id":"1504","user_id":"61","game_stage":"8","question":"31+56÷28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":56}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:33"},
{"history_id":"1505","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"63÷3÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:33"},
{"history_id":"1506","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"37x1+78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:34"},
{"history_id":"1507","user_id":"81","game_stage":"6","question":"96÷24÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:35"},
{"history_id":"1508","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"125+282-246","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":407,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":282}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":407,\"numB\":246}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":307,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":282}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":307,\"numB\":246}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:37"},
{"history_id":"1509","user_id":"77","game_stage":"7","question":"58x2÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:37"},
{"history_id":"1510","user_id":"84","game_stage":"7","question":"188+38-174","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:37"},
{"history_id":"1511","user_id":"71","game_stage":"6","question":"1x9÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:41"},
{"history_id":"1512","user_id":"73","game_stage":"6","question":"8÷2÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:41"},
{"history_id":"1513","user_id":"60","game_stage":"9","question":"34-235÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":235}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:43"},
{"history_id":"1514","user_id":"69","game_stage":"7","question":"95+234+258","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":234}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":587,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":329,\"numB\":258}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":234}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":587,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":329,\"numB\":258}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:46"},
{"history_id":"1515","user_id":"66","game_stage":"8","question":"172÷4+145","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":145}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":145}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:46"},
{"history_id":"1516","user_id":"87","game_stage":"4","question":"39x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:54"},
{"history_id":"1517","user_id":"63","game_stage":"7","question":"253-66+110","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":253,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":253,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":110}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:54"},
{"history_id":"1518","user_id":"61","game_stage":"8","question":"14x7+93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":93}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1400,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:05:58"},
{"history_id":"1519","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"14x16-104","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":224,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":104}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":224,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":104}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:03"},
{"history_id":"1520","user_id":"82","game_stage":"7","question":"4÷2x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:05"},
{"history_id":"1521","user_id":"81","game_stage":"6","question":"124÷4x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:07"},
{"history_id":"1522","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"20x10-172","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:12"},
{"history_id":"1523","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"30÷3÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:13"},
{"history_id":"1524","user_id":"76","game_stage":"7","question":"5x2x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:15"},
{"history_id":"1525","user_id":"74","game_stage":"8","question":"25x5+184","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":309,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":184}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":309,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":184}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:16"},
{"history_id":"1526","user_id":"72","game_stage":"8","question":"177+70x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":737,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":560}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":737,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":560}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:16"},
{"history_id":"1527","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"281-98-43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:17"},
{"history_id":"1528","user_id":"62","game_stage":"8","question":"98x4+149","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":541,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":392,\"numB\":149}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":541,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":392,\"numB\":149}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:18"},
{"history_id":"1529","user_id":"67","game_stage":"6","question":"30x7x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1470,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1470,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:21"},
{"history_id":"1530","user_id":"61","game_stage":"8","question":"187+9x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":108}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":108}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:27"},
{"history_id":"1531","user_id":"60","game_stage":"9","question":"58÷2+261","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":290,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":261}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":287,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":261}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:28"},
{"history_id":"1532","user_id":"69","game_stage":"7","question":"124x4x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":496,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":496,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":496,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":496,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:29"},
{"history_id":"1533","user_id":"77","game_stage":"7","question":"75x3÷45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:30"},
{"history_id":"1534","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"61-1-45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:32"},
{"history_id":"1535","user_id":"75","game_stage":"8","question":"61x5+118","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":423,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":305,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":423,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":305,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:35"},
{"history_id":"1536","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"120+120÷40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:51"},
{"history_id":"1537","user_id":"65","game_stage":"9","question":"221÷17-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:54"},
{"history_id":"1538","user_id":"61","game_stage":"8","question":"27-129÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:06:54"},
{"history_id":"1539","user_id":"73","game_stage":"7","question":"127+202-303","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":202}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":329,\"numB\":303}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":202}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":329,\"numB\":303}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:02"},
{"history_id":"1540","user_id":"84","game_stage":"7","question":"122x5÷122","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":610,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":610,\"numB\":122}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":610,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":610,\"numB\":122}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:03"},
{"history_id":"1541","user_id":"75","game_stage":"8","question":"104-10x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":564,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:04"},
{"history_id":"1542","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"85-49+27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":76}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:08"},
{"history_id":"1543","user_id":"74","game_stage":"8","question":"52-171÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:09"},
{"history_id":"1544","user_id":"60","game_stage":"9","question":"1+86x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":688,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":689,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":688}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:15"},
{"history_id":"1545","user_id":"82","game_stage":"7","question":"193-65+158","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":158}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":158}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:18"},
{"history_id":"1546","user_id":"61","game_stage":"8","question":"68-138÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:22"},
{"history_id":"1547","user_id":"87","game_stage":"6","question":"90+42-93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:28"},
{"history_id":"1548","user_id":"69","game_stage":"7","question":"108÷3x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:28"},
{"history_id":"1549","user_id":"75","game_stage":"8","question":"231-51x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":204}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":720,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:29"},
{"history_id":"1550","user_id":"62","game_stage":"8","question":"69-26÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:31"},
{"history_id":"1551","user_id":"71","game_stage":"7","question":"288+183+35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":471,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":183}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":506,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":471,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":471,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":183}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":506,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":471,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:34"},
{"history_id":"1552","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"247÷19-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:38"},
{"history_id":"1553","user_id":"80","game_stage":"8","question":"41x5+139","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:38"},
{"history_id":"1554","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"241+269-434","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":510,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":269}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":510,\"numB\":434}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":510,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":269}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":510,\"numB\":434}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:40"},
{"history_id":"1555","user_id":"62","game_stage":"8","question":"44÷11-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:50"},
{"history_id":"1556","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"9x9+191","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":191}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":191}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:50"},
{"history_id":"1557","user_id":"73","game_stage":"7","question":"235÷47÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:07:51"},
{"history_id":"1558","user_id":"65","game_stage":"9","question":"272+174÷58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":446,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":174}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":446,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:01"},
{"history_id":"1559","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"24÷2x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:06"},
{"history_id":"1560","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"84x9+111","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":756,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":867,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":756,\"numB\":111}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":756,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":867,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":756,\"numB\":111}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:06"},
{"history_id":"1561","user_id":"75","game_stage":"8","question":"216-54x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":162}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":486,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:09"},
{"history_id":"1562","user_id":"72","game_stage":"9","question":"42x11+200","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":662,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":462,\"numB\":200}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":200}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8862,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":211}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:10"},
{"history_id":"1563","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"50+164-27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":164}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":164}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:11"},
{"history_id":"1564","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"56÷8÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:18"},
{"history_id":"1565","user_id":"80","game_stage":"8","question":"125÷5-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:20"},
{"history_id":"1566","user_id":"62","game_stage":"8","question":"94+57÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:24"},
{"history_id":"1567","user_id":"87","game_stage":"6","question":"9x6÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:26"},
{"history_id":"1568","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"31x3-79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:26"},
{"history_id":"1569","user_id":"81","game_stage":"6","question":"182+8-125","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":125}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4444,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":125}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:30"},
{"history_id":"1570","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"61-4x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:40"},
{"history_id":"1571","user_id":"73","game_stage":"7","question":"169-96+255","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":255}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":985,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":255}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:47"},
{"history_id":"1572","user_id":"65","game_stage":"9","question":"117x2+9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:49"},
{"history_id":"1573","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"70+12x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:56"},
{"history_id":"1574","user_id":"80","game_stage":"8","question":"91+14x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":525,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:08:56"},
{"history_id":"1575","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"49÷7x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:00"},
{"history_id":"1576","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"76x15-788","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1140,\"numB\":788}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":362,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1140,\"numB\":788}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:05"},
{"history_id":"1577","user_id":"61","game_stage":"9","question":"122÷61+220","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":222,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":220}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":220}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:11"},
{"history_id":"1578","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"45÷15÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis04mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:11"},
{"history_id":"1579","user_id":"87","game_stage":"6","question":"186+52+47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:15"},
{"history_id":"1580","user_id":"82","game_stage":"8","question":"89x11+191","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":979,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":979,\"numB\":191}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":979,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":979,\"numB\":191}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:15"},
{"history_id":"1581","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"10÷5÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:23"},
{"history_id":"1582","user_id":"81","game_stage":"6","question":"131-82-21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:25"},
{"history_id":"1583","user_id":"73","game_stage":"7","question":"241-111-67","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:26"},
{"history_id":"1584","user_id":"72","game_stage":"9","question":"65x3+206","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":401,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":206}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":206}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":13585,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":209}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:28"},
{"history_id":"1585","user_id":"59","game_stage":"7","question":"145x16x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2320,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2320,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:31"},
{"history_id":"1586","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"130x14-523","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1820,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1820,\"numB\":523}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1820,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1820,\"numB\":523}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:34"},
{"history_id":"1587","user_id":"60","game_stage":"9","question":"193+174÷87","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:37"},
{"history_id":"1588","user_id":"82","game_stage":"8","question":"150÷30+63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":30}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":30}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:53"},
{"history_id":"1589","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"54x9+176","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":486,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":662,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":486,\"numB\":176}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":485,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":661,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":485,\"numB\":176}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:09:54"},
{"history_id":"1590","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"4÷2x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7377,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:07"},
{"history_id":"1591","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"859-78x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":858,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":859,\"numB\":858}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":781,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":859,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8591,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":781,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:07"},
{"history_id":"1592","user_id":"81","game_stage":"6","question":"78÷3÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:11"},
{"history_id":"1593","user_id":"61","game_stage":"9","question":"112x8+277","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":896,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":896,\"numB\":277}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":453,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":277}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:13"},
{"history_id":"1594","user_id":"73","game_stage":"7","question":"286-79-184","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":286,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":207,\"numB\":184}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":181,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":286,\"numB\":105}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:14"},
{"history_id":"1595","user_id":"60","game_stage":"9","question":"338-22x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":338,\"numB\":242}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":338,\"numB\":242}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:18"},
{"history_id":"1596","user_id":"71","game_stage":"7","question":"70x6÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:27"},
{"history_id":"1597","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"30÷15+109","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":109}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":109}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:29"},
{"history_id":"1598","user_id":"80","game_stage":"8","question":"174+112÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":286,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:36"},
{"history_id":"1599","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"62-35-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:40"},
{"history_id":"1600","user_id":"72","game_stage":"9","question":"21÷3+199","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":199}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":199}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:48"},
{"history_id":"1601","user_id":"60","game_stage":"9","question":"48-143÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:52"},
{"history_id":"1602","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"196-107x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":107}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":107}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:10:55"},
{"history_id":"1603","user_id":"82","game_stage":"8","question":"729-54x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":702,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":729,\"numB\":702}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":695,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":729,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":695,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:11:12"},
{"history_id":"1604","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"95x7-103","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":665,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":562,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":665,\"numB\":103}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":103}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:11:23"},
{"history_id":"1605","user_id":"61","game_stage":"9","question":"41x8+114","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":442,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":328,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":114}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":502,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":122}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:11:29"},
{"history_id":"1606","user_id":"80","game_stage":"8","question":"122÷61-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:11:40"},
{"history_id":"1607","user_id":"72","game_stage":"9","question":"30-69÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:11:47"},
{"history_id":"1608","user_id":"103","game_stage":"2","question":"43-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:28:31"},
{"history_id":"1609","user_id":"102","game_stage":"2","question":"79-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:28:35"},
{"history_id":"1610","user_id":"108","game_stage":"2","question":"87-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:28:49"},
{"history_id":"1611","user_id":"99","game_stage":"2","question":"95-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:28:50"},
{"history_id":"1612","user_id":"100","game_stage":"2","question":"8+20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:28:52"},
{"history_id":"1613","user_id":"97","game_stage":"2","question":"35+4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:03"},
{"history_id":"1614","user_id":"109","game_stage":"2","question":"39+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:05"},
{"history_id":"1615","user_id":"90","game_stage":"2","question":"70+18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:25"},
{"history_id":"1616","user_id":"95","game_stage":"2","question":"95-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:31"},
{"history_id":"1617","user_id":"93","game_stage":"2","question":"72+82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:32"},
{"history_id":"1618","user_id":"108","game_stage":"2","question":"63+58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:47"},
{"history_id":"1619","user_id":"88","game_stage":"2","question":"88+64","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:53"},
{"history_id":"1620","user_id":"101","game_stage":"2","question":"57-44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:54"},
{"history_id":"1621","user_id":"111","game_stage":"2","question":"73-24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:29:58"},
{"history_id":"1622","user_id":"102","game_stage":"2","question":"38+16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:30:04"},
{"history_id":"1623","user_id":"103","game_stage":"2","question":"38+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:30:10"},
{"history_id":"1624","user_id":"99","game_stage":"2","question":"31-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:30:12"},
{"history_id":"1625","user_id":"100","game_stage":"2","question":"78-47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:30:14"},
{"history_id":"1626","user_id":"109","game_stage":"2","question":"30+76","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":76}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":76}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:30:27"},
{"history_id":"1627","user_id":"97","game_stage":"2","question":"60-32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:30:40"},
{"history_id":"1628","user_id":"92","game_stage":"2","question":"84+75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:30:47"},
{"history_id":"1629","user_id":"93","game_stage":"2","question":"25+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:05"},
{"history_id":"1630","user_id":"116","game_stage":"2","question":"84+65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:07"},
{"history_id":"1631","user_id":"95","game_stage":"2","question":"82-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:09"},
{"history_id":"1632","user_id":"108","game_stage":"2","question":"46+6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:11"},
{"history_id":"1633","user_id":"88","game_stage":"2","question":"55+38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:13"},
{"history_id":"1634","user_id":"101","game_stage":"2","question":"36-32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:15"},
{"history_id":"1635","user_id":"91","game_stage":"2","question":"82-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:17"},
{"history_id":"1636","user_id":"90","game_stage":"2","question":"95-45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:20"},
{"history_id":"1637","user_id":"95","game_stage":"2","question":"56-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:30"},
{"history_id":"1638","user_id":"93","game_stage":"2","question":"80-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:39"},
{"history_id":"1639","user_id":"112","game_stage":"2","question":"30+33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:52"},
{"history_id":"1640","user_id":"105","game_stage":"2","question":"51-25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:31:59"},
{"history_id":"1641","user_id":"111","game_stage":"2","question":"71+41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:01"},
{"history_id":"1642","user_id":"100","game_stage":"2","question":"95+66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:07"},
{"history_id":"1643","user_id":"110","game_stage":"2","question":"92-22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:09"},
{"history_id":"1644","user_id":"115","game_stage":"2","question":"48+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:12"},
{"history_id":"1645","user_id":"92","game_stage":"2","question":"72-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:22"},
{"history_id":"1646","user_id":"116","game_stage":"2","question":"18+11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:24"},
{"history_id":"1647","user_id":"89","game_stage":"2","question":"99-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:34"},
{"history_id":"1648","user_id":"109","game_stage":"2","question":"31+42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:36"},
{"history_id":"1649","user_id":"103","game_stage":"2","question":"20-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:45"},
{"history_id":"1650","user_id":"102","game_stage":"2","question":"19+19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:45"},
{"history_id":"1651","user_id":"99","game_stage":"2","question":"3+49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:32:49"},
{"history_id":"1652","user_id":"104","game_stage":"2","question":"71-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:00"},
{"history_id":"1653","user_id":"98","game_stage":"2","question":"20+13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:05"},
{"history_id":"1654","user_id":"113","game_stage":"2","question":"19+28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:06"},
{"history_id":"1655","user_id":"95","game_stage":"2","question":"45-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:12"},
{"history_id":"1656","user_id":"91","game_stage":"2","question":"4+70","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":70}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:16"},
{"history_id":"1657","user_id":"88","game_stage":"2","question":"81-29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:17"},
{"history_id":"1658","user_id":"110","game_stage":"2","question":"79-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:33"},
{"history_id":"1659","user_id":"108","game_stage":"2","question":"92+14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:35"},
{"history_id":"1660","user_id":"90","game_stage":"2","question":"92+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:35"},
{"history_id":"1661","user_id":"107","game_stage":"2","question":"56+82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:41"},
{"history_id":"1662","user_id":"101","game_stage":"2","question":"69+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:42"},
{"history_id":"1663","user_id":"112","game_stage":"2","question":"97+49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:45"},
{"history_id":"1664","user_id":"100","game_stage":"3","question":"22÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:57"},
{"history_id":"1665","user_id":"93","game_stage":"2","question":"65-21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:58"},
{"history_id":"1666","user_id":"115","game_stage":"2","question":"54-33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:33:58"},
{"history_id":"1667","user_id":"97","game_stage":"2","question":"81+36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:01"},
{"history_id":"1668","user_id":"111","game_stage":"2","question":"75+2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:01"},
{"history_id":"1669","user_id":"105","game_stage":"2","question":"61+24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:21"},
{"history_id":"1670","user_id":"94","game_stage":"2","question":"82+37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:22"},
{"history_id":"1671","user_id":"102","game_stage":"3","question":"24x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:25"},
{"history_id":"1672","user_id":"104","game_stage":"2","question":"91-43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:26"},
{"history_id":"1673","user_id":"100","game_stage":"3","question":"70÷35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:27"},
{"history_id":"1674","user_id":"106","game_stage":"2","question":"30+12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:34"},
{"history_id":"1675","user_id":"96","game_stage":"2","question":"79-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:36"},
{"history_id":"1676","user_id":"103","game_stage":"3","question":"82÷41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:38"},
{"history_id":"1677","user_id":"98","game_stage":"2","question":"26+47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:48"},
{"history_id":"1678","user_id":"100","game_stage":"3","question":"38x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":228,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":228,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:55"},
{"history_id":"1679","user_id":"89","game_stage":"2","question":"68+89","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:58"},
{"history_id":"1680","user_id":"113","game_stage":"2","question":"92+61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:34:58"},
{"history_id":"1681","user_id":"95","game_stage":"3","question":"13x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:07"},
{"history_id":"1682","user_id":"99","game_stage":"3","question":"31x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:16"},
{"history_id":"1683","user_id":"95","game_stage":"3","question":"33x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:23"},
{"history_id":"1684","user_id":"103","game_stage":"3","question":"90÷15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:23"},
{"history_id":"1685","user_id":"90","game_stage":"3","question":"36x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:25"},
{"history_id":"1686","user_id":"108","game_stage":"3","question":"45x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:25"},
{"history_id":"1687","user_id":"102","game_stage":"3","question":"37x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:27"},
{"history_id":"1688","user_id":"110","game_stage":"2","question":"55-35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:30"},
{"history_id":"1689","user_id":"114","game_stage":"2","question":"48-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:31"},
{"history_id":"1690","user_id":"88","game_stage":"3","question":"54÷18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:31"},
{"history_id":"1691","user_id":"91","game_stage":"2","question":"97-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:31"},
{"history_id":"1692","user_id":"116","game_stage":"2","question":"96+14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:33"},
{"history_id":"1693","user_id":"97","game_stage":"2","question":"87+86","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":86}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:38"},
{"history_id":"1694","user_id":"93","game_stage":"3","question":"82÷41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:43"},
{"history_id":"1695","user_id":"94","game_stage":"2","question":"38-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:50"},
{"history_id":"1696","user_id":"101","game_stage":"3","question":"70÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:55"},
{"history_id":"1697","user_id":"112","game_stage":"2","question":"46+33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:59"},
{"history_id":"1698","user_id":"115","game_stage":"2","question":"36-25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:35:59"},
{"history_id":"1699","user_id":"103","game_stage":"3","question":"11x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:00"},
{"history_id":"1700","user_id":"92","game_stage":"2","question":"50-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:04"},
{"history_id":"1701","user_id":"95","game_stage":"3","question":"39x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:10"},
{"history_id":"1702","user_id":"88","game_stage":"3","question":"33÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:15"},
{"history_id":"1703","user_id":"108","game_stage":"3","question":"48x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:17"},
{"history_id":"1704","user_id":"104","game_stage":"2","question":"41-32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:20"},
{"history_id":"1705","user_id":"93","game_stage":"3","question":"90÷15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:24"},
{"history_id":"1706","user_id":"111","game_stage":"3","question":"75÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:24"},
{"history_id":"1707","user_id":"102","game_stage":"3","question":"11x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:26"},
{"history_id":"1708","user_id":"99","game_stage":"3","question":"18x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:38"},
{"history_id":"1709","user_id":"100","game_stage":"4","question":"83x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":498,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":498,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:38"},
{"history_id":"1710","user_id":"95","game_stage":"3","question":"32x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:40"},
{"history_id":"1711","user_id":"96","game_stage":"2","question":"57-41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:49"},
{"history_id":"1712","user_id":"88","game_stage":"3","question":"50÷25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:50"},
{"history_id":"1713","user_id":"101","game_stage":"3","question":"40÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:51"},
{"history_id":"1714","user_id":"106","game_stage":"2","question":"50-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:36:52"},
{"history_id":"1715","user_id":"100","game_stage":"4","question":"20x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:02"},
{"history_id":"1716","user_id":"90","game_stage":"3","question":"39x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:08"},
{"history_id":"1717","user_id":"93","game_stage":"3","question":"33÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:13"},
{"history_id":"1718","user_id":"114","game_stage":"2","question":"74-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:16"},
{"history_id":"1719","user_id":"108","game_stage":"3","question":"26x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:17"},
{"history_id":"1720","user_id":"89","game_stage":"2","question":"37+32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:17"},
{"history_id":"1721","user_id":"110","game_stage":"3","question":"38÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:22"},
{"history_id":"1722","user_id":"113","game_stage":"2","question":"85+10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:25"},
{"history_id":"1723","user_id":"100","game_stage":"4","question":"57+94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:29"},
{"history_id":"1724","user_id":"97","game_stage":"2","question":"99-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:34"},
{"history_id":"1725","user_id":"103","game_stage":"4","question":"110÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:42"},
{"history_id":"1726","user_id":"116","game_stage":"3","question":"16÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:45"},
{"history_id":"1727","user_id":"101","game_stage":"3","question":"35x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:46"},
{"history_id":"1728","user_id":"96","game_stage":"2","question":"47+31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:46"},
{"history_id":"1729","user_id":"105","game_stage":"2","question":"65-24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:49"},
{"history_id":"1730","user_id":"111","game_stage":"3","question":"92÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:50"},
{"history_id":"1731","user_id":"91","game_stage":"3","question":"23x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:51"},
{"history_id":"1732","user_id":"113","game_stage":"2","question":"56-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:52"},
{"history_id":"1733","user_id":"110","game_stage":"3","question":"30x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:57"},
{"history_id":"1734","user_id":"99","game_stage":"3","question":"46x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:37:59"},
{"history_id":"1735","user_id":"102","game_stage":"4","question":"103-86","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":86}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:00"},
{"history_id":"1736","user_id":"94","game_stage":"2","question":"98-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:03"},
{"history_id":"1737","user_id":"103","game_stage":"4","question":"39÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:07"},
{"history_id":"1738","user_id":"95","game_stage":"4","question":"142+54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:10"},
{"history_id":"1739","user_id":"104","game_stage":"3","question":"88÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:12"},
{"history_id":"1740","user_id":"116","game_stage":"3","question":"32÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:15"},
{"history_id":"1741","user_id":"92","game_stage":"3","question":"75÷25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:19"},
{"history_id":"1742","user_id":"88","game_stage":"4","question":"196÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:23"},
{"history_id":"1743","user_id":"112","game_stage":"3","question":"39÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:25"},
{"history_id":"1744","user_id":"99","game_stage":"3","question":"22x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:26"},
{"history_id":"1745","user_id":"103","game_stage":"4","question":"4x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:32"},
{"history_id":"1746","user_id":"98","game_stage":"2","question":"73-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:37"},
{"history_id":"1747","user_id":"106","game_stage":"2","question":"8+21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:39"},
{"history_id":"1748","user_id":"100","game_stage":"6","question":"28+150+87","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":150}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":265,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":87}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":150}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":87}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:44"},
{"history_id":"1749","user_id":"95","game_stage":"4","question":"15x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:44"},
{"history_id":"1750","user_id":"111","game_stage":"3","question":"21÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:47"},
{"history_id":"1751","user_id":"90","game_stage":"4","question":"53-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:51"},
{"history_id":"1752","user_id":"88","game_stage":"4","question":"172+97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:54"},
{"history_id":"1753","user_id":"93","game_stage":"4","question":"109-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:55"},
{"history_id":"1754","user_id":"115","game_stage":"3","question":"87÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:56"},
{"history_id":"1755","user_id":"109","game_stage":"3","question":"85÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:56"},
{"history_id":"1756","user_id":"110","game_stage":"3","question":"57÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:56"},
{"history_id":"1757","user_id":"103","game_stage":"4","question":"50-29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:38:59"},
{"history_id":"1758","user_id":"89","game_stage":"3","question":"98÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:04"},
{"history_id":"1759","user_id":"107","game_stage":"2","question":"24-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:05"},
{"history_id":"1760","user_id":"116","game_stage":"3","question":"98÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:05"},
{"history_id":"1761","user_id":"102","game_stage":"4","question":"129÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:06"},
{"history_id":"1762","user_id":"98","game_stage":"2","question":"63-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:08"},
{"history_id":"1763","user_id":"104","game_stage":"3","question":"96÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:11"},
{"history_id":"1764","user_id":"92","game_stage":"3","question":"19x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:16"},
{"history_id":"1765","user_id":"95","game_stage":"4","question":"145-63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:18"},
{"history_id":"1766","user_id":"97","game_stage":"3","question":"7x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:20"},
{"history_id":"1767","user_id":"100","game_stage":"6","question":"171-10-111","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":111}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:22"},
{"history_id":"1768","user_id":"88","game_stage":"4","question":"69+71","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":71}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:22"},
{"history_id":"1769","user_id":"112","game_stage":"3","question":"33÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:27"},
{"history_id":"1770","user_id":"108","game_stage":"4","question":"149+94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:28"},
{"history_id":"1771","user_id":"93","game_stage":"4","question":"160-44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:33"},
{"history_id":"1772","user_id":"91","game_stage":"3","question":"28÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:34"},
{"history_id":"1773","user_id":"90","game_stage":"4","question":"120-45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:35"},
{"history_id":"1774","user_id":"96","game_stage":"2","question":"14-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:35"},
{"history_id":"1775","user_id":"101","game_stage":"4","question":"64÷32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:36"},
{"history_id":"1776","user_id":"102","game_stage":"4","question":"86x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":946,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":876,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:36"},
{"history_id":"1777","user_id":"109","game_stage":"3","question":"84÷28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:42"},
{"history_id":"1778","user_id":"103","game_stage":"4","question":"188-78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:43"},
{"history_id":"1779","user_id":"102","game_stage":"4","question":"125-85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:53"},
{"history_id":"1780","user_id":"114","game_stage":"2","question":"70-40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:55"},
{"history_id":"1781","user_id":"115","game_stage":"3","question":"8÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:56"},
{"history_id":"1782","user_id":"92","game_stage":"3","question":"4x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:39:58"},
{"history_id":"1783","user_id":"89","game_stage":"3","question":"32x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:00"},
{"history_id":"1784","user_id":"90","game_stage":"4","question":"106÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:01"},
{"history_id":"1785","user_id":"93","game_stage":"4","question":"35+130","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":130}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:03"},
{"history_id":"1786","user_id":"105","game_stage":"3","question":"81÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:05"},
{"history_id":"1787","user_id":"106","game_stage":"3","question":"43x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:09"},
{"history_id":"1788","user_id":"108","game_stage":"4","question":"181-66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:10"},
{"history_id":"1789","user_id":"94","game_stage":"3","question":"47x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:13"},
{"history_id":"1790","user_id":"100","game_stage":"6","question":"135+67-109","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":202,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":202,\"numB\":109}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":202,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":202,\"numB\":109}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:17"},
{"history_id":"1791","user_id":"107","game_stage":"2","question":"29-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:20"},
{"history_id":"1792","user_id":"90","game_stage":"4","question":"194+24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:21"},
{"history_id":"1793","user_id":"98","game_stage":"3","question":"34÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:22"},
{"history_id":"1794","user_id":"91","game_stage":"3","question":"2x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:26"},
{"history_id":"1795","user_id":"110","game_stage":"4","question":"40+30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:26"},
{"history_id":"1796","user_id":"101","game_stage":"4","question":"56+119","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":119}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":119}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:26"},
{"history_id":"1797","user_id":"104","game_stage":"3","question":"72÷24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:27"},
{"history_id":"1798","user_id":"99","game_stage":"4","question":"116-92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:30"},
{"history_id":"1799","user_id":"94","game_stage":"3","question":"85÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:32"},
{"history_id":"1800","user_id":"95","game_stage":"6","question":"119+21+36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:32"},
{"history_id":"1801","user_id":"116","game_stage":"4","question":"35-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:33"},
{"history_id":"1802","user_id":"106","game_stage":"3","question":"66÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:35"},
{"history_id":"1803","user_id":"109","game_stage":"3","question":"92÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:37"},
{"history_id":"1804","user_id":"108","game_stage":"4","question":"72+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:41"},
{"history_id":"1805","user_id":"111","game_stage":"4","question":"170-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:44"},
{"history_id":"1806","user_id":"113","game_stage":"3","question":"90÷18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:45"},
{"history_id":"1807","user_id":"105","game_stage":"3","question":"48x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:47"},
{"history_id":"1808","user_id":"88","game_stage":"6","question":"150-92+128","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":128}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":128}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:50"},
{"history_id":"1809","user_id":"112","game_stage":"3","question":"96÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:54"},
{"history_id":"1810","user_id":"99","game_stage":"4","question":"81x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:56"},
{"history_id":"1811","user_id":"115","game_stage":"3","question":"42x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:57"},
{"history_id":"1812","user_id":"98","game_stage":"3","question":"11x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:57"},
{"history_id":"1813","user_id":"100","game_stage":"6","question":"67-46+35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:40:59"},
{"history_id":"1814","user_id":"97","game_stage":"3","question":"34÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:00"},
{"history_id":"1815","user_id":"110","game_stage":"4","question":"40÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:02"},
{"history_id":"1816","user_id":"89","game_stage":"3","question":"32÷16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:05"},
{"history_id":"1817","user_id":"106","game_stage":"3","question":"10x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:09"},
{"history_id":"1818","user_id":"102","game_stage":"6","question":"69-13-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:10"},
{"history_id":"1819","user_id":"108","game_stage":"4","question":"180-99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:12"},
{"history_id":"1820","user_id":"116","game_stage":"4","question":"174÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:12"},
{"history_id":"1821","user_id":"111","game_stage":"4","question":"52-44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:17"},
{"history_id":"1822","user_id":"109","game_stage":"3","question":"11x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:21"},
{"history_id":"1823","user_id":"110","game_stage":"4","question":"103-80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:25"},
{"history_id":"1824","user_id":"95","game_stage":"6","question":"73x8x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":584,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5840,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":584,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5840,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:25"},
{"history_id":"1825","user_id":"100","game_stage":"6","question":"25÷5x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:25"},
{"history_id":"1826","user_id":"98","game_stage":"3","question":"4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:26"},
{"history_id":"1827","user_id":"99","game_stage":"4","question":"24x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:26"},
{"history_id":"1828","user_id":"105","game_stage":"3","question":"70÷35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:31"},
{"history_id":"1829","user_id":"96","game_stage":"3","question":"20x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:32"},
{"history_id":"1830","user_id":"94","game_stage":"3","question":"32÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:40"},
{"history_id":"1831","user_id":"113","game_stage":"3","question":"80÷20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:42"},
{"history_id":"1832","user_id":"102","game_stage":"6","question":"45x10x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":450,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3400,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":450,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:45"},
{"history_id":"1833","user_id":"99","game_stage":"4","question":"43+27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:46"},
{"history_id":"1834","user_id":"116","game_stage":"4","question":"180÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:47"},
{"history_id":"1835","user_id":"93","game_stage":"6","question":"113+113-74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":74}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:48"},
{"history_id":"1836","user_id":"110","game_stage":"4","question":"151-98","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":98}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":98}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:48"},
{"history_id":"1837","user_id":"88","game_stage":"6","question":"98x9÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":882,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":882,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":882,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":882,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:50"},
{"history_id":"1838","user_id":"103","game_stage":"6","question":"138+73+94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:51"},
{"history_id":"1839","user_id":"92","game_stage":"4","question":"100-25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:41:52"},
{"history_id":"1840","user_id":"91","game_stage":"4","question":"97-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:07"},
{"history_id":"1841","user_id":"96","game_stage":"3","question":"48x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:08"},
{"history_id":"1842","user_id":"104","game_stage":"4","question":"48x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:08"},
{"history_id":"1843","user_id":"103","game_stage":"6","question":"5x5÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:12"},
{"history_id":"1844","user_id":"100","game_stage":"6","question":"85+196+13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":196}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":196}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:14"},
{"history_id":"1845","user_id":"110","game_stage":"4","question":"140-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:14"},
{"history_id":"1846","user_id":"90","game_stage":"6","question":"181-92+169","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":169}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":169}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:20"},
{"history_id":"1847","user_id":"88","game_stage":"6","question":"36-17+143","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":143}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:22"},
{"history_id":"1848","user_id":"97","game_stage":"3","question":"60÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:23"},
{"history_id":"1849","user_id":"92","game_stage":"4","question":"12x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:24"},
{"history_id":"1850","user_id":"101","game_stage":"6","question":"85+106+189","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":189}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":189}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:24"},
{"history_id":"1851","user_id":"115","game_stage":"4","question":"195-89","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:30"},
{"history_id":"1852","user_id":"104","game_stage":"4","question":"123-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:32"},
{"history_id":"1853","user_id":"94","game_stage":"3","question":"39x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:38"},
{"history_id":"1854","user_id":"93","game_stage":"6","question":"171+48-118","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:38"},
{"history_id":"1855","user_id":"103","game_stage":"6","question":"63÷7÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:38"},
{"history_id":"1856","user_id":"95","game_stage":"6","question":"25÷5x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4444,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:44"},
{"history_id":"1857","user_id":"96","game_stage":"3","question":"49÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:46"},
{"history_id":"1858","user_id":"113","game_stage":"3","question":"98÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:46"},
{"history_id":"1859","user_id":"91","game_stage":"4","question":"160+28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:48"},
{"history_id":"1860","user_id":"106","game_stage":"4","question":"171-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:57"},
{"history_id":"1861","user_id":"105","game_stage":"4","question":"58-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:57"},
{"history_id":"1862","user_id":"92","game_stage":"4","question":"127+156","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":283,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":156}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:59"},
{"history_id":"1863","user_id":"102","game_stage":"6","question":"28x11÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":308,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":308,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:42:59"},
{"history_id":"1864","user_id":"116","game_stage":"6","question":"109+161-58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:03"},
{"history_id":"1865","user_id":"114","game_stage":"3","question":"60÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:04"},
{"history_id":"1866","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"31-13+182","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":182}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":312}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:04"},
{"history_id":"1867","user_id":"89","game_stage":"4","question":"196÷28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:04"},
{"history_id":"1868","user_id":"115","game_stage":"4","question":"95x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1045,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1045,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:07"},
{"history_id":"1869","user_id":"95","game_stage":"6","question":"110+137+38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":247,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":247,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:09"},
{"history_id":"1870","user_id":"104","game_stage":"4","question":"86x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:12"},
{"history_id":"1871","user_id":"109","game_stage":"4","question":"101-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:19"},
{"history_id":"1872","user_id":"99","game_stage":"6","question":"78-75+186","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":186}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":261,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":261}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:23"},
{"history_id":"1873","user_id":"98","game_stage":"4","question":"118+39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":257,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:24"},
{"history_id":"1874","user_id":"91","game_stage":"4","question":"80x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:24"},
{"history_id":"1875","user_id":"102","game_stage":"6","question":"34x5x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:27"},
{"history_id":"1876","user_id":"111","game_stage":"6","question":"147+108+22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":277,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":277,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:28"},
{"history_id":"1877","user_id":"106","game_stage":"4","question":"8+188","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":188}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":188}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:28"},
{"history_id":"1878","user_id":"89","game_stage":"4","question":"51x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":561,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:29"},
{"history_id":"1879","user_id":"90","game_stage":"6","question":"86x11÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":946,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":473,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":946,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":946,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":473,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":946,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:32"},
{"history_id":"1880","user_id":"105","game_stage":"4","question":"187÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:35"},
{"history_id":"1881","user_id":"115","game_stage":"4","question":"28+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:36"},
{"history_id":"1882","user_id":"101","game_stage":"6","question":"93x3÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":279,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":279,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:38"},
{"history_id":"1883","user_id":"100","game_stage":"7","question":"202+291-261","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":493,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":202,\"numB\":291}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":493,\"numB\":261}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":291,\"numB\":261}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":202,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:43"},
{"history_id":"1884","user_id":"103","game_stage":"7","question":"210-68-123","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":123}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":123}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:45"},
{"history_id":"1885","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"140-59-74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":74}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:46"},
{"history_id":"1886","user_id":"89","game_stage":"4","question":"174+156","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":156}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:52"},
{"history_id":"1887","user_id":"116","game_stage":"6","question":"90x10x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":900,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11700,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":900,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11700,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:54"},
{"history_id":"1888","user_id":"110","game_stage":"6","question":"193+101-130","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":130}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:54"},
{"history_id":"1889","user_id":"102","game_stage":"6","question":"89+13+182","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":284,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":182}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":284,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":182}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:57"},
{"history_id":"1890","user_id":"105","game_stage":"4","question":"49÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:58"},
{"history_id":"1891","user_id":"109","game_stage":"4","question":"33+105","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":105}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":105}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:43:58"},
{"history_id":"1892","user_id":"93","game_stage":"6","question":"158÷2x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":632,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":632,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:01"},
{"history_id":"1893","user_id":"99","game_stage":"6","question":"158-86-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:01"},
{"history_id":"1894","user_id":"115","game_stage":"4","question":"14+124","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":124}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":124}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:03"},
{"history_id":"1895","user_id":"95","game_stage":"7","question":"40-36-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:05"},
{"history_id":"1896","user_id":"88","game_stage":"7","question":"259-127+181","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":127}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":181}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":127}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":181}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:05"},
{"history_id":"1897","user_id":"106","game_stage":"4","question":"127+124","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":124}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":124}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:06"},
{"history_id":"1898","user_id":"90","game_stage":"6","question":"176÷22÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:07"},
{"history_id":"1899","user_id":"111","game_stage":"6","question":"9x6x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":594,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":594,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:10"},
{"history_id":"1900","user_id":"103","game_stage":"7","question":"70-46+93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:15"},
{"history_id":"1901","user_id":"100","game_stage":"7","question":"204+161-282","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":365,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":365,\"numB\":282}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":365,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":365,\"numB\":282}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:16"},
{"history_id":"1902","user_id":"94","game_stage":"4","question":"12x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:18"},
{"history_id":"1903","user_id":"116","game_stage":"6","question":"2x11÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:19"},
{"history_id":"1904","user_id":"101","game_stage":"6","question":"117+11+154","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":154}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":154}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:20"},
{"history_id":"1905","user_id":"109","game_stage":"4","question":"44÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:21"},
{"history_id":"1906","user_id":"112","game_stage":"4","question":"183-76","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":76}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":76}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:23"},
{"history_id":"1907","user_id":"107","game_stage":"2","question":"30-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:28"},
{"history_id":"1908","user_id":"105","game_stage":"4","question":"57÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:30"},
{"history_id":"1909","user_id":"106","game_stage":"4","question":"77x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:37"},
{"history_id":"1910","user_id":"114","game_stage":"3","question":"23x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:41"},
{"history_id":"1911","user_id":"98","game_stage":"4","question":"90÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:43"},
{"history_id":"1912","user_id":"110","game_stage":"6","question":"10x6÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:44"},
{"history_id":"1913","user_id":"111","game_stage":"6","question":"116-55+18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:46"},
{"history_id":"1914","user_id":"95","game_stage":"7","question":"70x6÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:48"},
{"history_id":"1915","user_id":"94","game_stage":"4","question":"83-61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:50"},
{"history_id":"1916","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"36x12x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4752,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":432,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4752,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":432,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:52"},
{"history_id":"1917","user_id":"109","game_stage":"4","question":"173-60","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:53"},
{"history_id":"1918","user_id":"99","game_stage":"6","question":"61-7+184","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":184}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":184}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:55"},
{"history_id":"1919","user_id":"93","game_stage":"6","question":"83+37+60","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":60}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:55"},
{"history_id":"1920","user_id":"104","game_stage":"6","question":"149+149+154","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":452,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":154}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":452,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":154}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:57"},
{"history_id":"1921","user_id":"103","game_stage":"7","question":"189+83+48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:58"},
{"history_id":"1922","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"183+90","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":273,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":273,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:44:59"},
{"history_id":"1923","user_id":"112","game_stage":"4","question":"43+15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:02"},
{"history_id":"1924","user_id":"102","game_stage":"7","question":"177-118+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":118}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":118}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:12"},
{"history_id":"1925","user_id":"98","game_stage":"4","question":"132÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:14"},
{"history_id":"1926","user_id":"113","game_stage":"4","question":"92÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:17"},
{"history_id":"1927","user_id":"115","game_stage":"6","question":"197-27-93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:19"},
{"history_id":"1928","user_id":"110","game_stage":"6","question":"190+80+199","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":469,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":199}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":469,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":199}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:26"},
{"history_id":"1929","user_id":"94","game_stage":"4","question":"165+6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":17188877,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:28"},
{"history_id":"1930","user_id":"95","game_stage":"7","question":"86x10x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":860,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":860,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":860,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":860,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:28"},
{"history_id":"1931","user_id":"116","game_stage":"7","question":"146-134-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":122}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:29"},
{"history_id":"1932","user_id":"112","game_stage":"4","question":"105+180","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":180}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":180}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:31"},
{"history_id":"1933","user_id":"103","game_stage":"7","question":"55÷5x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:33"},
{"history_id":"1934","user_id":"88","game_stage":"7","question":"77x15÷77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1155,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1055,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1055,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis04mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:34"},
{"history_id":"1935","user_id":"104","game_stage":"6","question":"42x3x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":882,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":882,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:36"},
{"history_id":"1936","user_id":"90","game_stage":"7","question":"199+100+162","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":100}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":461,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":162}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":100}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":461,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":162}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:45"},
{"history_id":"1937","user_id":"113","game_stage":"4","question":"175÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:50"},
{"history_id":"1938","user_id":"94","game_stage":"4","question":"185÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:52"},
{"history_id":"1939","user_id":"98","game_stage":"4","question":"98x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":784,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":784,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:55"},
{"history_id":"1940","user_id":"112","game_stage":"4","question":"60x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:58"},
{"history_id":"1941","user_id":"101","game_stage":"7","question":"255+205+140","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":460,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":205}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":460,\"numB\":140}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":460,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":205}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":460,\"numB\":140}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:59"},
{"history_id":"1942","user_id":"89","game_stage":"6","question":"187-6-125","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":181,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":125}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":475,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1395,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":475}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:45:59"},
{"history_id":"1943","user_id":"91","game_stage":"6","question":"68+65-54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:00"},
{"history_id":"1944","user_id":"93","game_stage":"7","question":"270+95-318","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":365,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":365,\"numB\":318}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":365,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":365,\"numB\":318}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:02"},
{"history_id":"1945","user_id":"92","game_stage":"4","question":"95x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":950,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":950,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:09"},
{"history_id":"1946","user_id":"105","game_stage":"6","question":"130-84-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:09"},
{"history_id":"1947","user_id":"116","game_stage":"7","question":"273-81+5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":197,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":197,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:10"},
{"history_id":"1948","user_id":"106","game_stage":"6","question":"149+72-81","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":81}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:12"},
{"history_id":"1949","user_id":"113","game_stage":"4","question":"81x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:13"},
{"history_id":"1950","user_id":"88","game_stage":"7","question":"163-28+79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:14"},
{"history_id":"1951","user_id":"111","game_stage":"7","question":"295+86+22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":381,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":403,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":381,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":403,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":108}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:15"},
{"history_id":"1952","user_id":"104","game_stage":"6","question":"196÷14x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:16"},
{"history_id":"1953","user_id":"115","game_stage":"6","question":"62÷31x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:18"},
{"history_id":"1954","user_id":"114","game_stage":"3","question":"90÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:20"},
{"history_id":"1955","user_id":"94","game_stage":"4","question":"113-62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:21"},
{"history_id":"1956","user_id":"103","game_stage":"7","question":"249+180-426","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":429,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":180}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":429,\"numB\":426}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":429,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":180}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":429,\"numB\":426}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:23"},
{"history_id":"1957","user_id":"99","game_stage":"6","question":"168÷84÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:24"},
{"history_id":"1958","user_id":"102","game_stage":"7","question":"74÷2÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:25"},
{"history_id":"1959","user_id":"112","game_stage":"4","question":"175-36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:29"},
{"history_id":"1960","user_id":"95","game_stage":"8","question":"66÷33+152","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":152}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":152}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:37"},
{"history_id":"1961","user_id":"93","game_stage":"7","question":"190÷95÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:40"},
{"history_id":"1962","user_id":"107","game_stage":"3","question":"91÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:43"},
{"history_id":"1963","user_id":"109","game_stage":"6","question":"34+109-67","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:45"},
{"history_id":"1964","user_id":"90","game_stage":"7","question":"254÷2x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":508,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":508,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:45"},
{"history_id":"1965","user_id":"91","game_stage":"6","question":"12÷4x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:51"},
{"history_id":"1966","user_id":"89","game_stage":"6","question":"98-84-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:52"},
{"history_id":"1967","user_id":"116","game_stage":"7","question":"245÷5x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":245,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":245,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:52"},
{"history_id":"1968","user_id":"113","game_stage":"4","question":"114-93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:53"},
{"history_id":"1969","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"194-58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:53"},
{"history_id":"1970","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"162÷54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:58"},
{"history_id":"1971","user_id":"115","game_stage":"6","question":"37+184+123","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":123}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":123}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:46:59"},
{"history_id":"1972","user_id":"111","game_stage":"7","question":"72x6x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1728,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":432,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1728,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:01"},
{"history_id":"1973","user_id":"99","game_stage":"6","question":"173-1+115","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":287,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":115}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":287,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":115}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:12"},
{"history_id":"1974","user_id":"93","game_stage":"7","question":"216÷108x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:18"},
{"history_id":"1975","user_id":"106","game_stage":"6","question":"74+99+86","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":259,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":259,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":86}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:19"},
{"history_id":"1976","user_id":"110","game_stage":"7","question":"236-81-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:19"},
{"history_id":"1977","user_id":"109","game_stage":"6","question":"130÷65x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:30"},
{"history_id":"1978","user_id":"94","game_stage":"6","question":"80-73-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:32"},
{"history_id":"1979","user_id":"103","game_stage":"8","question":"129÷3+11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:34"},
{"history_id":"1980","user_id":"102","game_stage":"7","question":"267÷3x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":623,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":593,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:34"},
{"history_id":"1981","user_id":"89","game_stage":"6","question":"169+195+110","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":364,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":195}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":474,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":364,\"numB\":110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":346,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":195}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":456,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":346,\"numB\":110}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:35"},
{"history_id":"1982","user_id":"107","game_stage":"3","question":"19x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:35"},
{"history_id":"1983","user_id":"92","game_stage":"6","question":"177-43-121","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":121}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":121}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:39"},
{"history_id":"1984","user_id":"104","game_stage":"7","question":"43+148+35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":148}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":148}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:43"},
{"history_id":"1985","user_id":"95","game_stage":"8","question":"117-88x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:43"},
{"history_id":"1986","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"136÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:44"},
{"history_id":"1987","user_id":"111","game_stage":"7","question":"280-69+94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:50"},
{"history_id":"1988","user_id":"88","game_stage":"8","question":"27x9+183","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":426,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":183}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":426,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":183}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:52"},
{"history_id":"1989","user_id":"91","game_stage":"6","question":"159÷53x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:55"},
{"history_id":"1990","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"27+155-135","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":155}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":135}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":155}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":135}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:57"},
{"history_id":"1991","user_id":"109","game_stage":"6","question":"73x1÷73","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":73}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":73}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:58"},
{"history_id":"1992","user_id":"105","game_stage":"6","question":"62x12÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":744,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":744,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":744,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":744,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:47:59"},
{"history_id":"1993","user_id":"106","game_stage":"6","question":"25x5÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:03"},
{"history_id":"1994","user_id":"90","game_stage":"7","question":"219-31+266","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":454,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":266}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":444,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":266}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:07"},
{"history_id":"1995","user_id":"92","game_stage":"6","question":"4x8÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:08"},
{"history_id":"1996","user_id":"98","game_stage":"6","question":"117-32+122","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":32}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":122}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":122}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":203}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:10"},
{"history_id":"1997","user_id":"101","game_stage":"7","question":"79x9÷79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":711,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":711,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":701,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":701,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:12"},
{"history_id":"1998","user_id":"116","game_stage":"7","question":"21x14x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:12"},
{"history_id":"1999","user_id":"100","game_stage":"7","question":"69x14÷21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":966,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":966,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":966,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":966,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:15"},
{"history_id":"2000","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"166-61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:15"},
{"history_id":"2001","user_id":"103","game_stage":"8","question":"61-138÷46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:17"},
{"history_id":"2002","user_id":"107","game_stage":"3","question":"30÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:18"},
{"history_id":"2003","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"22+64÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:19"},
{"history_id":"2004","user_id":"99","game_stage":"6","question":"45x3÷27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:22"},
{"history_id":"2005","user_id":"89","game_stage":"6","question":"25+37+106","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":106}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":106}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:25"},
{"history_id":"2006","user_id":"115","game_stage":"7","question":"158-109-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:29"},
{"history_id":"2007","user_id":"94","game_stage":"6","question":"69x6x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":414,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4554,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":414,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":414,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4554,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":414,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:30"},
{"history_id":"2008","user_id":"105","game_stage":"6","question":"18x8÷48","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:30"},
{"history_id":"2009","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"55÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:31"},
{"history_id":"2010","user_id":"102","game_stage":"7","question":"35+105+288","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":105}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":428,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":288}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":105}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":428,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":288}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:34"},
{"history_id":"2011","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"104-96+122","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":122}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":122}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:35"},
{"history_id":"2012","user_id":"95","game_stage":"8","question":"174+82x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":738,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":912,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":738}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":738,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":912,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":738}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:39"},
{"history_id":"2013","user_id":"110","game_stage":"7","question":"211-68+58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":126}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:41"},
{"history_id":"2014","user_id":"103","game_stage":"8","question":"84+105÷35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:43"},
{"history_id":"2015","user_id":"88","game_stage":"8","question":"82x6-283","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":492,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":492,\"numB\":283}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":492,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":492,\"numB\":283}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:43"},
{"history_id":"2016","user_id":"104","game_stage":"7","question":"67x11x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":737,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11792,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":737,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":737,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11792,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":737,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:47"},
{"history_id":"2017","user_id":"100","game_stage":"7","question":"34x2÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:48"},
{"history_id":"2018","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"3x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:50"},
{"history_id":"2019","user_id":"116","game_stage":"7","question":"187+208-44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":395,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":208}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":395,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":395,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":208}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":395,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:55"},
{"history_id":"2020","user_id":"92","game_stage":"6","question":"87+144+81","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":81}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:48:56"},
{"history_id":"2021","user_id":"94","game_stage":"6","question":"190+182-72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":372,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":372,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:02"},
{"history_id":"2022","user_id":"106","game_stage":"6","question":"84+196-141","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":196}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":141}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":196}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":141}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:02"},
{"history_id":"2023","user_id":"98","game_stage":"6","question":"49+156-151","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":156}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":156}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":151}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:05"},
{"history_id":"2024","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"57÷3+163","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":163}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":163}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6722,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":166}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:10"},
{"history_id":"2025","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"186-96","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:12"},
{"history_id":"2026","user_id":"110","game_stage":"7","question":"245+71+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":245,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":388,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":316,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":388,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":245,\"numB\":143}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:16"},
{"history_id":"2027","user_id":"88","game_stage":"8","question":"110÷55-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:19"},
{"history_id":"2028","user_id":"115","game_stage":"7","question":"127x10÷127","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1270,\"numB\":127}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1270,\"numB\":127}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:22"},
{"history_id":"2029","user_id":"99","game_stage":"6","question":"84÷12÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:24"},
{"history_id":"2030","user_id":"109","game_stage":"7","question":"248-71-66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":248,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":248,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:27"},
{"history_id":"2031","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"35x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":385,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis08","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:29"},
{"history_id":"2032","user_id":"112","game_stage":"6","question":"86-51+138","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":138}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":138}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":371,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":285}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:33"},
{"history_id":"2033","user_id":"90","game_stage":"7","question":"95x16x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":13680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1520,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":144}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:34"},
{"history_id":"2034","user_id":"89","game_stage":"6","question":"27x13x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3861,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":351,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":351,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:38"},
{"history_id":"2035","user_id":"99","game_stage":"6","question":"92+2+7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:46"},
{"history_id":"2036","user_id":"98","game_stage":"6","question":"10x12x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:47"},
{"history_id":"2037","user_id":"110","game_stage":"7","question":"78÷13x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:57"},
{"history_id":"2038","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"17x11+195","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":382,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":195}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":195}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:49:57"},
{"history_id":"2039","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"20÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:00"},
{"history_id":"2040","user_id":"107","game_stage":"4","question":"44x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":484,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":484,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:01"},
{"history_id":"2041","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"35-27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:02"},
{"history_id":"2042","user_id":"113","game_stage":"6","question":"98+112-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:08"},
{"history_id":"2043","user_id":"105","game_stage":"7","question":"57+182-132","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":239,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":132}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":239,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":132}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:10"},
{"history_id":"2044","user_id":"116","game_stage":"8","question":"85x7+4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":595,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":599,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":595,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":935,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:11"},
{"history_id":"2045","user_id":"98","game_stage":"6","question":"90x9÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":810,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":810,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":720,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":720,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:18"},
{"history_id":"2046","user_id":"103","game_stage":"9","question":"97x9+199","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":873,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1072,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":873,\"numB\":199}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":873,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1072,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":873,\"numB\":199}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:19"},
{"history_id":"2047","user_id":"104","game_stage":"7","question":"132x11÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1452,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":363,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1452,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1451,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":362,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1451,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:22"},
{"history_id":"2048","user_id":"112","game_stage":"6","question":"184+28-102","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":102}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":102}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:22"},
{"history_id":"2049","user_id":"110","game_stage":"7","question":"72x2x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:31"},
{"history_id":"2050","user_id":"109","game_stage":"7","question":"188÷94÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:32"},
{"history_id":"2051","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"88x7÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":616,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":616,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:33"},
{"history_id":"2052","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"129÷3+148","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":148}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":148}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:33"},
{"history_id":"2053","user_id":"107","game_stage":"4","question":"120÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:35"},
{"history_id":"2054","user_id":"89","game_stage":"6","question":"64x9x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":576,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":576,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:37"},
{"history_id":"2055","user_id":"101","game_stage":"7","question":"116÷2÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:40"},
{"history_id":"2056","user_id":"115","game_stage":"7","question":"87÷3÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:43"},
{"history_id":"2057","user_id":"98","game_stage":"6","question":"174÷58x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:50:51"},
{"history_id":"2058","user_id":"109","game_stage":"7","question":"125x8÷200","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1000,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1000,\"numB\":200}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":200}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:06"},
{"history_id":"2059","user_id":"99","game_stage":"7","question":"144-87-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:12"},
{"history_id":"2060","user_id":"109","game_stage":"7","question":"141x10÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1410,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1410,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:25"},
{"history_id":"2061","user_id":"101","game_stage":"7","question":"234+113-25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":347,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":322,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":347,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":347,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":322,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":347,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:29"},
{"history_id":"2062","user_id":"89","game_stage":"6","question":"127+153-107","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":153}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":107}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":153}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":107}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:30"},
{"history_id":"2063","user_id":"112","game_stage":"6","question":"19x7÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:31"},
{"history_id":"2064","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"175÷7x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:34"},
{"history_id":"2065","user_id":"90","game_stage":"7","question":"225-144+232","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":232}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":232}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:35"},
{"history_id":"2066","user_id":"88","game_stage":"9","question":"61x8+261","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":488,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":749,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":488,\"numB\":261}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":488,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":749,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":488,\"numB\":261}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:35"},
{"history_id":"2067","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"126÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:38"},
{"history_id":"2068","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"194÷97-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:47"},
{"history_id":"2069","user_id":"107","game_stage":"4","question":"98-55","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":55}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:51"},
{"history_id":"2070","user_id":"105","game_stage":"7","question":"112x10x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1120,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1120,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:53"},
{"history_id":"2071","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"32x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:58"},
{"history_id":"2072","user_id":"113","game_stage":"6","question":"44-12+83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:51:59"},
{"history_id":"2073","user_id":"98","game_stage":"7","question":"245+257-463","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":502,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":245,\"numB\":257}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":502,\"numB\":463}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":245,\"numB\":257}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":463}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:52:14"},
{"history_id":"2074","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"46x4÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:52:15"},
{"history_id":"2075","user_id":"112","game_stage":"6","question":"42÷14x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:52:16"},
{"history_id":"2076","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"53x1-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:52:30"},
{"history_id":"2077","user_id":"107","game_stage":"4","question":"117-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:52:36"},
{"history_id":"2078","user_id":"98","game_stage":"7","question":"173-112+189","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":189}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":189}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:52:51"},
{"history_id":"2079","user_id":"113","game_stage":"6","question":"110-26+188","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":188}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":188}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:52:57"},
{"history_id":"2080","user_id":"113","game_stage":"6","question":"130-77-21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-21 11:53:43"},
{"history_id":"2296","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"(212+19)x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1386,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":499,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-23 09:10:21"},
{"history_id":"2297","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"16x12x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 09:10:55"},
{"history_id":"2298","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"1930÷(290-97)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1930,\"numB\":193}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1930,\"numB\":193}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 09:13:26"},
{"history_id":"2299","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"135x10÷45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1350,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1350,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1350,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1350,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 09:13:41"},
{"history_id":"2300","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"98x5÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":490,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":490,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-23 09:13:55"},
{"history_id":"2301","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"412-21x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":412,\"numB\":315}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":412,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-23 09:14:08"},
{"history_id":"2302","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"143-129-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 09:14:28"},
{"history_id":"2303","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"219-126+164","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":126}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":257,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":164}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":126}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":164}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-23 09:14:42"},
{"history_id":"2304","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"(104+172)x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":172}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2484,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":276,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":172}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2484,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":276,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:00:38"},
{"history_id":"2305","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"148x9+280","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1332,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1612,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1332,\"numB\":280}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":280}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":437,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":289}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis07","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:01:11"},
{"history_id":"2306","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"1x(215-145)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":145}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":215}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":145}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:01:39"},
{"history_id":"2307","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"121x3-117","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":363,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":363,\"numB\":117}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":117}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":120}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:02:14"},
{"history_id":"2308","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"(139+94)x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1864,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":291,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":102}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:02:58"},
{"history_id":"2309","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u723a\u723a\u5728\u6d77\u908a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u7f8e\u9e97\u7684\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u4ed6\u62ff22\u500b\u888b\u5b50\u53bb\u8490\u96c6\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u5df2\u77e5\u6bcf\u500b\u888b\u5b50\u5167\u88dd\u67094\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u8c6c\u723a\u723a\u60f3\u5c07\u77f3\u982d\u653e\u5728\u5c55\u793a\u6ac3\u4f9b\u4eba\u89c0\u8cde\uff0c\u4ed6\u5c07\u8490\u96c6\u56de\u4f86\u7684\u77f3\u982d\u5e73\u5206\u653e\u4e0a11\u5c64\u5c55\u793a\u6ac3\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u5c64\u5c55\u793a\u6ac3\u4e0a\u6709\u5e7e\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"22x4÷11","userAns_obj":"22x4÷11","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:24:52"},
{"history_id":"2310","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\u5230\u8c6c\u8c6c\u8d85\u5e02\u8cb7\u4e8654\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\uff0c\u56de\u5bb6\u5f8c\u5c072\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u4e00\u5305\uff0c\u9001\u7d66\u8c6c\u963f\u5b2410\u5305\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"54÷2-10","userAns_obj":"54÷2÷10","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:25:36"},
{"history_id":"2311","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u6dd8\u6c70\u8c6c\u8cb7\u4e8681\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u56de\u4f86\uff0c\u6bcf27\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u6210\u4e00\u5305\uff0c\u8c6c\u72d7\u72d7\u770b\u5230\u9905\u4e7e\u60f3\u5403\uff0c\u65bc\u662f\u5077\u5077\u62ff\u8d70\u4e862\u5305\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6dd8\u6c70\u8c6c\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"81÷27-2","userAns_obj":"81÷27-2","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:25:47"},
{"history_id":"2312","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u5c0f\u5f1f\u8eab\u4e0a\u5171\u670928\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff0c\u5df2\u7d93\u5403\u6389\u4e8615\u500b\uff0c\u60f3\u5c07\u5269\u4e0b\u7684\u9eb5\u5305\u5e73\u5747\u5206\u7d6613\u500b\u5925\u4f34\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u500b\u5925\u4f34\u6703\u62ff\u5230\u5e7e\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"(28-15)÷13","userAns_obj":"(28-15)÷13","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:26:01"},
{"history_id":"2313","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"26x(188-149)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1014,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1014,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":188}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:28:47"},
{"history_id":"2314","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"142x29-3245","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":873,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4118,\"numB\":3245}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":3245}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:29:21"},
{"history_id":"2315","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"35x(299-105)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":105}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6790,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":194}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":105}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6790,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":299}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:29:52"},
{"history_id":"2316","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"299+135÷27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":135}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:30:32"},
{"history_id":"2317","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"149-196÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":196}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:32:23"},
{"history_id":"2318","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"94x(155+296)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":451,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":296}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42394,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":451}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":451,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":296}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42934,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":155}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:33:01"},
{"history_id":"2319","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"7120-130x54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7020,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7120,\"numB\":7020}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7020,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7120,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:33:26"},
{"history_id":"2320","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"136x38+216","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":5384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5168,\"numB\":216}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":5384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":216}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:34:07"},
{"history_id":"2321","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"238+134x22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2948,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":2948}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2948,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":134}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:36:30"},
{"history_id":"2322","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"(142+182)x87","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":28188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":324,\"numB\":87}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15976,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":87}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:37:10"},
{"history_id":"2323","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"(162+101)x61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":263,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16043,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":263,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16043,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:37:41"},
{"history_id":"2324","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"(124-108)x80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:38:12"},
{"history_id":"2325","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"(211-104)÷107","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":104}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":107}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":104}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":107}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:40:28"},
{"history_id":"2326","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"(221+241)÷42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":241}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":462,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":241}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:40:55"},
{"history_id":"2327","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"(140-111)x60","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1740,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1740,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:41:27"},
{"history_id":"2328","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"95x(183-132)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":132}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4845,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":51}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":132}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4845,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":183}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-23 10:42:02"},
{"history_id":"2329","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"53+194÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:49:41"},
{"history_id":"2330","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"36x12-355","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":432,\"numB\":355}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":433,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":433,\"numB\":355}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:50:07"},
{"history_id":"2331","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"123+182-183","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":305,\"numB\":183}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":305,\"numB\":183}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:50:29"},
{"history_id":"2332","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"1454-90x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1454,\"numB\":1440}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1454,\"numB\":1440}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:53:47"},
{"history_id":"2333","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"242÷2x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":242,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":484,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":242,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":484,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:54:05"},
{"history_id":"2334","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"18÷2x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:54:19"},
{"history_id":"2335","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"193+273÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:54:44"},
{"history_id":"2336","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"88+7x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:55:05"},
{"history_id":"2337","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"288÷12-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:55:25"},
{"history_id":"2338","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"52x16x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":832,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5824,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":832,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis08","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:55:43"},
{"history_id":"2339","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"270+154÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":277,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":277,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 12:59:48"},
{"history_id":"2340","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"241-86-123","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":123}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":241,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 01:00:07"},
{"history_id":"2341","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"276+134x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1072,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":276,\"numB\":1072}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":276,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 01:00:31"},
{"history_id":"2342","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"109x10-970","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1090,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1090,\"numB\":970}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1090,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1090,\"numB\":970}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 01:00:56"},
{"history_id":"2355","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"48x14-348","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":672,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":672,\"numB\":348}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":672,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":672,\"numB\":348}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 02:47:55"},
{"history_id":"2356","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"250÷10÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 02:48:16"},
{"history_id":"2357","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"44x6÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 02:48:28"},
{"history_id":"2358","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"45÷5-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 02:48:40"},
{"history_id":"2359","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"243+82x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":325,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 02:48:57"},
{"history_id":"2360","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"79+285+176","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":364,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":285}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":364,\"numB\":176}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":285}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":176}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 02:51:37"},
{"history_id":"2361","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"105÷5-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 02:51:48"},
{"history_id":"2362","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"172+236÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":290,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":236}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 02:52:00"},
{"history_id":"2363","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"157+28+152","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":185,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":157,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":337,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":152}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":157,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":152}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:02:51"},
{"history_id":"2364","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"140-66+67","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:39:18"},
{"history_id":"2365","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"130x7+161","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":910,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1071,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":910,\"numB\":161}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":910,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1071,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":910,\"numB\":161}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:39:35"},
{"history_id":"2366","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"87-54÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:39:58"},
{"history_id":"2367","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"576-35x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":525,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":576,\"numB\":525}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":525,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":576,\"numB\":525}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:40:41"},
{"history_id":"2368","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"58x12÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":696,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:41:01"},
{"history_id":"2369","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"39÷3x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:41:12"},
{"history_id":"2370","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"(251-142)x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":109,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":142}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":545,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":109,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":142}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":545,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:41:47"},
{"history_id":"2371","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"9x(60+198)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":198}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2322,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":258}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":198}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:46:00"},
{"history_id":"2372","user_id":"1","game_stage":"999","question":"256÷64÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 03:46:17"},
{"history_id":"2376","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8def\u4e0a\u6709\u4e00\u5806\u77f3\u982d\u64cb\u4f4f\u53bb\u8def\uff0c\u9700\u8981\u5c07\u77f3\u982d\u79fb\u958b\u624d\u80fd\u884c\u8d70\uff0c\u5df2\u77e5\u7e3d\u5171\u67098\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u67098\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u4e00\u6b21\u6700\u591a\u53ea\u80fd\u642c\u904b4\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u7e3d\u5171\u8981\u642c\u904b\u5e7e\u6b21\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"8x8÷4","userAns_obj":"8x8÷4","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 06:55:10"},
{"history_id":"2377","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\u5230\u8c6c\u8c6c\u8d85\u5e02\u8cb7\u4e8657\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\uff0c\u56de\u5bb6\u5f8c\u5c073\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u4e00\u5305\uff0c\u9001\u7d66\u8c6c\u963f\u5b2414\u5305\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"57÷3-14","userAns_obj":"57÷3-14","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 06:55:24"},
{"history_id":"2378","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u963f\u5b24\u71b1\u5fc3\u52a9\u4eba\uff0c\u6bcf\u6b21\u90fd\u6703\u5c07\u505a\u597d\u7684\u9eb5\u5305\u5206\u9001\u7d66\u6751\u4e2d\u7684\u5b69\u5b50\u5011\uff0c\u5df2\u77e5\u8c6c\u963f\u5b24\u88fd\u4f5c\u4e8653\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff0c\u4fdd\u7559\u4e8647\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\u7d66\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\uff0c\u5269\u4e0b\u7684\u5e73\u5206\u7d66\u6751\u4e2d3\u500b\u5b69\u5b50\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u500b\u5b69\u5b50\u6703\u62ff\u5230\u5e7e\u500b\u8c6c\u963f\u5b24\u7684\u611b\u5fc3\u9eb5\u5305\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"(53-47)÷3","userAns_obj":"(53-47)÷3","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 06:55:41"},
{"history_id":"2379","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"235-104-107","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":104}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":107}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":104}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":107}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 06:56:33"},
{"history_id":"2380","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"159-295÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":295}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 06:57:03"},
{"history_id":"2381","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"6888÷(185-101)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6888,\"numB\":84}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6888,\"numB\":185}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-24 06:57:40"},
{"history_id":"2382","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"90÷10-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 06:58:05"},
{"history_id":"2383","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\ufeff\u5730\u4e0a\u7684\u77f3\u982d\u5171\u67095\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u67092\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u73fe\u5728\u60f3\u5168\u90e8\u6df7\u5728\u4e00\u8d77\u4e26\u4e14\u5e73\u5206\u62105\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u5e73\u5206\u904e\u5f8c\u6bcf\u5806\u88e1\u9762\u6709\u5e7e\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"5x2÷5","userAns_obj":"5x2÷5","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:31:35"},
{"history_id":"2384","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u6dd8\u6c70\u8c6c\u8cb7\u4e8612\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u56de\u4f86\uff0c\u6bcf3\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u6210\u4e00\u5305\uff0c\u8c6c\u72d7\u72d7\u770b\u5230\u9905\u4e7e\u60f3\u5403\uff0c\u65bc\u662f\u5077\u5077\u62ff\u8d70\u4e862\u5305\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6dd8\u6c70\u8c6c\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"12÷3-2","userAns_obj":"12÷3-2","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:31:50"},
{"history_id":"2385","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u5c0f\u5f1f\u8eab\u4e0a\u5171\u670994\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff0c\u5df2\u7d93\u5403\u6389\u4e863\u500b\uff0c\u60f3\u5c07\u5269\u4e0b\u7684\u9eb5\u5305\u5e73\u5747\u5206\u7d6613\u500b\u5925\u4f34\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u500b\u5925\u4f34\u6703\u62ff\u5230\u5e7e\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"(94-3)÷13","userAns_obj":"(94-3)÷13","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:32:07"},
{"history_id":"2386","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"(167-124)÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":124}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":124}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:32:52"},
{"history_id":"2387","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"133÷19+223","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":223}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":223}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:33:23"},
{"history_id":"2388","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"140x68-2006","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7514,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9520,\"numB\":2006}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7514,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":2006}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:33:59"},
{"history_id":"2389","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8def\u4e0a\u6709\u4e00\u5806\u77f3\u982d\u64cb\u4f4f\u53bb\u8def\uff0c\u9700\u8981\u5c07\u77f3\u982d\u79fb\u958b\u624d\u80fd\u884c\u8d70\uff0c\u5df2\u77e5\u7e3d\u5171\u670941\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u67095\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u4e00\u6b21\u6700\u591a\u53ea\u80fd\u642c\u904b5\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u7e3d\u5171\u8981\u642c\u904b\u5e7e\u6b21\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"41x5÷5","userAns_obj":"41x5÷5","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:37:36"},
{"history_id":"2390","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u5730\u74dc\u8c6c\u5bb6\u88e1\u670995\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\uff0c\u8c6c\u5abd\u5abd\u5c075\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u6210\u4e00\u888b\uff0c\u5730\u74dc\u8c6c\u8caa\u5403\u5148\u62ff\u8d70\u4e866\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u5730\u74dc\u8c6c\u5bb6\u4e2d\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u888b\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"95÷5-6","userAns_obj":"95÷5-6","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:37:50"},
{"history_id":"2391","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u5c0f\u5f1f\u8eab\u4e0a\u5171\u67098\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff0c\u5df2\u7d93\u5403\u6389\u4e864\u500b\uff0c\u60f3\u5c07\u5269\u4e0b\u7684\u9eb5\u5305\u5e73\u5747\u5206\u7d662\u500b\u5925\u4f34\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u500b\u5925\u4f34\u6703\u62ff\u5230\u5e7e\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"(8-4)÷2","userAns_obj":"(8-4)÷2","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:38:10"},
{"history_id":"2392","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"200-200÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":100}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":200}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:39:14"},
{"history_id":"2393","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"18096÷(122+190)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":190}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18096,\"numB\":312}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":190}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18096,\"numB\":122}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:40:03"},
{"history_id":"2394","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"12714÷(275-112)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":275,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12714,\"numB\":163}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":275,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12714,\"numB\":275}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:40:40"},
{"history_id":"2395","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8def\u4e0a\u6709\u4e00\u5806\u77f3\u982d\u64cb\u4f4f\u53bb\u8def\uff0c\u9700\u8981\u5c07\u77f3\u982d\u79fb\u958b\u624d\u80fd\u884c\u8d70\uff0c\u5df2\u77e5\u7e3d\u5171\u670932\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u67098\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u4e00\u6b21\u6700\u591a\u53ea\u80fd\u642c\u904b8\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u7e3d\u5171\u8981\u642c\u904b\u5e7e\u6b21\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"32x8÷8","userAns_obj":"32x8÷8","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:43:27"},
{"history_id":"2396","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\u5230\u8c6c\u8c6c\u8d85\u5e02\u8cb7\u4e8650\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\uff0c\u56de\u5bb6\u5f8c\u5c075\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u4e00\u5305\uff0c\u9001\u7d66\u8c6c\u963f\u5b248\u5305\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"50÷5-8","userAns_obj":"50÷5-8","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:43:43"},
{"history_id":"2397","user_id":"1","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u5c0f\u5f1f\u8eab\u4e0a\u5171\u670979\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff0c\u5df2\u7d93\u5403\u6389\u4e862\u500b\uff0c\u60f3\u5c07\u5269\u4e0b\u7684\u9eb5\u5305\u5e73\u5747\u5206\u7d6611\u500b\u5925\u4f34\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u500b\u5925\u4f34\u6703\u62ff\u5230\u5e7e\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"(79-2)÷11","userAns_obj":"(79-2)÷11","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:43:56"},
{"history_id":"2398","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"(262+261)x69","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":523,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":262,\"numB\":261}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36087,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":523,\"numB\":69}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":523,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":262,\"numB\":261}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36087,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":261,\"numB\":69}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:44:52"},
{"history_id":"2399","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"104+198÷18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":198}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:45:15"},
{"history_id":"2400","user_id":"1","game_stage":"15","question":"11049÷(131+250)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":381,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":250}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11049,\"numB\":381}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":381,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":250}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11049,\"numB\":131}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-24 07:46:05"},
{"history_id":"2401","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"50-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:10:14"},
{"history_id":"2402","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"47-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:11:44"},
{"history_id":"2403","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"63-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:13:17"},
{"history_id":"2404","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"68÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:14:10"},
{"history_id":"2405","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"34÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:14:25"},
{"history_id":"2406","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"75÷15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:14:34"},
{"history_id":"2407","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"10x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:15:04"},
{"history_id":"2408","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"30x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:15:11"},
{"history_id":"2409","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"1x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis08","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:15:19"},
{"history_id":"2410","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"48÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:15:41"},
{"history_id":"2411","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"55÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:15:58"},
{"history_id":"2412","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"36÷18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:16:19"},
{"history_id":"2413","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"94÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:16:34"},
{"history_id":"2414","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"4x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis07","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:16:49"},
{"history_id":"2418","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"44x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:20:39"},
{"history_id":"2419","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"54÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:21:17"},
{"history_id":"2421","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"29x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:21:44"},
{"history_id":"2422","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"90-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:30:32"},
{"history_id":"2423","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"62+42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:30:45"},
{"history_id":"2424","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"54-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:30:56"},
{"history_id":"2425","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"92+53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:32:02"},
{"history_id":"2426","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"11+71","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":71}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:33:32"},
{"history_id":"2430","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"50-45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:40:28"},
{"history_id":"2431","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"64+99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:40:43"},
{"history_id":"2432","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"9+2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:40:54"},
{"history_id":"2433","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"71+33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:42:53"},
{"history_id":"2434","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"1x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:44:10"},
{"history_id":"2435","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"29x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:44:18"},
{"history_id":"2436","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"25x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:44:28"},
{"history_id":"2437","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"57÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:45:32"},
{"history_id":"2438","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"46x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:45:45"},
{"history_id":"2439","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"29x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis07","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:46:07"},
{"history_id":"2440","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"48x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:46:24"},
{"history_id":"2441","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"5x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis07","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:46:46"},
{"history_id":"2442","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"31+54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:47:58"},
{"history_id":"2443","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"56+60","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 08:48:15"},
{"history_id":"2444","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"36-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:12:28"},
{"history_id":"2453","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"57-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:34:15"},
{"history_id":"2454","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"13+31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:37:37"},
{"history_id":"2455","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"33+13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:38:47"},
{"history_id":"2456","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"97-33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:40:31"},
{"history_id":"2457","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"87+83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:52:23"},
{"history_id":"2458","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"48-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:53:45"},
{"history_id":"2459","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"60+85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:53:58"},
{"history_id":"2460","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"53-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:54:07"},
{"history_id":"2461","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"60-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:56:42"},
{"history_id":"2462","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"34-29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:56:52"},
{"history_id":"2463","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"44+4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 09:57:08"},
{"history_id":"2464","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"23+88","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 10:00:26"},
{"history_id":"2465","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"84+12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 10:04:25"},
{"history_id":"2466","user_id":"1","game_stage":"2","question":"28+18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-24 10:08:32"},
{"history_id":"2467","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"21x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 10:09:16"},
{"history_id":"2468","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"65÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 10:09:24"},
{"history_id":"2469","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"29x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-24 10:09:31"},
{"history_id":"2470","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"3x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:33:16"},
{"history_id":"2471","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"86÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:33:25"},
{"history_id":"2472","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"14x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:33:36"},
{"history_id":"2473","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:34:45"},
{"history_id":"2474","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"44÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:34:53"},
{"history_id":"2475","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"82÷41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:35:01"},
{"history_id":"2476","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"17x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis08","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:36:24"},
{"history_id":"2477","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"1x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:36:32"},
{"history_id":"2478","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:36:47"},
{"history_id":"2479","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"5x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:36:58"},
{"history_id":"2480","user_id":"1","game_stage":"3","question":"69÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:37:16"},
{"history_id":"2481","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"37-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:53:34"},
{"history_id":"2482","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"72-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:53:44"},
{"history_id":"2483","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"1+69","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":69}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":69}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:53:53"},
{"history_id":"2484","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"4-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:55:17"},
{"history_id":"2485","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"83-22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:55:31"},
{"history_id":"2486","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"21+62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:56:33"},
{"history_id":"2487","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"83+59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:56:47"},
{"history_id":"2488","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"94-38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:58:33"},
{"history_id":"2489","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"30-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 03:59:34"},
{"history_id":"2490","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"86+70","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":70}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:01:09"},
{"history_id":"2491","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"7x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:01:59"},
{"history_id":"2492","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"26x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis08","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:02:07"},
{"history_id":"2493","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"93÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:02:15"},
{"history_id":"2494","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"62÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:03:28"},
{"history_id":"2495","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"12÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:03:36"},
{"history_id":"2496","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"45x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:03:47"},
{"history_id":"2497","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"15x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:04:39"},
{"history_id":"2498","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"48x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:04:47"},
{"history_id":"2499","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"72÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:04:55"},
{"history_id":"2500","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"47x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:06:57"},
{"history_id":"2501","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"50÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:07:04"},
{"history_id":"2502","user_id":"2","game_stage":"3","question":"45x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:07:12"},
{"history_id":"2503","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"93+17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:08:14"},
{"history_id":"2504","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"75-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:08:26"},
{"history_id":"2505","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"95-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:08:37"},
{"history_id":"2506","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"46+63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":109,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:15:23"},
{"history_id":"2507","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"81+33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:15:35"},
{"history_id":"2508","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"79+98","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":98}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":98}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:15:47"},
{"history_id":"2509","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"70+63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:17:48"},
{"history_id":"2510","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"19+70","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":70}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:18:56"},
{"history_id":"2511","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"96-42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:19:07"},
{"history_id":"2512","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"89-44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:19:16"},
{"history_id":"2513","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"33+45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:21:10"},
{"history_id":"2514","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"15-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:21:22"},
{"history_id":"2515","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"79-14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:22:31"},
{"history_id":"2516","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"45-40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:22:44"},
{"history_id":"2517","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"70-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 04:24:21"},
{"history_id":"2518","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"8+50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:44:04"},
{"history_id":"2519","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"9+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:45:07"},
{"history_id":"2520","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"1+22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:45:15"},
{"history_id":"2521","user_id":"2","game_stage":"2","question":"26+27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:45:24"},
{"history_id":"2522","user_id":"2","game_stage":"14","question":"\ufeff\u5730\u4e0a\u7684\u77f3\u982d\u5171\u670911\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u67098\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff0c\u73fe\u5728\u60f3\u5168\u90e8\u6df7\u5728\u4e00\u8d77\u4e26\u4e14\u5e73\u5206\u62104\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u5e73\u5206\u904e\u5f8c\u6bcf\u5806\u88e1\u9762\u6709\u5e7e\u9846\u77f3\u982d\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"11x8÷4","userAns_obj":"11x8÷4","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:48:35"},
{"history_id":"2523","user_id":"2","game_stage":"14","question":"\u6dd8\u6c70\u8c6c\u8cb7\u4e8682\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u56de\u4f86\uff0c\u6bcf2\u500b\u9905\u4e7e\u88dd\u6210\u4e00\u5305\uff0c\u8c6c\u72d7\u72d7\u770b\u5230\u9905\u4e7e\u60f3\u5403\uff0c\u65bc\u662f\u5077\u5077\u62ff\u8d70\u4e8616\u5305\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6dd8\u6c70\u8c6c\u9084\u5269\u4e0b\u591a\u5c11\u5305\u9905\u4e7e\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"82÷2-16","userAns_obj":"82÷2-16","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:48:48"},
{"history_id":"2524","user_id":"2","game_stage":"14","question":"\u8c6c\u963f\u5b24\u71b1\u5fc3\u52a9\u4eba\uff0c\u6bcf\u6b21\u90fd\u6703\u5c07\u505a\u597d\u7684\u9eb5\u5305\u5206\u9001\u7d66\u6751\u4e2d\u7684\u5b69\u5b50\u5011\uff0c\u5df2\u77e5\u8c6c\u963f\u5b24\u88fd\u4f5c\u4e8659\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\uff0c\u4fdd\u7559\u4e8618\u500b\u9eb5\u5305\u7d66\u8c6c\u7d05\u5e3d\uff0c\u5269\u4e0b\u7684\u5e73\u5206\u7d66\u6751\u4e2d41\u500b\u5b69\u5b50\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u6bcf\u500b\u5b69\u5b50\u6703\u62ff\u5230\u5e7e\u500b\u8c6c\u963f\u5b24\u7684\u611b\u5fc3\u9eb5\u5305\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"(59-18)÷41","userAns_obj":"(59-18)÷41","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:49:05"},
{"history_id":"2525","user_id":"2","game_stage":"15","question":"247÷19+259","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":259}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":272,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":259}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:49:50"},
{"history_id":"2526","user_id":"2","game_stage":"15","question":"32x(137+226)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":363,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":226}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11616,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":363}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":363,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":226}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11616,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":137}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:51:26"},
{"history_id":"2527","user_id":"2","game_stage":"15","question":"(167+125)÷146","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":292,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":292,\"numB\":146}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":292,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":146}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 08:52:17"},
{"history_id":"2528","user_id":"2","game_stage":"999","question":"(170+248)x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":418,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":248}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5852,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":418,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":418,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":248}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5852,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":418,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:01:29"},
{"history_id":"2529","user_id":"2","game_stage":"999","question":"8x(126+184)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":310}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":310}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:01:54"},
{"history_id":"2530","user_id":"2","game_stage":"999","question":"604-97x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":582,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":604,\"numB\":582}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":604,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:02:11"},
{"history_id":"2531","user_id":"2","game_stage":"999","question":"217-27x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":162}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05mis08","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:02:24"},
{"history_id":"2532","user_id":"2","game_stage":"999","question":"33x10-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":321,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":330,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:02:36"},
{"history_id":"2533","user_id":"33","game_stage":"9","question":"239+75÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":254,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":254,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:37:54"},
{"history_id":"2534","user_id":"38","game_stage":"10","question":"80÷(48÷6)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:37:54"},
{"history_id":"2535","user_id":"56","game_stage":"8","question":"5x11+172","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":227,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:37:56"},
{"history_id":"2536","user_id":"40","game_stage":"10","question":"2x(187+160)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":347,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":160}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":694,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":347}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":187}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":534,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":374,\"numB\":160}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:06"},
{"history_id":"2537","user_id":"48","game_stage":"7","question":"278-77+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:10"},
{"history_id":"2538","user_id":"58","game_stage":"8","question":"176÷8+194","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":194}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":194}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:12"},
{"history_id":"2539","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"82+102+287","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":102}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":471,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":287}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":102}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":471,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":287}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:17"},
{"history_id":"2540","user_id":"31","game_stage":"7","question":"29+100-106","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":100}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":106}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":100}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":106}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:18"},
{"history_id":"2541","user_id":"37","game_stage":"11","question":"350÷(108-73)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":350,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":350,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:22"},
{"history_id":"2542","user_id":"56","game_stage":"8","question":"112÷14+40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:23"},
{"history_id":"2544","user_id":"55","game_stage":"6","question":"125+111+56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":292,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":56}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":292,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":167}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:29"},
{"history_id":"2545","user_id":"58","game_stage":"8","question":"9x1-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:31"},
{"history_id":"2546","user_id":"51","game_stage":"9","question":"64÷4+237","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":237}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":237}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:36"},
{"history_id":"2547","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"191-51+66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:42"},
{"history_id":"2548","user_id":"36","game_stage":"7","question":"172-55+53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:43"},
{"history_id":"2549","user_id":"38","game_stage":"10","question":"81-(148-69)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:43"},
{"history_id":"2550","user_id":"40","game_stage":"10","question":"48÷(42÷7)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:48"},
{"history_id":"2551","user_id":"48","game_stage":"7","question":"2x10÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:48"},
{"history_id":"2552","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"95x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:48"},
{"history_id":"2553","user_id":"58","game_stage":"8","question":"39÷13+88","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:54"},
{"history_id":"2554","user_id":"54","game_stage":"4","question":"90-21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:56"},
{"history_id":"2555","user_id":"42","game_stage":"4","question":"120-83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:57"},
{"history_id":"2556","user_id":"33","game_stage":"9","question":"523-56x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":448,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":523,\"numB\":448}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":448,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":523,\"numB\":448}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:58"},
{"history_id":"2557","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"146÷73x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:59"},
{"history_id":"2558","user_id":"32","game_stage":"8","question":"2+148÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":148}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:38:59"},
{"history_id":"2559","user_id":"31","game_stage":"7","question":"72+227+42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":227}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":341,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":227}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":341,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:02"},
{"history_id":"2560","user_id":"45","game_stage":"8","question":"197+78x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":936}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":275,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:11"},
{"history_id":"2561","user_id":"37","game_stage":"11","question":"(76+106)x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":364,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":364,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:14"},
{"history_id":"2562","user_id":"38","game_stage":"10","question":"(109-35)÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:16"},
{"history_id":"2563","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"184-96+117","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":117}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":117}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:18"},
{"history_id":"2564","user_id":"56","game_stage":"8","question":"71+155÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":155}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:19"},
{"history_id":"2565","user_id":"50","game_stage":"3","question":"9x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:21"},
{"history_id":"2566","user_id":"55","game_stage":"6","question":"40x3÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:22"},
{"history_id":"2567","user_id":"36","game_stage":"7","question":"104÷52÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:24"},
{"history_id":"2568","user_id":"57","game_stage":"7","question":"216-141+282","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":357,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":282}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":423,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":282}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":423}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:26"},
{"history_id":"2569","user_id":"40","game_stage":"10","question":"(123+126)x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":126}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":747,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":126}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":747,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:27"},
{"history_id":"2570","user_id":"54","game_stage":"4","question":"90x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":900,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":900,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:28"},
{"history_id":"2571","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"69x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":621,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":621,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:28"},
{"history_id":"2572","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"95x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:28"},
{"history_id":"2573","user_id":"33","game_stage":"9","question":"172+282÷141","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:29"},
{"history_id":"2574","user_id":"32","game_stage":"8","question":"35+111÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:30"},
{"history_id":"2575","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"173-37-78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:35"},
{"history_id":"2576","user_id":"42","game_stage":"4","question":"186÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:42"},
{"history_id":"2577","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"8÷2÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:45"},
{"history_id":"2578","user_id":"51","game_stage":"9","question":"223+123x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":861,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1084,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":223,\"numB\":861}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":861,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1084,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":223,\"numB\":861}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:45"},
{"history_id":"2579","user_id":"45","game_stage":"8","question":"2x6+183","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":183}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":183}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:47"},
{"history_id":"2580","user_id":"37","game_stage":"11","question":"(285-65)÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":220,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":220,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:48"},
{"history_id":"2581","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"141-62+114","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":223,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:49"},
{"history_id":"2582","user_id":"38","game_stage":"10","question":"(186-43)x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1716,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1716,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:50"},
{"history_id":"2583","user_id":"31","game_stage":"7","question":"186÷62÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:39:57"},
{"history_id":"2584","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"6+53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:01"},
{"history_id":"2585","user_id":"40","game_stage":"10","question":"(103+12)÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:02"},
{"history_id":"2586","user_id":"36","game_stage":"7","question":"122÷2÷61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:04"},
{"history_id":"2587","user_id":"32","game_stage":"8","question":"26x12-254","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":254}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":254}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:07"},
{"history_id":"2588","user_id":"54","game_stage":"4","question":"122÷61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:08"},
{"history_id":"2589","user_id":"57","game_stage":"7","question":"70+81-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:14"},
{"history_id":"2590","user_id":"46","game_stage":"4","question":"68-57","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:17"},
{"history_id":"2591","user_id":"44","game_stage":"4","question":"69x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":621,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":621,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:17"},
{"history_id":"2592","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"184÷92÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:17"},
{"history_id":"2593","user_id":"50","game_stage":"3","question":"13x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:19"},
{"history_id":"2594","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"187÷17x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":170}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:21"},
{"history_id":"2595","user_id":"55","game_stage":"6","question":"130÷2x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:21"},
{"history_id":"2596","user_id":"51","game_stage":"9","question":"100-91÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:25"},
{"history_id":"2597","user_id":"48","game_stage":"7","question":"66x12÷18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":792,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":792,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":792,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":792,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:30"},
{"history_id":"2598","user_id":"32","game_stage":"8","question":"110÷55+108","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":108}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":108}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:32"},
{"history_id":"2599","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"172-93+16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":93}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":109,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":109}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:45"},
{"history_id":"2600","user_id":"58","game_stage":"9","question":"74x5+244","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":614,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":244}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":614,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":244}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:46"},
{"history_id":"2601","user_id":"31","game_stage":"7","question":"126÷2÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:51"},
{"history_id":"2602","user_id":"53","game_stage":"8","question":"146+177÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":323,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":177}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1368,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":323,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:40:59"},
{"history_id":"2603","user_id":"33","game_stage":"10","question":"1405÷(160+121)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1405,\"numB\":281}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1405,\"numB\":281}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:03"},
{"history_id":"2604","user_id":"42","game_stage":"6","question":"21-14-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:04"},
{"history_id":"2605","user_id":"45","game_stage":"8","question":"376-85x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":340,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":376,\"numB\":340}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":291,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":376,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":291,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:07"},
{"history_id":"2606","user_id":"57","game_stage":"7","question":"219÷73÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:15"},
{"history_id":"2607","user_id":"37","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c69\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527235\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272109\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"9x(35+109)","userAns_obj":"(35x9)+109","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:22"},
{"history_id":"2608","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"133÷19÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:22"},
{"history_id":"2609","user_id":"51","game_stage":"9","question":"231+228÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:23"},
{"history_id":"2610","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"132÷4x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:23"},
{"history_id":"2611","user_id":"33","game_stage":"10","question":"1x(185-31)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":154}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":154}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:33"},
{"history_id":"2612","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"36+118+102","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":118}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":102}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":118}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":102}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:33"},
{"history_id":"2613","user_id":"48","game_stage":"7","question":"232+79-172","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":311,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":311,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":311,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":311,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:33"},
{"history_id":"2614","user_id":"53","game_stage":"8","question":"7x10+148","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":148}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":148}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:34"},
{"history_id":"2615","user_id":"40","game_stage":"11","question":"603÷(268÷4)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":603,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":603,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:34"},
{"history_id":"2616","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"57x14÷266","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":798,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":798,\"numB\":266}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":808,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":808,\"numB\":266}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:34"},
{"history_id":"2617","user_id":"38","game_stage":"11","question":"143÷(26÷2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:37"},
{"history_id":"2618","user_id":"56","game_stage":"8","question":"145+22x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:39"},
{"history_id":"2619","user_id":"46","game_stage":"6","question":"149-72+100","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":100}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:40"},
{"history_id":"2620","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"153÷3÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:49"},
{"history_id":"2621","user_id":"32","game_stage":"7","question":"161+120-176","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":176}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":176}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:49"},
{"history_id":"2623","user_id":"54","game_stage":"6","question":"169-5-77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:55"},
{"history_id":"2624","user_id":"45","game_stage":"8","question":"52-70÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:41:58"},
{"history_id":"2625","user_id":"42","game_stage":"6","question":"69-6+144","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":144}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":144}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:00"},
{"history_id":"2626","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"65x4x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3640,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:04"},
{"history_id":"2627","user_id":"37","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u62107\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u580676\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u5806162\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"7x(76+162)","userAns_obj":"(76x7)+162","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u52a0\u6cd5\u8207\u4e58\u6cd5\u6703\u4f7f\u7d50\u679c\u589e","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:04"},
{"history_id":"2628","user_id":"33","game_stage":"10","question":"77-(108-70)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:04"},
{"history_id":"2629","user_id":"31","game_stage":"8","question":"98x1+117","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":117}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":117}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:06"},
{"history_id":"2630","user_id":"55","game_stage":"7","question":"266-31-40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:08"},
{"history_id":"2631","user_id":"56","game_stage":"8","question":"282-44x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":264}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":264}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:13"},
{"history_id":"2632","user_id":"50","game_stage":"4","question":"75-62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:14"},
{"history_id":"2633","user_id":"57","game_stage":"7","question":"228+284-467","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":284}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":512,\"numB\":467}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":284}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":512,\"numB\":467}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:16"},
{"history_id":"2634","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"198+186+136","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":384,\"numB\":136}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":384,\"numB\":136}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:18"},
{"history_id":"2635","user_id":"32","game_stage":"7","question":"251-119+114","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":119}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":119}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:19"},
{"history_id":"2636","user_id":"39","game_stage":"7","question":"166-85+299","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":299}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":299}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:21"},
{"history_id":"2637","user_id":"56","game_stage":"8","question":"90x1+40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:33"},
{"history_id":"2638","user_id":"38","game_stage":"11","question":"(153-39)x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1482,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1482,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:33"},
{"history_id":"2639","user_id":"58","game_stage":"9","question":"128-202÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":202,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":101}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":202,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":101}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:34"},
{"history_id":"2640","user_id":"40","game_stage":"11","question":"(268+129)x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":397,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4367,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":397,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":397,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4367,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":397,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:37"},
{"history_id":"2641","user_id":"53","game_stage":"8","question":"355-61x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":355,\"numB\":305}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":355,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1470,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:38"},
{"history_id":"2642","user_id":"35","game_stage":"7","question":"100-20+145","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":145}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":145}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:40"},
{"history_id":"2644","user_id":"37","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86117\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86137\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e8610\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"10x(117+137)","userAns_obj":"(117+137)x10","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:48"},
{"history_id":"2645","user_id":"42","game_stage":"6","question":"38x3x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":798,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":798,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:52"},
{"history_id":"2646","user_id":"31","game_stage":"8","question":"56x6-312","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":336,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":336,\"numB\":312}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":336,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":336,\"numB\":312}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:56"},
{"history_id":"2647","user_id":"50","game_stage":"4","question":"196÷98","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":98}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":98}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:58"},
{"history_id":"2648","user_id":"54","game_stage":"6","question":"69÷23x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:42:59"},
{"history_id":"2649","user_id":"55","game_stage":"7","question":"44x8x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1408,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":352,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":352,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:05"},
{"history_id":"2650","user_id":"45","game_stage":"8","question":"57+94÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:05"},
{"history_id":"2651","user_id":"32","game_stage":"7","question":"141x7÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":987,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":987,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":987,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":987,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:06"},
{"history_id":"2652","user_id":"46","game_stage":"6","question":"87x12÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1044,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1044,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1044,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1044,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:08"},
{"history_id":"2653","user_id":"51","game_stage":"10","question":"228÷(99-80)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:08"},
{"history_id":"2654","user_id":"48","game_stage":"8","question":"29+67x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":536,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":565,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":536}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":768,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:09"},
{"history_id":"2655","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"114÷6÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:10"},
{"history_id":"2656","user_id":"38","game_stage":"11","question":"592÷(204+92)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":296,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":592,\"numB\":296}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":296,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":592,\"numB\":296}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:13"},
{"history_id":"2657","user_id":"50","game_stage":"4","question":"1x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:20"},
{"history_id":"2658","user_id":"40","game_stage":"11","question":"1x(70-52)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":48}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:22"},
{"history_id":"2659","user_id":"53","game_stage":"8","question":"458-48x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":458,\"numB\":432}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":410,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":458,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3690,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":410,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:22"},
{"history_id":"2660","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"153÷51÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:23"},
{"history_id":"2661","user_id":"58","game_stage":"9","question":"256-73x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":219}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":219}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:30"},
{"history_id":"2662","user_id":"46","game_stage":"6","question":"8x1x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:34"},
{"history_id":"2663","user_id":"33","game_stage":"11","question":"13x(297-125)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:38"},
{"history_id":"2664","user_id":"31","game_stage":"8","question":"222-21x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":222,\"numB\":168}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":222,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:38"},
{"history_id":"2665","user_id":"48","game_stage":"8","question":"125+170÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":170}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:46"},
{"history_id":"2666","user_id":"32","game_stage":"7","question":"223-111-95","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":223,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":95}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":223,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":95}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:47"},
{"history_id":"2667","user_id":"54","game_stage":"6","question":"78+73+65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:48"},
{"history_id":"2668","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"193+142÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":533,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":142}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":533,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:43:57"},
{"history_id":"2669","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"61+75-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:01"},
{"history_id":"2670","user_id":"51","game_stage":"10","question":"(111-62)÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:08"},
{"history_id":"2671","user_id":"39","game_stage":"8","question":"25x10+66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:08"},
{"history_id":"2672","user_id":"33","game_stage":"11","question":"(79-39)x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:16"},
{"history_id":"2673","user_id":"31","game_stage":"8","question":"21x10-63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:19"},
{"history_id":"2674","user_id":"32","game_stage":"7","question":"246-139-46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":246,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":46}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":246,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:23"},
{"history_id":"2675","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"148÷74÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:26"},
{"history_id":"2676","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"178÷89÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":89}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":89}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:26"},
{"history_id":"2677","user_id":"35","game_stage":"8","question":"24+69÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:27"},
{"history_id":"2679","user_id":"51","game_stage":"10","question":"18÷(34-31)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:35"},
{"history_id":"2680","user_id":"42","game_stage":"6","question":"182-59-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:43"},
{"history_id":"2681","user_id":"57","game_stage":"8","question":"78x1+57","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:45"},
{"history_id":"2682","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"188÷2+196","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":290,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":196}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":196}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:46"},
{"history_id":"2683","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"299+195÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":338,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":494,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":195}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":494,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:47"},
{"history_id":"2684","user_id":"39","game_stage":"8","question":"535-70x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":490,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":535,\"numB\":490}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":490,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":535,\"numB\":490}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:48"},
{"history_id":"2685","user_id":"46","game_stage":"7","question":"174-130-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":130}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":130}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:49"},
{"history_id":"2686","user_id":"33","game_stage":"11","question":"119÷(161-144)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:49"},
{"history_id":"2687","user_id":"48","game_stage":"8","question":"93+96x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":1152}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2388,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:50"},
{"history_id":"2688","user_id":"40","game_stage":"11","question":"426÷(115-44)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":426,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":366,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":426,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:44:54"},
{"history_id":"2690","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"56-27-26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:03"},
{"history_id":"2691","user_id":"55","game_stage":"7","question":"130x16÷32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2080,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2080,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:07"},
{"history_id":"2692","user_id":"54","game_stage":"7","question":"116-112-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:13"},
{"history_id":"2693","user_id":"39","game_stage":"8","question":"194÷97-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:18"},
{"history_id":"2694","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"63÷21+143","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":143}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:21"},
{"history_id":"2695","user_id":"40","game_stage":"11","question":"(243+50)x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":879,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":293,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":879,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":293,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:23"},
{"history_id":"2696","user_id":"51","game_stage":"10","question":"(196+82)÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":278,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":278,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:23"},
{"history_id":"2697","user_id":"35","game_stage":"8","question":"34+93x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":406,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":372}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":406,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":372}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:27"},
{"history_id":"2698","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"87+137+46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":224,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":46}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":224,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:29"},
{"history_id":"2699","user_id":"57","game_stage":"8","question":"20x12-108","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":108}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":108}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:31"},
{"history_id":"2700","user_id":"45","game_stage":"8","question":"94÷2+144","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":144}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":144}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:32"},
{"history_id":"2702","user_id":"42","game_stage":"6","question":"28x1÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:37"},
{"history_id":"2703","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"62x2+200","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":200}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":324,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":200}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:45"},
{"history_id":"2704","user_id":"53","game_stage":"8","question":"86x9+85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":774,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":859,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":774,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":779,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":874,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":779,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:51"},
{"history_id":"2705","user_id":"58","game_stage":"10","question":"528÷(177-89)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":89}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":528,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":89}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":528,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:52"},
{"history_id":"2706","user_id":"34","game_stage":"6","question":"94-18-43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:58"},
{"history_id":"2707","user_id":"55","game_stage":"7","question":"232-115+198","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":115}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":198}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":115}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":198}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:45:58"},
{"history_id":"2708","user_id":"45","game_stage":"8","question":"69÷23-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:05"},
{"history_id":"2709","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"59x6÷118","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":354,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":354,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:07"},
{"history_id":"2710","user_id":"46","game_stage":"7","question":"69x12÷92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":828,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":828,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":828,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":828,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:10"},
{"history_id":"2711","user_id":"32","game_stage":"9","question":"17+299÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":299}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":316,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:12"},
{"history_id":"2712","user_id":"31","game_stage":"9","question":"16+59x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":413,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":429,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":413}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":525,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:14"},
{"history_id":"2713","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"132÷22x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:18"},
{"history_id":"2714","user_id":"57","game_stage":"8","question":"119-19x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:20"},
{"history_id":"2715","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"96-170÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:22"},
{"history_id":"2716","user_id":"53","game_stage":"8","question":"144+194÷97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":146,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:27"},
{"history_id":"2717","user_id":"42","game_stage":"6","question":"88x9x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":792,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1584,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":792,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":792,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1584,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":792,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:31"},
{"history_id":"2718","user_id":"35","game_stage":"8","question":"309-92x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":309,\"numB\":276}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":309,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":651,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:39"},
{"history_id":"2719","user_id":"33","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86104\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86139\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e869\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"9x(104+139)","userAns_obj":"(139+104)x9","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:44"},
{"history_id":"2720","user_id":"45","game_stage":"8","question":"23x2-29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:48"},
{"history_id":"2721","user_id":"47","game_stage":"6","question":"121+4-62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":62}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:48"},
{"history_id":"2722","user_id":"40","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86120\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86113\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e8612\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"12x(120+113)","userAns_obj":"-120x12+113","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:49"},
{"history_id":"2723","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"56x13-181","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":728,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":547,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":728,\"numB\":181}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":728,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7547,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":728,\"numB\":181}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:52"},
{"history_id":"2724","user_id":"38","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u621013\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u580643\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u5806140\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"13x(43+140)","userAns_obj":"(13x43)+140","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:54"},
{"history_id":"2725","user_id":"58","game_stage":"10","question":"(23+164)x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":164}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":164}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:46:54"},
{"history_id":"2726","user_id":"46","game_stage":"7","question":"94x3x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:00"},
{"history_id":"2727","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"43+173-93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":173}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":173}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:01"},
{"history_id":"2728","user_id":"32","game_stage":"9","question":"192+136x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":816,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1008,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":816}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":816,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1008,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":816}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:04"},
{"history_id":"2729","user_id":"54","game_stage":"7","question":"128x9÷24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1152,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1152,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:06"},
{"history_id":"2730","user_id":"31","game_stage":"9","question":"254÷127+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":127}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":127}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:09"},
{"history_id":"2731","user_id":"53","game_stage":"8","question":"39-8x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:12"},
{"history_id":"2732","user_id":"57","game_stage":"8","question":"82x13+166","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1066,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1066,\"numB\":166}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1066,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1066,\"numB\":166}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:20"},
{"history_id":"2733","user_id":"51","game_stage":"11","question":"15x(175+140)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":140}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4725,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":315}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":140}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4725,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":315}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:23"},
{"history_id":"2734","user_id":"58","game_stage":"10","question":"48÷(72÷12)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:24"},
{"history_id":"2735","user_id":"40","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u621013\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u580659\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u5806151\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"13x(59+151)","userAns_obj":"151x13+59","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u52a0\u6cd5\u8207\u4e58\u6cd5\u6703\u4f7f\u7d50\u679c\u589e","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:26"},
{"history_id":"2736","user_id":"38","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86128\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8656\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e867\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"7x(128+56)","userAns_obj":"(128+56)x7","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:32"},
{"history_id":"2737","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"435-93x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":435,\"numB\":372}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":435,\"numB\":93}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1368,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":342,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:33"},
{"history_id":"2738","user_id":"35","game_stage":"8","question":"45-116÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:36"},
{"history_id":"2739","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"128÷2-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:37"},
{"history_id":"2741","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"60x9+75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":615,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":540,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":615,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":540,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:45"},
{"history_id":"2742","user_id":"39","game_stage":"8","question":"60÷4+137","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":137}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":137}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:46"},
{"history_id":"2743","user_id":"53","game_stage":"8","question":"28-51÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:49"},
{"history_id":"2744","user_id":"40","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c611\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527221\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272145\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"11x(21+145)","userAns_obj":"11+21x145","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u52a0\u6cd5\u8207\u4e58\u6cd5\u6703\u4f7f\u7d50\u679c\u589e","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:52"},
{"history_id":"2745","user_id":"31","game_stage":"9","question":"82-20÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:53"},
{"history_id":"2746","user_id":"32","game_stage":"9","question":"30x12-107","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":360,\"numB\":107}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":107}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2850,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":95}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:47:59"},
{"history_id":"2747","user_id":"48","game_stage":"8","question":"21+63x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":126}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":123}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:13"},
{"history_id":"2748","user_id":"54","game_stage":"7","question":"133-116+189","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":189}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":359,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":189}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:15"},
{"history_id":"2749","user_id":"39","game_stage":"8","question":"54-38÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:16"},
{"history_id":"2750","user_id":"34","game_stage":"7","question":"269-35-24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":269,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":269,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":304,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:18"},
{"history_id":"2751","user_id":"42","game_stage":"7","question":"177-120-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:21"},
{"history_id":"2752","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"360-64x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":360,\"numB\":320}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":360,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:34"},
{"history_id":"2753","user_id":"51","game_stage":"11","question":"(67+58)÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:35"},
{"history_id":"2754","user_id":"47","game_stage":"7","question":"125+274-274","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":399,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":274}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":399,\"numB\":274}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":399,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":274}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":399,\"numB\":274}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:36"},
{"history_id":"2755","user_id":"32","game_stage":"9","question":"18-218÷109","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:36"},
{"history_id":"2757","user_id":"39","game_stage":"8","question":"367-79x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":367,\"numB\":316}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":367,\"numB\":316}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:50"},
{"history_id":"2758","user_id":"45","game_stage":"9","question":"114x5+12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":570,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":582,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":570,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":570,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":582,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":570,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:51"},
{"history_id":"2759","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"185÷5-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:48:59"},
{"history_id":"2760","user_id":"31","game_stage":"9","question":"120+144÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:00"},
{"history_id":"2761","user_id":"54","game_stage":"7","question":"18+55+156","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":156}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:03"},
{"history_id":"2762","user_id":"34","game_stage":"7","question":"185+167+40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":167}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":352,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":167}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":352,\"numB\":40}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:04"},
{"history_id":"2763","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"196-93-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":93}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":93}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:05"},
{"history_id":"2764","user_id":"32","game_stage":"9","question":"52x5-176","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":176}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":176}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:09"},
{"history_id":"2765","user_id":"58","game_stage":"11","question":"16x(204+127)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":331,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":127}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":331}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":331,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":127}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":331}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:18"},
{"history_id":"2766","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"123-12x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":108}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":999,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:21"},
{"history_id":"2767","user_id":"40","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86184\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86120\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e864\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"4x(184+120)","userAns_obj":"","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:23"},
{"history_id":"2768","user_id":"42","game_stage":"7","question":"146+139-169","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":169}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":285,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":169}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:24"},
{"history_id":"2769","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"174+9÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:26"},
{"history_id":"2771","user_id":"34","game_stage":"7","question":"20÷4÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:33"},
{"history_id":"2772","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"205+31x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":155}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":441,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":236}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:36"},
{"history_id":"2773","user_id":"35","game_stage":"8","question":"158÷79+7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":79}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:39"},
{"history_id":"2774","user_id":"50","game_stage":"6","question":"86-75-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:50"},
{"history_id":"2775","user_id":"47","game_stage":"7","question":"174÷3x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":928,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":928,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:49:54"},
{"history_id":"2776","user_id":"51","game_stage":"11","question":"11x(264-78)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2046,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":186}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2046,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":186}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:02"},
{"history_id":"2777","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"681-85x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":681,\"numB\":680}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":596,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":681,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4768,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":596,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:05"},
{"history_id":"2778","user_id":"57","game_stage":"9","question":"195÷65+286","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":286}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":286}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:07"},
{"history_id":"2779","user_id":"53","game_stage":"9","question":"150+35x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":605,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":455}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":185,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2505,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:07"},
{"history_id":"2780","user_id":"40","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c612\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527261\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u527235\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"12x(61+35)","userAns_obj":"12+61-35","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u52a0\u6cd5\u8207\u4e58\u6cd5\u6703\u4f7f\u7d50\u679c\u589e","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:11"},
{"history_id":"2781","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"30x11+11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":341,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":330,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":660,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:11"},
{"history_id":"2782","user_id":"34","game_stage":"7","question":"7x8x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:12"},
{"history_id":"2783","user_id":"35","game_stage":"8","question":"56x3-50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:19"},
{"history_id":"2784","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"27÷3+86","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":86}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:37"},
{"history_id":"2785","user_id":"48","game_stage":"8","question":"8x8+139","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:39"},
{"history_id":"2786","user_id":"58","game_stage":"11","question":"(200-38)÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:39"},
{"history_id":"2787","user_id":"31","game_stage":"9","question":"213+57÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:42"},
{"history_id":"2788","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"110÷10-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:43"},
{"history_id":"2790","user_id":"47","game_stage":"7","question":"70x10÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":700,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":700,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":700,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":700,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:53"},
{"history_id":"2791","user_id":"32","game_stage":"10","question":"11x(59+101)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1760,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":160}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":101}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1760,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":160}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:53"},
{"history_id":"2792","user_id":"54","game_stage":"8","question":"196÷98+57","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:50:55"},
{"history_id":"2793","user_id":"50","game_stage":"6","question":"53x7x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":371,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3339,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":371,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":371,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3339,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":371,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:05"},
{"history_id":"2794","user_id":"39","game_stage":"9","question":"94+280÷40","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:16"},
{"history_id":"2795","user_id":"45","game_stage":"9","question":"180-252÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":84}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":84}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:17"},
{"history_id":"2796","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"165+28x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":417,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":252}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":417,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":252}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:17"},
{"history_id":"2797","user_id":"35","game_stage":"8","question":"116÷4+135","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":135}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":135}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:19"},
{"history_id":"2798","user_id":"53","game_stage":"9","question":"108+123x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1338,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":1230}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2310,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:20"},
{"history_id":"2799","user_id":"58","game_stage":"11","question":"(159-59)÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:23"},
{"history_id":"2800","user_id":"40","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u62105\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u5806125\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u5806196\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"5x(125+196)","userAns_obj":"196-(125+5)","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u52a0\u6cd5\u8207\u4e58\u6cd5\u6703\u4f7f\u7d50\u679c\u589e","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:27"},
{"history_id":"2801","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"288+64÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":640,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":352}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:37"},
{"history_id":"2803","user_id":"42","game_stage":"7","question":"204÷3÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":204,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:49"},
{"history_id":"2804","user_id":"32","game_stage":"10","question":"(170+38)÷104","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":104}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":104}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:52"},
{"history_id":"2805","user_id":"51","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c613\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u52724\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272113\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"13x(4+113)","userAns_obj":"x4)((11313","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:59"},
{"history_id":"2806","user_id":"39","game_stage":"9","question":"66-6÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:51:59"},
{"history_id":"2807","user_id":"54","game_stage":"8","question":"42-49÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:52:08"},
{"history_id":"2808","user_id":"57","game_stage":"9","question":"152÷4-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:52:11"},
{"history_id":"2809","user_id":"35","game_stage":"9","question":"25x5+236","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":361,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":236}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":361,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":236}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:52:30"},
{"history_id":"2810","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"29x7-74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":74}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:52:41"},
{"history_id":"2811","user_id":"40","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86111\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86180\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e869\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"9x(111+180)","userAns_obj":"","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:52:43"},
{"history_id":"2812","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"137+147÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:52:48"},
{"history_id":"2814","user_id":"35","game_stage":"9","question":"274÷137-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":136}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:53:49"},
{"history_id":"2815","user_id":"45","game_stage":"9","question":"114x1-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:54:01"},
{"history_id":"2816","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"290+138x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1670,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":1380}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1670,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":1380}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:55:07"},
{"history_id":"2817","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"287÷41-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":287,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":287,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:56:18"},
{"history_id":"2818","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"288÷2-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 09:56:55"},
{"history_id":"2819","user_id":"36","game_stage":"8","question":"100-26x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:08:06"},
{"history_id":"2820","user_id":"35","game_stage":"9","question":"209-23x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":209,\"numB\":161}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":209,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1302,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:08:12"},
{"history_id":"2821","user_id":"53","game_stage":"9","question":"221+121x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":1936}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":342,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:08:38"},
{"history_id":"2822","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"77÷11-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:08:43"},
{"history_id":"2823","user_id":"40","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u621010\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u580650\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u5806181\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"10x(50+181)","userAns_obj":"(50+181)x10","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:09:02"},
{"history_id":"2824","user_id":"35","game_stage":"9","question":"1106-134x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1072,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1106,\"numB\":1072}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":972,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1106,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7776,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":972,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:09:30"},
{"history_id":"2825","user_id":"51","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u62105\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u5806171\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u5806118\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"5x(171+118)","userAns_obj":"171x5","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u52a0\u6cd5\u8207\u4e58\u6cd5\u6703\u4f7f\u7d50\u679c\u589e","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:09:35"},
{"history_id":"2826","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"138+89x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":534,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":672,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":534}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":227,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":89}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1362,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":227,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:09:56"},
{"history_id":"2827","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"22x10-184","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":220,\"numB\":184}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":220,\"numB\":184}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:09:56"},
{"history_id":"2828","user_id":"32","game_stage":"10","question":"(141-85)x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:10:07"},
{"history_id":"2829","user_id":"51","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8632\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86150\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e8612\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"12x(32+150)","userAns_obj":"(32+150)x12","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:10:09"},
{"history_id":"2830","user_id":"58","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8621\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8678\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e862\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"2x(21+78)","userAns_obj":"(21+78)x2","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:10:25"},
{"history_id":"2831","user_id":"53","game_stage":"9","question":"283+27÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":283,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":283,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:10:37"},
{"history_id":"2832","user_id":"34","game_stage":"8","question":"47x13+193","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":611,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":804,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":611,\"numB\":193}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":193}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:10:37"},
{"history_id":"2833","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"193-41x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":164}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":164}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:10:50"},
{"history_id":"2834","user_id":"36","game_stage":"9","question":"296+26x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":810,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:10:58"},
{"history_id":"2835","user_id":"55","game_stage":"8","question":"3x6-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:11:13"},
{"history_id":"2836","user_id":"34","game_stage":"8","question":"107+87÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:11:16"},
{"history_id":"2837","user_id":"57","game_stage":"9","question":"267+110x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":990,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1257,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":990}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":990,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1257,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":990}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:11:23"},
{"history_id":"2838","user_id":"48","game_stage":"8","question":"24÷8+180","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":180}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":180}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:11:35"},
{"history_id":"2839","user_id":"35","game_stage":"9","question":"32x10+62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":382,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":320,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:11:36"},
{"history_id":"2840","user_id":"34","game_stage":"8","question":"128÷4+175","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":175}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":175}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:11:43"},
{"history_id":"2841","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"126÷2+146","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":146}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":146}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:11:48"},
{"history_id":"2842","user_id":"53","game_stage":"9","question":"1701-121x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1694,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1701,\"numB\":1694}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1694,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1701,\"numB\":1694}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:12:02"},
{"history_id":"2843","user_id":"32","game_stage":"11","question":"711÷(237÷3)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":711,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":711,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis04mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:12:10"},
{"history_id":"2844","user_id":"35","game_stage":"9","question":"96+93x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":375,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":279}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":375,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":279}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:12:23"},
{"history_id":"2845","user_id":"48","game_stage":"8","question":"123-95x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":95}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":95}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:12:26"},
{"history_id":"2846","user_id":"34","game_stage":"8","question":"39-8x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":32}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:12:30"},
{"history_id":"2847","user_id":"35","game_stage":"9","question":"55÷5-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:12:50"},
{"history_id":"2848","user_id":"56","game_stage":"9","question":"1096-82x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1066,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1096,\"numB\":1066}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1066,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1096,\"numB\":1066}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:13:01"},
{"history_id":"2849","user_id":"54","game_stage":"8","question":"12x5-37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:13:04"},
{"history_id":"2850","user_id":"48","game_stage":"8","question":"38÷2+101","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":101}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":101}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:13:07"},
{"history_id":"2851","user_id":"57","game_stage":"10","question":"139-(143-9)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":134}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":134}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:13:09"},
{"history_id":"2852","user_id":"53","game_stage":"9","question":"158-250÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":125}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":125}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:13:17"},
{"history_id":"2853","user_id":"32","game_stage":"11","question":"(176-139)-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:13:25"},
{"history_id":"2854","user_id":"35","game_stage":"9","question":"16+4x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:13:25"},
{"history_id":"2855","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"138÷2+182","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":182}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":182}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:13:56"},
{"history_id":"2856","user_id":"54","game_stage":"8","question":"608-45x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":585,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":608,\"numB\":585}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":563,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":608,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7319,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":563,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:03"},
{"history_id":"2857","user_id":"32","game_stage":"11","question":"(73+153)x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":153}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":904,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":153}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":904,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:16"},
{"history_id":"2858","user_id":"57","game_stage":"10","question":"16÷(64÷8)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:17"},
{"history_id":"2860","user_id":"31","game_stage":"9","question":"28÷7+56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:33"},
{"history_id":"2861","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"59-114÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:35"},
{"history_id":"2862","user_id":"34","game_stage":"8","question":"172÷2+63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:38"},
{"history_id":"2863","user_id":"53","game_stage":"10","question":"123-(168-50)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:38"},
{"history_id":"2864","user_id":"54","game_stage":"8","question":"63x3-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:44"},
{"history_id":"2865","user_id":"55","game_stage":"9","question":"142÷2+273","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":273}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":273}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:46"},
{"history_id":"2866","user_id":"35","game_stage":"4","question":"182÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:47"},
{"history_id":"2867","user_id":"47","game_stage":"8","question":"30+42÷21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:14:56"},
{"history_id":"2868","user_id":"46","game_stage":"8","question":"144+87÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:07"},
{"history_id":"2870","user_id":"35","game_stage":"4","question":"61x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":366,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":366,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:13"},
{"history_id":"2871","user_id":"48","game_stage":"9","question":"92x6+207","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":759,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":552,\"numB\":207}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":759,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":552,\"numB\":207}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:19"},
{"history_id":"2872","user_id":"34","game_stage":"8","question":"220-21x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":220,\"numB\":168}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":220,\"numB\":168}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:20"},
{"history_id":"2873","user_id":"57","game_stage":"10","question":"(195-25)x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1870,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1870,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:24"},
{"history_id":"2874","user_id":"56","game_stage":"10","question":"1524÷(193-66)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1524,\"numB\":127}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1524,\"numB\":127}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:32"},
{"history_id":"2875","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"196+55-213","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":213}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":213}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:34"},
{"history_id":"2876","user_id":"53","game_stage":"10","question":"(175+18)÷193","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":193}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":193}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:39"},
{"history_id":"2877","user_id":"39","game_stage":"9","question":"74x2-29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1484,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1455,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1484,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:42"},
{"history_id":"2878","user_id":"35","game_stage":"4","question":"188-91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:43"},
{"history_id":"2879","user_id":"42","game_stage":"7","question":"88+284+154","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":284}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":526,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":372,\"numB\":154}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":284,\"numB\":154}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:44"},
{"history_id":"2881","user_id":"47","game_stage":"8","question":"119+70x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":840,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":959,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":840}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:47"},
{"history_id":"2882","user_id":"34","game_stage":"8","question":"194÷97+154","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":154}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":154}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:49"},
{"history_id":"2883","user_id":"32","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86181\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8631\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e866\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"6x(181+31)","userAns_obj":"(181+31)x6","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:49"},
{"history_id":"2884","user_id":"31","game_stage":"9","question":"116÷29-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:15:56"},
{"history_id":"2885","user_id":"50","game_stage":"6","question":"106÷53x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:02"},
{"history_id":"2886","user_id":"55","game_stage":"9","question":"141x7-135","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":987,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":852,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":987,\"numB\":135}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":987,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":852,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":987,\"numB\":135}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:08"},
{"history_id":"2887","user_id":"36","game_stage":"9","question":"135+87÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:08"},
{"history_id":"2888","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"136÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:12"},
{"history_id":"2889","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"97x5x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":485,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":485,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":485,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":485,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":485,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":485,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:16"},
{"history_id":"2891","user_id":"56","game_stage":"10","question":"395÷(64+15)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":395,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":395,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:25"},
{"history_id":"2892","user_id":"42","game_stage":"7","question":"2x5÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:33"},
{"history_id":"2893","user_id":"48","game_stage":"9","question":"84-33÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:44"},
{"history_id":"2894","user_id":"44","game_stage":"6","question":"165-75-46","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":46}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":46}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:48"},
{"history_id":"2895","user_id":"53","game_stage":"10","question":"(101-15)x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:52"},
{"history_id":"2896","user_id":"56","game_stage":"10","question":"(68-38)÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:52"},
{"history_id":"2897","user_id":"39","game_stage":"9","question":"292÷4-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":292,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":292,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:16:53"},
{"history_id":"2898","user_id":"36","game_stage":"9","question":"34x4-115","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":115}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":115}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:01"},
{"history_id":"2899","user_id":"31","game_stage":"9","question":"88-161÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":161}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:02"},
{"history_id":"2900","user_id":"55","game_stage":"9","question":"865-100x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":865,\"numB\":800}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":865,\"numB\":800}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:13"},
{"history_id":"2901","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"120÷15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:16"},
{"history_id":"2902","user_id":"48","game_stage":"9","question":"249÷83+188","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":188}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":188}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:18"},
{"history_id":"2903","user_id":"54","game_stage":"9","question":"104+95÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:22"},
{"history_id":"2904","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"60+168","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":228,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":168}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1221181111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":168}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:31"},
{"history_id":"2905","user_id":"50","game_stage":"7","question":"292-81-175","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":292,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":175}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":292,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":175}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:40"},
{"history_id":"2906","user_id":"39","game_stage":"9","question":"55x13-605","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":715,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":715,\"numB\":605}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":715,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":715,\"numB\":605}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:17:48"},
{"history_id":"2907","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"69÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":948787878,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:03"},
{"history_id":"2908","user_id":"36","game_stage":"9","question":"179-81x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":81}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":81}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:13"},
{"history_id":"2909","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"58÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:25"},
{"history_id":"2910","user_id":"57","game_stage":"11","question":"2604÷(284-98)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":284,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2604,\"numB\":186}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":284,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2783,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2604,\"numB\":106}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:31"},
{"history_id":"2911","user_id":"55","game_stage":"10","question":"10x(81+116)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":197,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1970,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":197}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":810,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":926,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":810,\"numB\":116}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:31"},
{"history_id":"2912","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"134+111","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":111}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":111}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:35"},
{"history_id":"2913","user_id":"56","game_stage":"11","question":"15x(82+176)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":176}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3870,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":258}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":176}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3870,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":258}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:42"},
{"history_id":"2914","user_id":"50","game_stage":"7","question":"81x5x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":405,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":405,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":405,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":405,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:43"},
{"history_id":"2915","user_id":"40","game_stage":"4","question":"84x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":924,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":924,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:18:57"},
{"history_id":"2916","user_id":"48","game_stage":"10","question":"2639÷(166+37)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2639,\"numB\":203}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2639,\"numB\":203}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:19:15"},
{"history_id":"2917","user_id":"36","game_stage":"9","question":"854-59x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":826,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":854,\"numB\":826}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":826,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":854,\"numB\":826}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:19:30"},
{"history_id":"2918","user_id":"50","game_stage":"7","question":"160÷8x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:19:35"},
{"history_id":"2919","user_id":"56","game_stage":"11","question":"(159-117)-35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":117}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":117}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:19:40"},
{"history_id":"2920","user_id":"55","game_stage":"10","question":"3497÷(138+131)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":131}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3497,\"numB\":269}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":131}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3497,\"numB\":269}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:19:52"},
{"history_id":"2921","user_id":"56","game_stage":"11","question":"1520÷(240+140)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":380,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":140}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1520,\"numB\":380}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":380,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":140}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1520,\"numB\":380}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:20:37"},
{"history_id":"2922","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"16+16-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:34:58"},
{"history_id":"2923","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"45+5+57","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:15"},
{"history_id":"2924","user_id":"16","game_stage":"8","question":"49÷7+33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:19"},
{"history_id":"2925","user_id":"29","game_stage":"9","question":"146+84x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":840,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":986,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":840}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":840,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":986,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":840}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:19"},
{"history_id":"2926","user_id":"30","game_stage":"7","question":"289-40+213","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":289,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":213}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":289,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":213}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:20"},
{"history_id":"2927","user_id":"12","game_stage":"4","question":"166-94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:30"},
{"history_id":"2928","user_id":"23","game_stage":"8","question":"126+12÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:33"},
{"history_id":"2929","user_id":"24","game_stage":"4","question":"58+171","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":171}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":759,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":171}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:40"},
{"history_id":"2930","user_id":"16","game_stage":"8","question":"7x2-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:48"},
{"history_id":"2931","user_id":"30","game_stage":"7","question":"261-47+79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":261,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":261,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:53"},
{"history_id":"2932","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"189÷3x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":567,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:56"},
{"history_id":"2933","user_id":"12","game_stage":"4","question":"195-72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:57"},
{"history_id":"2934","user_id":"25","game_stage":"8","question":"25x5+168","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":168}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":168}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:35:57"},
{"history_id":"2935","user_id":"7","game_stage":"7","question":"285+53+255","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":338,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":593,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":338,\"numB\":255}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":308,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":255}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":593,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":308}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:03"},
{"history_id":"2936","user_id":"11","game_stage":"8","question":"148+49x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":196}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":197,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":788,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:03"},
{"history_id":"2937","user_id":"29","game_stage":"9","question":"23-146÷73","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:03"},
{"history_id":"2938","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"136+81x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":162}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":434,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:04"},
{"history_id":"2939","user_id":"16","game_stage":"8","question":"552-88x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":528,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":552,\"numB\":528}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":528,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":552,\"numB\":528}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:14"},
{"history_id":"2940","user_id":"27","game_stage":"6","question":"113+66-77","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:16"},
{"history_id":"2941","user_id":"12","game_stage":"4","question":"99-79","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:18"},
{"history_id":"2942","user_id":"6","game_stage":"4","question":"33x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:19"},
{"history_id":"2943","user_id":"28","game_stage":"4","question":"74-24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:21"},
{"history_id":"2944","user_id":"25","game_stage":"8","question":"64÷4-10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:24"},
{"history_id":"2945","user_id":"15","game_stage":"7","question":"122-90+167","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":90}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":167}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":90}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":167}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:25"},
{"history_id":"2946","user_id":"10","game_stage":"4","question":"116÷58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:30"},
{"history_id":"2947","user_id":"11","game_stage":"8","question":"83+8x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:32"},
{"history_id":"2948","user_id":"23","game_stage":"8","question":"186+44x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":406,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":220}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:33"},
{"history_id":"2949","user_id":"13","game_stage":"8","question":"74÷37+158","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":158}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":158}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:37"},
{"history_id":"2950","user_id":"29","game_stage":"9","question":"230÷5-13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:40"},
{"history_id":"2951","user_id":"14","game_stage":"7","question":"243-37-110","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":110}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:46"},
{"history_id":"2952","user_id":"25","game_stage":"8","question":"60+31x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:47"},
{"history_id":"2953","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"64x12+28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":768,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":796,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":768,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":768,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":796,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":768,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:36:49"},
{"history_id":"2954","user_id":"6","game_stage":"4","question":"138÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:03"},
{"history_id":"2955","user_id":"24","game_stage":"4","question":"142÷71","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":71}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:05"},
{"history_id":"2956","user_id":"28","game_stage":"4","question":"88÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:09"},
{"history_id":"2957","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"24x13x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2808,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:11"},
{"history_id":"2958","user_id":"23","game_stage":"8","question":"84+11x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:11"},
{"history_id":"2959","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"62-99÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:12"},
{"history_id":"2960","user_id":"7","game_stage":"7","question":"92x11x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1012,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4048,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1012,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4048,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:13"},
{"history_id":"2961","user_id":"11","game_stage":"8","question":"50+91x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1001,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1051,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":1001}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1551,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:13"},
{"history_id":"2962","user_id":"19","game_stage":"4","question":"9x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:15"},
{"history_id":"2963","user_id":"8","game_stage":"7","question":"214-88+38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":126}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:17"},
{"history_id":"2964","user_id":"12","game_stage":"6","question":"184-92-35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:37"},
{"history_id":"2965","user_id":"30","game_stage":"7","question":"69x10x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":690,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":690,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":690,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":690,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:38"},
{"history_id":"2966","user_id":"13","game_stage":"8","question":"42x12-268","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":504,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":504,\"numB\":268}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":504,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":504,\"numB\":268}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:40"},
{"history_id":"2967","user_id":"3","game_stage":"7","question":"92-8+29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:40"},
{"history_id":"2968","user_id":"24","game_stage":"4","question":"125+83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:40"},
{"history_id":"2969","user_id":"26","game_stage":"7","question":"184+295+215","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":479,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":295}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":694,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":479,\"numB\":215}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":510,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":215}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":694,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":510}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:42"},
{"history_id":"2970","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"80x5-114","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":400,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":400,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":400,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":400,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:43"},
{"history_id":"2971","user_id":"10","game_stage":"4","question":"92÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:45"},
{"history_id":"2972","user_id":"15","game_stage":"7","question":"88x11x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":968,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4840,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":968,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":968,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4940,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":968,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:45"},
{"history_id":"2973","user_id":"28","game_stage":"4","question":"175+78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:46"},
{"history_id":"2974","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"298÷149+18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":149}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:48"},
{"history_id":"2975","user_id":"29","game_stage":"10","question":"85-(58-17)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:53"},
{"history_id":"2976","user_id":"19","game_stage":"4","question":"166÷83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:55"},
{"history_id":"2977","user_id":"27","game_stage":"6","question":"91x1x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:55"},
{"history_id":"2978","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"151-17+114","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:56"},
{"history_id":"2979","user_id":"14","game_stage":"7","question":"119-31+9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:37:57"},
{"history_id":"2980","user_id":"12","game_stage":"6","question":"119-61-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:15"},
{"history_id":"2981","user_id":"7","game_stage":"7","question":"192-134-22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":112}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:17"},
{"history_id":"2982","user_id":"24","game_stage":"4","question":"147÷21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:19"},
{"history_id":"2983","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"63x7+20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":441,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":461,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":441,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1701,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:19"},
{"history_id":"2984","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"135÷3-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":0}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:29"},
{"history_id":"2985","user_id":"13","game_stage":"8","question":"28x7-27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:29"},
{"history_id":"2986","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"86x5x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":430,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":430,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":430,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":430,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:41"},
{"history_id":"2987","user_id":"10","game_stage":"4","question":"47x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:45"},
{"history_id":"2988","user_id":"8","game_stage":"7","question":"38+18-53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:46"},
{"history_id":"2989","user_id":"30","game_stage":"7","question":"148÷4÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:46"},
{"history_id":"2990","user_id":"27","game_stage":"6","question":"135÷5÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:47"},
{"history_id":"2991","user_id":"19","game_stage":"4","question":"120÷15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:48"},
{"history_id":"2992","user_id":"15","game_stage":"7","question":"52x5÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:49"},
{"history_id":"2993","user_id":"26","game_stage":"7","question":"273÷7÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:53"},
{"history_id":"2994","user_id":"6","game_stage":"6","question":"130-47+55","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":55}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:54"},
{"history_id":"2995","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"44÷22÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:38:59"},
{"history_id":"2996","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"76-55÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:02"},
{"history_id":"2997","user_id":"23","game_stage":"8","question":"23+125÷25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:07"},
{"history_id":"2998","user_id":"7","game_stage":"7","question":"233+75+226","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":308,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":534,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":308,\"numB\":226}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":301,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":226}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":534,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":301}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:09"},
{"history_id":"2999","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"56-21+117","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":117}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":271,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":117}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:15"},
{"history_id":"3000","user_id":"14","game_stage":"7","question":"129x6x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":774,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1548,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":774,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":774,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1548,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":774,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:20"},
{"history_id":"3001","user_id":"10","game_stage":"4","question":"125-85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:27"},
{"history_id":"3002","user_id":"12","game_stage":"6","question":"40x9x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":360,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":360,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:29"},
{"history_id":"3003","user_id":"11","game_stage":"8","question":"185÷5+18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:31"},
{"history_id":"3004","user_id":"18","game_stage":"3","question":"38x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:32"},
{"history_id":"3005","user_id":"21","game_stage":"6","question":"121+51-151","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":151}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:34"},
{"history_id":"3006","user_id":"6","game_stage":"6","question":"28+27-51","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":51}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":51}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:44"},
{"history_id":"3007","user_id":"28","game_stage":"6","question":"105-97+25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:47"},
{"history_id":"3008","user_id":"24","game_stage":"6","question":"76-43-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:51"},
{"history_id":"3009","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"207÷3+200","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":207,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":200}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":200}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":207,\"numB\":203}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:52"},
{"history_id":"3010","user_id":"15","game_stage":"7","question":"29x6÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:53"},
{"history_id":"3011","user_id":"29","game_stage":"10","question":"370÷(111÷3)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:56"},
{"history_id":"3012","user_id":"12","game_stage":"6","question":"41x5÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:39:56"},
{"history_id":"3013","user_id":"17","game_stage":"3","question":"65÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:00"},
{"history_id":"3014","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"4÷2+231","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":231}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":231}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:01"},
{"history_id":"3015","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"19+194-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":213,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":213,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":999,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:06"},
{"history_id":"3016","user_id":"23","game_stage":"8","question":"102-118÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:08"},
{"history_id":"3017","user_id":"14","game_stage":"7","question":"249+166-285","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":415,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":166}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":415,\"numB\":285}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":405,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":166}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":405,\"numB\":285}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:09"},
{"history_id":"3018","user_id":"11","game_stage":"8","question":"145÷5-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:16"},
{"history_id":"3019","user_id":"8","game_stage":"7","question":"176÷2x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:19"},
{"history_id":"3020","user_id":"25","game_stage":"9","question":"170+16x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":378,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":208}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5580,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:21"},
{"history_id":"3021","user_id":"6","game_stage":"6","question":"182÷91÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:29"},
{"history_id":"3022","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"137+59+172","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":368,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":43243772,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":73737216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43243772,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:33"},
{"history_id":"3023","user_id":"26","game_stage":"7","question":"176÷88x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:34"},
{"history_id":"3024","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"172÷2+143","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":143}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:34"},
{"history_id":"3025","user_id":"24","game_stage":"6","question":"93x6x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":558,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":558,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":876,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:35"},
{"history_id":"3026","user_id":"29","game_stage":"10","question":"(132-91)÷41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:35"},
{"history_id":"3027","user_id":"21","game_stage":"7","question":"4+53-45","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:38"},
{"history_id":"3028","user_id":"28","game_stage":"6","question":"133-81+180","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":180}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":180}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:38"},
{"history_id":"3029","user_id":"7","game_stage":"8","question":"99÷33+193","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":193}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":193}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:39"},
{"history_id":"3030","user_id":"14","game_stage":"7","question":"106÷53x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:42"},
{"history_id":"3031","user_id":"18","game_stage":"3","question":"88÷44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:54"},
{"history_id":"3032","user_id":"11","game_stage":"8","question":"900-85x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":850,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":900,\"numB\":850}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":815,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":900,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":815,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:40:59"},
{"history_id":"3033","user_id":"19","game_stage":"6","question":"116+172+174","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":172}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":346,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":174}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":346}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:00"},
{"history_id":"3034","user_id":"15","game_stage":"7","question":"236+193+164","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":429,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":193}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":593,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":429,\"numB\":164}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":479,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":193}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":643,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":479,\"numB\":164}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:01"},
{"history_id":"3035","user_id":"10","game_stage":"6","question":"159-10+71","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":71}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:02"},
{"history_id":"3036","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"1795-142x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1704,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1795,\"numB\":1704}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1704,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1795,\"numB\":1704}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:02"},
{"history_id":"3037","user_id":"23","game_stage":"8","question":"42-124÷62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:04"},
{"history_id":"3038","user_id":"12","game_stage":"7","question":"232-139-51","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":51}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":51}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:09"},
{"history_id":"3039","user_id":"7","game_stage":"8","question":"15-16÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:11"},
{"history_id":"3040","user_id":"8","game_stage":"7","question":"181-133+207","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":133}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":207}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":133}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":207}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:13"},
{"history_id":"3041","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"65÷13+27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:16"},
{"history_id":"3042","user_id":"27","game_stage":"7","question":"149+165+80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":314,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":165}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":394,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":314,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":394,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":245}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:21"},
{"history_id":"3043","user_id":"24","game_stage":"6","question":"123÷3x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":369,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":369,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:24"},
{"history_id":"3044","user_id":"6","game_stage":"6","question":"23x6÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:26"},
{"history_id":"3045","user_id":"3","game_stage":"7","question":"273÷7÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:28"},
{"history_id":"3046","user_id":"25","game_stage":"9","question":"44+130x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1604,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":1560}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":471,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":130}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5652,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":471,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:32"},
{"history_id":"3047","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"105+91x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":910,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1015,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":910}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":910,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1015,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":910}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:36"},
{"history_id":"3048","user_id":"23","game_stage":"8","question":"132+67x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":804,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":804}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":804,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":804}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:44"},
{"history_id":"3049","user_id":"18","game_stage":"3","question":"36÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:47"},
{"history_id":"3050","user_id":"7","game_stage":"8","question":"53-119÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:54"},
{"history_id":"3051","user_id":"12","game_stage":"7","question":"115x1÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:57"},
{"history_id":"3052","user_id":"10","game_stage":"6","question":"82x4÷164","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":328,\"numB\":164}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":328,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":328,\"numB\":164}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:41:58"},
{"history_id":"3053","user_id":"21","game_stage":"7","question":"67x8÷134","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":536,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":536,\"numB\":134}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":536,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":536,\"numB\":134}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:01"},
{"history_id":"3054","user_id":"28","game_stage":"6","question":"123-88+36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:01"},
{"history_id":"3055","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"45÷3-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:11"},
{"history_id":"3056","user_id":"26","game_stage":"8","question":"12+68x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":816,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":828,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":816}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:15"},
{"history_id":"3057","user_id":"3","game_stage":"7","question":"260÷26x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:15"},
{"history_id":"3058","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"35-155÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis04mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:16"},
{"history_id":"3059","user_id":"14","game_stage":"8","question":"15x8+143","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":263,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":263,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":143}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:18"},
{"history_id":"3060","user_id":"17","game_stage":"3","question":"13x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:22"},
{"history_id":"3061","user_id":"24","game_stage":"6","question":"87x9x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":783,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2349,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":783,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":783,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2349,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":783,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:26"},
{"history_id":"3062","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"88x4+145","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":497,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":352,\"numB\":145}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":497,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":352,\"numB\":145}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:28"},
{"history_id":"3063","user_id":"11","game_stage":"8","question":"34-16÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:30"},
{"history_id":"3064","user_id":"10","game_stage":"6","question":"199-61+110","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":110}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":171}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:34"},
{"history_id":"3065","user_id":"29","game_stage":"11","question":"27÷(21÷7)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:36"},
{"history_id":"3066","user_id":"6","game_stage":"7","question":"273-123+166","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":166}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":166}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:38"},
{"history_id":"3067","user_id":"9","game_stage":"8","question":"7x8+6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:39"},
{"history_id":"3068","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"78x4+170","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":482,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":170}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":170}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":13572,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:39"},
{"history_id":"3069","user_id":"21","game_stage":"7","question":"93÷31x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:42"},
{"history_id":"3070","user_id":"12","game_stage":"7","question":"292-39+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":292,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":345,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":253,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":292,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":345,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":253,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:43"},
{"history_id":"3071","user_id":"14","game_stage":"8","question":"28÷14-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:48"},
{"history_id":"3072","user_id":"25","game_stage":"9","question":"176+7x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1464,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:54"},
{"history_id":"3073","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"190+99÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":289,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:54"},
{"history_id":"3074","user_id":"27","game_stage":"7","question":"232÷116x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:42:55"},
{"history_id":"3075","user_id":"11","game_stage":"8","question":"126÷9-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:10"},
{"history_id":"3076","user_id":"15","game_stage":"7","question":"242+237+225","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":479,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":242,\"numB\":237}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":704,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":479,\"numB\":225}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":479,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":242,\"numB\":237}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":704,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":479,\"numB\":225}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:11"},
{"history_id":"3077","user_id":"26","game_stage":"8","question":"45+59x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":708,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":753,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":708}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:12"},
{"history_id":"3078","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"173-278÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":278}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":541,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:19"},
{"history_id":"3079","user_id":"29","game_stage":"11","question":"(176-133)÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":133}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":133}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:19"},
{"history_id":"3080","user_id":"17","game_stage":"3","question":"32÷16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:19"},
{"history_id":"3081","user_id":"10","game_stage":"6","question":"174÷3÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:20"},
{"history_id":"3082","user_id":"14","game_stage":"8","question":"141÷3+4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":51,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:20"},
{"history_id":"3083","user_id":"6","game_stage":"7","question":"9÷3x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:34"},
{"history_id":"3084","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"116x7-154","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":812,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":658,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":812,\"numB\":154}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":154}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:38"},
{"history_id":"3085","user_id":"34","game_stage":"9","question":"156+21x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":126}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":126}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:39"},
{"history_id":"3086","user_id":"19","game_stage":"6","question":"44x12÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":528,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":528,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:42"},
{"history_id":"3087","user_id":"23","game_stage":"9","question":"89+75÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:45"},
{"history_id":"3088","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"272-74x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":222,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":222}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":594,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:46"},
{"history_id":"3089","user_id":"28","game_stage":"6","question":"172÷4x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":516,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":516,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:46"},
{"history_id":"3090","user_id":"12","game_stage":"8","question":"6÷2+65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:50"},
{"history_id":"3091","user_id":"15","game_stage":"7","question":"160÷4÷20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:50"},
{"history_id":"3092","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"65÷5-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:52"},
{"history_id":"3093","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"142÷71+95","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":95}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":95}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:54"},
{"history_id":"3094","user_id":"18","game_stage":"4","question":"18x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:43:56"},
{"history_id":"3095","user_id":"26","game_stage":"8","question":"21+59x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":767,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":788,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":767}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":767,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":788,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":767}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:00"},
{"history_id":"3096","user_id":"8","game_stage":"8","question":"87+195÷15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":195}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:01"},
{"history_id":"3097","user_id":"29","game_stage":"11","question":"3x(182+120)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":302,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":906,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":302}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":302,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":906,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":302}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:02"},
{"history_id":"3098","user_id":"28","game_stage":"6","question":"16÷8x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:09"},
{"history_id":"3099","user_id":"24","game_stage":"7","question":"193-81+218","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":218}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":218}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:09"},
{"history_id":"3100","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"16÷4-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:14"},
{"history_id":"3101","user_id":"7","game_stage":"9","question":"1x3+226","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":226}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":226}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:15"},
{"history_id":"3102","user_id":"19","game_stage":"6","question":"60÷12÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:18"},
{"history_id":"3103","user_id":"9","game_stage":"9","question":"147x3+238","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":441,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":679,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":441,\"numB\":238}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":679,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":917,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":679,\"numB\":238}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:21"},
{"history_id":"3104","user_id":"23","game_stage":"9","question":"128-24x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:24"},
{"history_id":"3105","user_id":"12","game_stage":"8","question":"9-116÷58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:26"},
{"history_id":"3106","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"427-48x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":427,\"numB\":384}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":427,\"numB\":384}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:30"},
{"history_id":"3107","user_id":"27","game_stage":"7","question":"143x2÷26","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":286,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":0}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis07","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:30"},
{"history_id":"3108","user_id":"34","game_stage":"9","question":"14x12-82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:34"},
{"history_id":"3109","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"39x1-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:34"},
{"history_id":"3110","user_id":"18","game_stage":"4","question":"11+185","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":185}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":185}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:35"},
{"history_id":"3111","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"148x11+20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1628,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1648,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1628,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1628,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1628,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:39"},
{"history_id":"3112","user_id":"6","game_stage":"7","question":"77x15÷105","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1155,\"numB\":105}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1155,\"numB\":105}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:44"},
{"history_id":"3113","user_id":"8","game_stage":"8","question":"125÷5+21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:46"},
{"history_id":"3114","user_id":"26","game_stage":"8","question":"578-57x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":513,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":578,\"numB\":513}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":521,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":578,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4689,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":521,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:47"},
{"history_id":"3115","user_id":"7","game_stage":"9","question":"50-56÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:52"},
{"history_id":"3116","user_id":"16","game_stage":"9","question":"87x14-973","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1218,\"numB\":973}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":245,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1218,\"numB\":973}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:54"},
{"history_id":"3117","user_id":"14","game_stage":"9","question":"5+272÷68","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:57"},
{"history_id":"3118","user_id":"12","game_stage":"8","question":"12x8-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:44:59"},
{"history_id":"3119","user_id":"24","game_stage":"7","question":"68x6÷51","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":408,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":408,\"numB\":51}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":408,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":408,\"numB\":51}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:01"},
{"history_id":"3120","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"48-81÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:04"},
{"history_id":"3121","user_id":"9","game_stage":"9","question":"2x5+101","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":101}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":101}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:06"},
{"history_id":"3122","user_id":"15","game_stage":"7","question":"42x10x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2940,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2940,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:07"},
{"history_id":"3123","user_id":"18","game_stage":"4","question":"70x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:14"},
{"history_id":"3124","user_id":"27","game_stage":"7","question":"50x12x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6000,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":600,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6000,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":120}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:15"},
{"history_id":"3125","user_id":"25","game_stage":"9","question":"287+59x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":885,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":287,\"numB\":885}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":346,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":287,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":346,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:30"},
{"history_id":"3126","user_id":"8","game_stage":"8","question":"30-69÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:35"},
{"history_id":"3127","user_id":"23","game_stage":"9","question":"22-106÷53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:40"},
{"history_id":"3128","user_id":"14","game_stage":"9","question":"536-42x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":536,\"numB\":462}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":536,\"numB\":420}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:41"},
{"history_id":"3129","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"93+112÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":112}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:43"},
{"history_id":"3130","user_id":"17","game_stage":"4","question":"8÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:51"},
{"history_id":"3131","user_id":"28","game_stage":"7","question":"216-106-78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":106}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:53"},
{"history_id":"3132","user_id":"7","game_stage":"9","question":"134x16+296","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2144,\"numB\":296}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2144,\"numB\":296}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:53"},
{"history_id":"3133","user_id":"9","game_stage":"9","question":"214÷107-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":107}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":107}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:57"},
{"history_id":"3134","user_id":"29","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c64\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u5272156\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272184\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"4x(156+184)","userAns_obj":"156x4+184","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:57"},
{"history_id":"3135","user_id":"19","game_stage":"7","question":"105+287-41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":287}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":392,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":287}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":392,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:45:59"},
{"history_id":"3136","user_id":"25","game_stage":"9","question":"67+10÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:46:08"},
{"history_id":"3137","user_id":"10","game_stage":"7","question":"180-60+272","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":60}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":392,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":272}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":272}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":232}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:46:11"},
{"history_id":"3138","user_id":"19","game_stage":"7","question":"268÷4x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":737,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:47:16"},
{"history_id":"3139","user_id":"19","game_stage":"7","question":"63x15x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":945,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":945,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":9450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":150}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:48:36"},
{"history_id":"3140","user_id":"19","game_stage":"7","question":"145÷5÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:49:21"},
{"history_id":"3141","user_id":"12","game_stage":"9","question":"192÷3+251","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":251}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":251}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:59:06"},
{"history_id":"3142","user_id":"19","game_stage":"8","question":"193+8x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:59:11"},
{"history_id":"3143","user_id":"19","game_stage":"8","question":"84-23x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 10:59:36"},
{"history_id":"3144","user_id":"12","game_stage":"9","question":"56-98÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:00:20"},
{"history_id":"3145","user_id":"19","game_stage":"8","question":"55x2-99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:00:28"},
{"history_id":"3146","user_id":"16","game_stage":"10","question":"108÷(45÷5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:00:41"},
{"history_id":"3147","user_id":"12","game_stage":"9","question":"110x4-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":434,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":440,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":440,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":434,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":440,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:00:57"},
{"history_id":"3148","user_id":"11","game_stage":"9","question":"206+294÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":500,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":294}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":500,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:01:04"},
{"history_id":"3149","user_id":"8","game_stage":"8","question":"89-68÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:01:37"},
{"history_id":"3150","user_id":"29","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u621011\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u5806121\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u580687\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"11x(121+87)","userAns_obj":"(121+87)x11","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:01:39"},
{"history_id":"3151","user_id":"25","game_stage":"9","question":"128x2-88","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":88}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:01:44"},
{"history_id":"3152","user_id":"11","game_stage":"9","question":"279+66÷33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":279,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":279,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:01:51"},
{"history_id":"3153","user_id":"19","game_stage":"8","question":"87÷29+120","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":120}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":149}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:01:56"},
{"history_id":"3154","user_id":"16","game_stage":"10","question":"936÷(44+60)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":60}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":936,\"numB\":104}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":936,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:01:58"},
{"history_id":"3155","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"21x7+44","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":44}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":44}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:06"},
{"history_id":"3156","user_id":"12","game_stage":"10","question":"10x(91-28)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":630,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":630,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:13"},
{"history_id":"3157","user_id":"24","game_stage":"7","question":"78x7÷91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":546,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":546,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":546,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":546,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:17"},
{"history_id":"3158","user_id":"15","game_stage":"8","question":"44+44÷22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:28"},
{"history_id":"3159","user_id":"3","game_stage":"8","question":"178÷2+60","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":60}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:38"},
{"history_id":"3160","user_id":"16","game_stage":"10","question":"6x(44-11)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":44}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:38"},
{"history_id":"3161","user_id":"19","game_stage":"8","question":"593-69x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":593,\"numB\":552}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":593,\"numB\":552}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:42"},
{"history_id":"3162","user_id":"12","game_stage":"10","question":"20÷(95÷19)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:54"},
{"history_id":"3163","user_id":"25","game_stage":"9","question":"26-45÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:55"},
{"history_id":"3164","user_id":"11","game_stage":"9","question":"38x8-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":274,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":304,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":304,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":274,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":304,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:02:59"},
{"history_id":"3165","user_id":"15","game_stage":"8","question":"91x1+116","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":116}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":116}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:03:01"},
{"history_id":"3166","user_id":"8","game_stage":"8","question":"71+147÷49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":147}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:03:08"},
{"history_id":"3167","user_id":"34","game_stage":"9","question":"189÷3-56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:03:13"},
{"history_id":"3168","user_id":"3","game_stage":"8","question":"22÷2-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:03:17"},
{"history_id":"3169","user_id":"34","game_stage":"9","question":"286÷11-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":286,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":286,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:03:47"},
{"history_id":"3170","user_id":"12","game_stage":"10","question":"116-(163-71)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:03:48"},
{"history_id":"3171","user_id":"15","game_stage":"8","question":"60-148÷74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:03:58"},
{"history_id":"3172","user_id":"7","game_stage":"10","question":"228÷(190÷5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:04:04"},
{"history_id":"3173","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"147x16-1457","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":895,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2352,\"numB\":1457}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":895,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2352,\"numB\":1457}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:04:04"},
{"history_id":"3174","user_id":"3","game_stage":"8","question":"87÷29+170","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":170}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":170}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:04:07"},
{"history_id":"3175","user_id":"16","game_stage":"10","question":"205-(165-14)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":165}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:04:29"},
{"history_id":"3176","user_id":"24","game_stage":"8","question":"49÷7+193","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":193}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":193}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":200}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:04:30"},
{"history_id":"3177","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"91÷7+151","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":151}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:04:56"},
{"history_id":"3178","user_id":"12","game_stage":"11","question":"906÷(198+104)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":302,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":104}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":906,\"numB\":302}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":302,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":104}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":906,\"numB\":302}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:04:58"},
{"history_id":"3179","user_id":"25","game_stage":"10","question":"70÷(28÷2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:04:59"},
{"history_id":"3180","user_id":"8","game_stage":"8","question":"105+65÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:01"},
{"history_id":"3181","user_id":"11","game_stage":"9","question":"143x9+142","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1287,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1429,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1287,\"numB\":142}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1349,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1207,\"numB\":142}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:09"},
{"history_id":"3182","user_id":"15","game_stage":"8","question":"44-117÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:17"},
{"history_id":"3183","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"218÷2+24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":109,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:21"},
{"history_id":"3184","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"65-99÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:22"},
{"history_id":"3185","user_id":"24","game_stage":"8","question":"125+8÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:26"},
{"history_id":"3186","user_id":"7","game_stage":"10","question":"(172+74)x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":246,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":246,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:28"},
{"history_id":"3187","user_id":"19","game_stage":"9","question":"79x14+100","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1106,\"numB\":100}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":100}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:40"},
{"history_id":"3188","user_id":"8","game_stage":"8","question":"227-55x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":227,\"numB\":165}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":227,\"numB\":165}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:40"},
{"history_id":"3189","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"27-86÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:42"},
{"history_id":"3190","user_id":"25","game_stage":"10","question":"(110+73)÷61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:05:46"},
{"history_id":"3191","user_id":"24","game_stage":"8","question":"29+68x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":136}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:05"},
{"history_id":"3192","user_id":"8","game_stage":"8","question":"44÷4+19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:05"},
{"history_id":"3193","user_id":"7","game_stage":"10","question":"(175-70)x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:17"},
{"history_id":"3194","user_id":"13","game_stage":"9","question":"1473-133x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1463,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1473,\"numB\":1463}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1463,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1473,\"numB\":1463}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:17"},
{"history_id":"3195","user_id":"19","game_stage":"9","question":"85÷17+93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:23"},
{"history_id":"3196","user_id":"11","game_stage":"9","question":"228+247÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:29"},
{"history_id":"3197","user_id":"6","game_stage":"8","question":"33÷3+52","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":52}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":52}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:35"},
{"history_id":"3198","user_id":"16","game_stage":"10","question":"810÷(165-3)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":810,\"numB\":162}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":810,\"numB\":165}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:36"},
{"history_id":"3199","user_id":"23","game_stage":"9","question":"141÷3+96","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:43"},
{"history_id":"3200","user_id":"25","game_stage":"10","question":"87÷(58÷2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:47"},
{"history_id":"3201","user_id":"12","game_stage":"11","question":"(276+91)x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":367,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":276,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1468,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":367,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":367,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":276,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1468,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":367,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:47"},
{"history_id":"3202","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"193+45÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":238,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:06:54"},
{"history_id":"3203","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"170÷85+174","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:02"},
{"history_id":"3204","user_id":"19","game_stage":"9","question":"32x1-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:10"},
{"history_id":"3205","user_id":"9","game_stage":"9","question":"181+108÷36","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":289,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:16"},
{"history_id":"3206","user_id":"6","game_stage":"8","question":"28÷2-9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:17"},
{"history_id":"3207","user_id":"3","game_stage":"9","question":"174+224÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":112}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":398,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":224}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":398,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:25"},
{"history_id":"3208","user_id":"25","game_stage":"10","question":"(17+199)x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":199}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":199}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":216,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:37"},
{"history_id":"3209","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"89x8-85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":712,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":627,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":712,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:48"},
{"history_id":"3210","user_id":"6","game_stage":"8","question":"108÷54+151","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":151}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:49"},
{"history_id":"3211","user_id":"13","game_stage":"10","question":"411÷(134+3)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":411,\"numB\":137}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":411,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:07:59"},
{"history_id":"3212","user_id":"8","game_stage":"9","question":"161+81x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":729,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":890,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":729}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":242,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":242,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:05"},
{"history_id":"3213","user_id":"28","game_stage":"7","question":"161÷7x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:07"},
{"history_id":"3214","user_id":"7","game_stage":"11","question":"3x(3+159)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":159}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":486,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":162}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":159}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":486,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":162}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:10"},
{"history_id":"3215","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"71-18-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:11"},
{"history_id":"3216","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"69x8+42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":594,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":552,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":594,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":552,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:18"},
{"history_id":"3217","user_id":"11","game_stage":"10","question":"615÷(188+17)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":615,\"numB\":205}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":615,\"numB\":205}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:19"},
{"history_id":"3218","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"116÷29-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:25"},
{"history_id":"3219","user_id":"3","game_stage":"9","question":"264+295÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":269,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":295}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:26"},
{"history_id":"3220","user_id":"9","game_stage":"9","question":"254-26x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":208}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":208}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:27"},
{"history_id":"3221","user_id":"19","game_stage":"9","question":"12+119÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":119}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:27"},
{"history_id":"3222","user_id":"12","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c69\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u5272160\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u527253\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"9x(160+53)","userAns_obj":"(160+53)x9","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:28"},
{"history_id":"3223","user_id":"24","game_stage":"8","question":"140+42÷21","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:37"},
{"history_id":"3224","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"185÷37-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":147,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:47"},
{"history_id":"3225","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"72÷12÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:48"},
{"history_id":"3226","user_id":"21","game_stage":"8","question":"77-85÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:08:55"},
{"history_id":"3227","user_id":"26","game_stage":"8","question":"33÷3+58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:02"},
{"history_id":"3228","user_id":"14","game_stage":"9","question":"106÷2-18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:08"},
{"history_id":"3229","user_id":"28","game_stage":"7","question":"223+150+139","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":373,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":223,\"numB\":150}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":373,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":373,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":223,\"numB\":150}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":373,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:14"},
{"history_id":"3230","user_id":"19","game_stage":"9","question":"8+100÷50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:16"},
{"history_id":"3231","user_id":"7","game_stage":"11","question":"(101+125)÷113","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":113}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":113}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:18"},
{"history_id":"3232","user_id":"8","game_stage":"9","question":"244+29x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":261,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":505,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":244,\"numB\":261}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":273,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":244,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2457,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:20"},
{"history_id":"3233","user_id":"5","game_stage":"6","question":"84x8x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":672,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2016,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":672,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:22"},
{"history_id":"3234","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"36-27÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:22"},
{"history_id":"3235","user_id":"25","game_stage":"11","question":"1x(266-124)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":124}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":142}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":124}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":142}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:23"},
{"history_id":"3236","user_id":"13","game_stage":"10","question":"1208÷(171-20)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1208,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1208,\"numB\":171}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:32"},
{"history_id":"3237","user_id":"3","game_stage":"9","question":"57+111x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1332,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1389,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":1332}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2016,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:36"},
{"history_id":"3238","user_id":"11","game_stage":"10","question":"(114+39)x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1071,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1071,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:37"},
{"history_id":"3239","user_id":"24","game_stage":"8","question":"69x9+186","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":621,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":807,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":621,\"numB\":186}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":75155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":195}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:09:56"},
{"history_id":"3240","user_id":"26","game_stage":"8","question":"138+152÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:02"},
{"history_id":"3241","user_id":"7","game_stage":"11","question":"(44+174)x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":174}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":174}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:04"},
{"history_id":"3242","user_id":"16","game_stage":"10","question":"6x(35+61)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":96}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":271,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":210,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:08"},
{"history_id":"3243","user_id":"6","game_stage":"9","question":"176+115x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1610,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1786,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":1610}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":291,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":115}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4074,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":291,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:08"},
{"history_id":"3244","user_id":"11","game_stage":"10","question":"(147-76)÷71","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":76}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":76}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":71}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:09"},
{"history_id":"3245","user_id":"18","game_stage":"6","question":"199+50-92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":249,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:20"},
{"history_id":"3246","user_id":"21","game_stage":"9","question":"59+38x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":418,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":477,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":418}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1067,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:23"},
{"history_id":"3247","user_id":"24","game_stage":"8","question":"27+18x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":117,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:28"},
{"history_id":"3248","user_id":"10","game_stage":"7","question":"239+82-287","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":321,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":321,\"numB\":287}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":321,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":321,\"numB\":287}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:33"},
{"history_id":"3249","user_id":"25","game_stage":"11","question":"(230-73)x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1099,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":157,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1099,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":157,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:38"},
{"history_id":"3250","user_id":"14","game_stage":"9","question":"797-56x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":728,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":797,\"numB\":728}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":728,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":797,\"numB\":728}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:44"},
{"history_id":"3251","user_id":"9","game_stage":"10","question":"1x(101+94)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":195}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":195}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:44"},
{"history_id":"3252","user_id":"26","game_stage":"8","question":"86-166÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:51"},
{"history_id":"3253","user_id":"19","game_stage":"10","question":"104÷(39÷3)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:58"},
{"history_id":"3254","user_id":"18","game_stage":"6","question":"98÷49x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:10:58"},
{"history_id":"3255","user_id":"17","game_stage":"4","question":"86÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:07"},
{"history_id":"3256","user_id":"24","game_stage":"8","question":"187÷17-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:09"},
{"history_id":"3257","user_id":"9","game_stage":"10","question":"774÷(172÷2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":774,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":774,\"numB\":86}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:18"},
{"history_id":"3258","user_id":"10","game_stage":"7","question":"209÷19÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":209,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":209,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:27"},
{"history_id":"3259","user_id":"6","game_stage":"9","question":"38x9+198","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":342,\"numB\":198}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":342,\"numB\":198}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:30"},
{"history_id":"3260","user_id":"18","game_stage":"6","question":"17-5-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:38"},
{"history_id":"3261","user_id":"25","game_stage":"11","question":"(168-38)÷65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:40"},
{"history_id":"3262","user_id":"19","game_stage":"10","question":"50÷(65÷13)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:44"},
{"history_id":"3263","user_id":"24","game_stage":"8","question":"70x4+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":372,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:48"},
{"history_id":"3264","user_id":"3","game_stage":"9","question":"85÷5+184","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":184}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":199,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":184}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:50"},
{"history_id":"3265","user_id":"21","game_stage":"9","question":"75+296÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":371,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":296}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":371,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:53"},
{"history_id":"3266","user_id":"26","game_stage":"8","question":"33x5+86","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":86}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":86}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:11:55"},
{"history_id":"3267","user_id":"17","game_stage":"4","question":"166÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:01"},
{"history_id":"3268","user_id":"9","game_stage":"10","question":"(103-16)÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:06"},
{"history_id":"3269","user_id":"11","game_stage":"11","question":"6x(35+113)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":888,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":148}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":948,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":158}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:06"},
{"history_id":"3270","user_id":"14","game_stage":"10","question":"91-(154-90)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":90}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":90}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:09"},
{"history_id":"3271","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"147+78x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":858,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1005,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":858}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":858,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1005,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":858}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:25"},
{"history_id":"3272","user_id":"19","game_stage":"10","question":"(79+164)x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":164}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":164}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:33"},
{"history_id":"3273","user_id":"8","game_stage":"9","question":"233+18÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":235,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:36"},
{"history_id":"3274","user_id":"17","game_stage":"4","question":"12x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:37"},
{"history_id":"3275","user_id":"13","game_stage":"10","question":"1160÷(181+109)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":290,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1160,\"numB\":290}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":290,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1160,\"numB\":290}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:38"},
{"history_id":"3276","user_id":"6","game_stage":"9","question":"43-93÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:12:47"},
{"history_id":"3277","user_id":"11","game_stage":"11","question":"14x(227-136)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":227,\"numB\":136}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1274,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":227,\"numB\":136}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:11"},
{"history_id":"3278","user_id":"14","game_stage":"10","question":"(86-48)÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:13"},
{"history_id":"3279","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"85x8-56","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":624,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":680,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":624,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":680,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:22"},
{"history_id":"3280","user_id":"19","game_stage":"10","question":"(189+108)x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":594,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":594,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:29"},
{"history_id":"3281","user_id":"13","game_stage":"10","question":"(128-66)÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:36"},
{"history_id":"3282","user_id":"14","game_stage":"10","question":"(82-50)÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:39"},
{"history_id":"3283","user_id":"11","game_stage":"11","question":"50÷(295÷59)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":295,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:47"},
{"history_id":"3284","user_id":"30","game_stage":"8","question":"33-108÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:52"},
{"history_id":"3285","user_id":"17","game_stage":"4","question":"106÷53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:13:54"},
{"history_id":"3286","user_id":"6","game_stage":"9","question":"224+55÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:14:01"},
{"history_id":"3287","user_id":"13","game_stage":"10","question":"(185-20)÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:14:21"},
{"history_id":"3288","user_id":"11","game_stage":"11","question":"(65÷5)÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-25 11:14:34"},
{"history_id":"3289","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"142÷2+259","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":259}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":330,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":259}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:10"},
{"history_id":"3290","user_id":"60","game_stage":"10","question":"103-(86-22)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:27"},
{"history_id":"3291","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"196-12+2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:29"},
{"history_id":"3292","user_id":"74","game_stage":"8","question":"30÷10+124","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":124}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":124}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:37"},
{"history_id":"3293","user_id":"65","game_stage":"10","question":"8x(155-41)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":912,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":155}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1999,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":1240,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:38"},
{"history_id":"3294","user_id":"63","game_stage":"8","question":"50+75x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":225}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":375,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:40"},
{"history_id":"3295","user_id":"72","game_stage":"9","question":"93x1+73","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":73}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":73}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:41"},
{"history_id":"3296","user_id":"67","game_stage":"7","question":"200-71+65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":71}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:42"},
{"history_id":"3297","user_id":"71","game_stage":"7","question":"113-75-34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":34}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:45"},
{"history_id":"3298","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"146-81+16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:52"},
{"history_id":"3299","user_id":"77","game_stage":"8","question":"148÷37+80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:53"},
{"history_id":"3300","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"21-14+183","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":183}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":183}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:58"},
{"history_id":"3301","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"143÷13+43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:59"},
{"history_id":"3302","user_id":"76","game_stage":"8","question":"37+33x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:35:59"},
{"history_id":"3303","user_id":"63","game_stage":"8","question":"27x10+31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":301,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":301,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:04"},
{"history_id":"3304","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"1292-84x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1292,\"numB\":1260}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":32,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1292,\"numB\":1260}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:04"},
{"history_id":"3305","user_id":"59","game_stage":"8","question":"84÷4+119","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":119}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":119}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:08"},
{"history_id":"3306","user_id":"65","game_stage":"10","question":"7x(51+55)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":742,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":106}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":357,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":412,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":357,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:16"},
{"history_id":"3307","user_id":"67","game_stage":"7","question":"207÷3÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":207,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":207,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:22"},
{"history_id":"3308","user_id":"74","game_stage":"8","question":"94-192÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:24"},
{"history_id":"3309","user_id":"84","game_stage":"7","question":"127-49+64","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:24"},
{"history_id":"3310","user_id":"86","game_stage":"8","question":"62x4+57","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":248,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":305,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":248,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:24"},
{"history_id":"3311","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"1x6x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:26"},
{"history_id":"3312","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"105+8÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:29"},
{"history_id":"3313","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"60+4x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6768,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:30"},
{"history_id":"3314","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"48x6-30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":258,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:33"},
{"history_id":"3315","user_id":"71","game_stage":"7","question":"22+116+52","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":52}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":52}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:34"},
{"history_id":"3316","user_id":"80","game_stage":"9","question":"39+138÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:34"},
{"history_id":"3317","user_id":"76","game_stage":"8","question":"61+59x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":649,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":710,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":649}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:41"},
{"history_id":"3318","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"48÷8-4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:42"},
{"history_id":"3319","user_id":"75","game_stage":"8","question":"10x11+55","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":55}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:43"},
{"history_id":"3320","user_id":"72","game_stage":"9","question":"115÷5-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:46"},
{"history_id":"3321","user_id":"79","game_stage":"6","question":"30+47+102","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":102}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":102}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:51"},
{"history_id":"3322","user_id":"65","game_stage":"10","question":"4x(141+1)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":142,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":568,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":142}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":564,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":565,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":564,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:51"},
{"history_id":"3323","user_id":"63","game_stage":"8","question":"53x11-31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":583,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":583,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":583,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":583,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:52"},
{"history_id":"3324","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"164-10-54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":164,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:36:56"},
{"history_id":"3325","user_id":"60","game_stage":"10","question":"3x(111-12)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:00"},
{"history_id":"3326","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"68+86x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":860,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":928,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":860}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:02"},
{"history_id":"3327","user_id":"84","game_stage":"7","question":"120x1x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:04"},
{"history_id":"3328","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"40x5+142","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":142}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":142}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:05"},
{"history_id":"3329","user_id":"59","game_stage":"8","question":"65x12+102","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":780,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":882,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":780,\"numB\":102}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":780,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":882,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":780,\"numB\":102}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:11"},
{"history_id":"3330","user_id":"82","game_stage":"8","question":"90+64x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":448,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":538,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":448}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1078,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:17"},
{"history_id":"3331","user_id":"74","game_stage":"8","question":"65+80x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1040,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":1040}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1040,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":1040}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:18"},
{"history_id":"3332","user_id":"75","game_stage":"8","question":"53x4-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:20"},
{"history_id":"3333","user_id":"77","game_stage":"8","question":"105÷35-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:21"},
{"history_id":"3334","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"60x5+43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":343,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":300,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":343,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":300,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:25"},
{"history_id":"3335","user_id":"86","game_stage":"8","question":"57-194÷97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:30"},
{"history_id":"3336","user_id":"87","game_stage":"7","question":"141-53-85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:33"},
{"history_id":"3337","user_id":"59","game_stage":"8","question":"62÷2-28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:36"},
{"history_id":"3338","user_id":"60","game_stage":"10","question":"(79-50)x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:37"},
{"history_id":"3339","user_id":"75","game_stage":"8","question":"72÷9+188","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":188}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":188}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:40"},
{"history_id":"3340","user_id":"82","game_stage":"8","question":"25÷5+101","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":101}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":101}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:43"},
{"history_id":"3341","user_id":"77","game_stage":"8","question":"150÷25-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:48"},
{"history_id":"3342","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"72+49÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":121,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:49"},
{"history_id":"3343","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"431-66x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":431,\"numB\":396}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":431,\"numB\":396}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:52"},
{"history_id":"3344","user_id":"84","game_stage":"7","question":"297÷3x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:37:55"},
{"history_id":"3345","user_id":"63","game_stage":"8","question":"696-55x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":660,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":696,\"numB\":660}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":660,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":696,\"numB\":660}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:02"},
{"history_id":"3346","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"98-6x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":552,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:09"},
{"history_id":"3347","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"328-31x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":328,\"numB\":310}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":328,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2970,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:10"},
{"history_id":"3348","user_id":"71","game_stage":"7","question":"61x7x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":427,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4697,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":427,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4697,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:12"},
{"history_id":"3349","user_id":"86","game_stage":"8","question":"171÷3+64","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":121,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:16"},
{"history_id":"3350","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"3x16x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:17"},
{"history_id":"3351","user_id":"59","game_stage":"8","question":"696-55x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":660,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":696,\"numB\":660}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":641,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":696,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7692,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":641,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:19"},
{"history_id":"3352","user_id":"82","game_stage":"8","question":"72-17x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":68}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:21"},
{"history_id":"3353","user_id":"67","game_stage":"7","question":"24x13÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:22"},
{"history_id":"3354","user_id":"80","game_stage":"9","question":"63-285÷95","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":285,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:23"},
{"history_id":"3355","user_id":"87","game_stage":"7","question":"270÷5÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:25"},
{"history_id":"3356","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"75÷5+139","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:38"},
{"history_id":"3357","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"40+23x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":115}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:42"},
{"history_id":"3358","user_id":"76","game_stage":"8","question":"42+98÷49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:43"},
{"history_id":"3359","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"218+232÷116","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":450,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":232}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":450,\"numB\":116}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:49"},
{"history_id":"3360","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"79-88÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:51"},
{"history_id":"3361","user_id":"82","game_stage":"8","question":"49x6-250","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":250}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":294,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":250}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:38:58"},
{"history_id":"3362","user_id":"60","game_stage":"11","question":"798÷(82+32)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":32}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":798,\"numB\":114}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":114,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":32}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":798,\"numB\":114}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:00"},
{"history_id":"3363","user_id":"65","game_stage":"10","question":"4440÷(180+190)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":190}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4440,\"numB\":370}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":370,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":190}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4440,\"numB\":370}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:01"},
{"history_id":"3364","user_id":"59","game_stage":"8","question":"16x11+156","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":332,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":156}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":332,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:04"},
{"history_id":"3365","user_id":"64","game_stage":"7","question":"63÷3x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:05"},
{"history_id":"3366","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"274÷2+272","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":409,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":272}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":409,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":272}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:05"},
{"history_id":"3367","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"6x6-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:06"},
{"history_id":"3368","user_id":"80","game_stage":"9","question":"251+98÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":265,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":265,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":251,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:06"},
{"history_id":"3369","user_id":"71","game_stage":"7","question":"58x2÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:18"},
{"history_id":"3370","user_id":"72","game_stage":"9","question":"120+253÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":253,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":253,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:21"},
{"history_id":"3371","user_id":"68","game_stage":"8","question":"77+55x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":55}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:28"},
{"history_id":"3372","user_id":"67","game_stage":"8","question":"42÷14+54","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:34"},
{"history_id":"3373","user_id":"77","game_stage":"9","question":"105+186÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":186}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:42"},
{"history_id":"3374","user_id":"63","game_stage":"9","question":"260+279÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":279,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":291,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":279,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":291,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:44"},
{"history_id":"3375","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"87-9x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":456,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:44"},
{"history_id":"3376","user_id":"82","game_stage":"8","question":"4÷2+43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:45"},
{"history_id":"3377","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"165÷55+4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:39:45"},
{"history_id":"3378","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"92-87÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:00"},
{"history_id":"3379","user_id":"65","game_stage":"10","question":"1668÷(7+132)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":132}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1668,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":132}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1668,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:00"},
{"history_id":"3380","user_id":"86","game_stage":"9","question":"81+58x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:10"},
{"history_id":"3381","user_id":"67","game_stage":"8","question":"28-177÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:11"},
{"history_id":"3382","user_id":"79","game_stage":"7","question":"158+295+240","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":453,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":295}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":693,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":453,\"numB\":240}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":453,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":295}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":693,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":453,\"numB\":240}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:11"},
{"history_id":"3383","user_id":"60","game_stage":"11","question":"287÷(203+84)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":287,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":287,\"numB\":287}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":287,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":84}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":287,\"numB\":287}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:15"},
{"history_id":"3384","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"9+12x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":48}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:18"},
{"history_id":"3385","user_id":"63","game_stage":"9","question":"14÷7-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:20"},
{"history_id":"3386","user_id":"74","game_stage":"9","question":"57+184÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":214,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:30"},
{"history_id":"3387","user_id":"84","game_stage":"8","question":"145+13x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1738,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:31"},
{"history_id":"3388","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"70÷35+22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:32"},
{"history_id":"3389","user_id":"67","game_stage":"8","question":"160+138÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:35"},
{"history_id":"3390","user_id":"76","game_stage":"8","question":"159÷53+152","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":152}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":155,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":152}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:43"},
{"history_id":"3391","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"70x15-457","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1050,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":593,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1050,\"numB\":457}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1050,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":593,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1050,\"numB\":457}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:54"},
{"history_id":"3392","user_id":"63","game_stage":"9","question":"56÷4-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:40:55"},
{"history_id":"3393","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"116+147÷49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":263,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":147}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:01"},
{"history_id":"3394","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"635-49x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":588,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":635,\"numB\":588}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":590,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":635,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":590,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:04"},
{"history_id":"3395","user_id":"74","game_stage":"9","question":"1x4+227","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":227}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":231,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":227}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:06"},
{"history_id":"3396","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"13+141x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":1128}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":154,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:06"},
{"history_id":"3397","user_id":"84","game_stage":"8","question":"70+67x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":338,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":268}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":548,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:09"},
{"history_id":"3398","user_id":"75","game_stage":"9","question":"120÷2+294","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":294}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":294}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:11"},
{"history_id":"3399","user_id":"68","game_stage":"8","question":"64x5+187","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":507,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":320,\"numB\":187}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":507,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":320,\"numB\":187}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:13"},
{"history_id":"3400","user_id":"86","game_stage":"9","question":"157-236÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":157,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":157,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:14"},
{"history_id":"3401","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"41-129÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:16"},
{"history_id":"3402","user_id":"77","game_stage":"9","question":"7+54÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:17"},
{"history_id":"3403","user_id":"87","game_stage":"7","question":"9+116-75","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":116}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:17"},
{"history_id":"3404","user_id":"78","game_stage":"9","question":"61x4+39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":244,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":283,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":244,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":244,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":283,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":244,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:26"},
{"history_id":"3405","user_id":"76","game_stage":"8","question":"438-42x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":378,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":438,\"numB\":378}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":438,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3564,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":396,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:26"},
{"history_id":"3406","user_id":"82","game_stage":"9","question":"108x7+267","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":756,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1023,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":756,\"numB\":267}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":756,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1023,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":756,\"numB\":267}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:38"},
{"history_id":"3407","user_id":"79","game_stage":"7","question":"85x16x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1360,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8160,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1360,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":96,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":860,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":96}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:44"},
{"history_id":"3408","user_id":"65","game_stage":"10","question":"156÷(130÷5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:45"},
{"history_id":"3409","user_id":"64","game_stage":"8","question":"152+126÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":278,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":126}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:46"},
{"history_id":"3410","user_id":"74","game_stage":"9","question":"33-64÷16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:49"},
{"history_id":"3411","user_id":"72","game_stage":"10","question":"76÷(66-28)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:51"},
{"history_id":"3412","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"39-22÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:53"},
{"history_id":"3413","user_id":"59","game_stage":"9","question":"146x12+29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1752,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1781,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1752,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1752,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1781,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1752,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:56"},
{"history_id":"3414","user_id":"75","game_stage":"9","question":"79x13-941","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1027,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1027,\"numB\":941}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":941,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":941}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05mis06","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:41:58"},
{"history_id":"3415","user_id":"68","game_stage":"8","question":"947-74x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":888,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":947,\"numB\":888}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":888,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":947,\"numB\":888}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:05"},
{"history_id":"3416","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"177+76x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":532,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":709,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":532}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":532,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":704,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":532}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:08"},
{"history_id":"3417","user_id":"84","game_stage":"8","question":"46+42x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:12"},
{"history_id":"3418","user_id":"76","game_stage":"8","question":"22-152÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:14"},
{"history_id":"3419","user_id":"60","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86116\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86154\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e865\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"5x(116+154)","userAns_obj":"(116+154)x5","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:20"},
{"history_id":"3420","user_id":"67","game_stage":"9","question":"213+25x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":438,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":225}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":438,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":225}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:21"},
{"history_id":"3421","user_id":"77","game_stage":"9","question":"136x16+295","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2471,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2176,\"numB\":295}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2471,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2176,\"numB\":295}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:25"},
{"history_id":"3422","user_id":"79","game_stage":"7","question":"206÷2÷103","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":103}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":103}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:29"},
{"history_id":"3423","user_id":"86","game_stage":"9","question":"114x13+4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1482,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1486,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1482,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1482,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1486,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1482,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:29"},
{"history_id":"3424","user_id":"63","game_stage":"10","question":"1x(115-61)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:35"},
{"history_id":"3425","user_id":"87","game_stage":"7","question":"114÷19x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:36"},
{"history_id":"3426","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"51-77÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:37"},
{"history_id":"3427","user_id":"68","game_stage":"8","question":"63+80x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":623,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":560}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":623,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":560}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:37"},
{"history_id":"3428","user_id":"74","game_stage":"9","question":"203+60x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":780,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":983,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":780}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":780,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":983,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":780}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:38"},
{"history_id":"3429","user_id":"75","game_stage":"9","question":"268÷67-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":268,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:44"},
{"history_id":"3430","user_id":"76","game_stage":"8","question":"364-51x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":306,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":364,\"numB\":306}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":364,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1878,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":313,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:44"},
{"history_id":"3431","user_id":"71","game_stage":"8","question":"40x2+125","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":125}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":125}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":127}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:49"},
{"history_id":"3432","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"71+87÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":87}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:54"},
{"history_id":"3433","user_id":"84","game_stage":"8","question":"53x10-141","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":530,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":389,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":530,\"numB\":141}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":530,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":389,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":530,\"numB\":141}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:42:55"},
{"history_id":"3434","user_id":"59","game_stage":"9","question":"234-18x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":216}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":216}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:03"},
{"history_id":"3435","user_id":"70","game_stage":"6","question":"152-41-42","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":42}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":178,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":42}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:05"},
{"history_id":"3436","user_id":"82","game_stage":"9","question":"296-29x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":203}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":267,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1669,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:06"},
{"history_id":"3437","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"115÷23+187","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":187}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":187}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:07"},
{"history_id":"3438","user_id":"78","game_stage":"10","question":"11x(86+110)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":110}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":196}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":110}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":196}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:09"},
{"history_id":"3439","user_id":"67","game_stage":"9","question":"99-259÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:14"},
{"history_id":"3440","user_id":"72","game_stage":"10","question":"3072÷(97+159)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":159}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3072,\"numB\":256}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":159}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3072,\"numB\":256}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:16"},
{"history_id":"3441","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"72x12+94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":864,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":958,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":864,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":864,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":958,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":864,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:17"},
{"history_id":"3442","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"80÷40+93","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:18"},
{"history_id":"3443","user_id":"84","game_stage":"8","question":"74÷37-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:26"},
{"history_id":"3444","user_id":"75","game_stage":"9","question":"102x7+174","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":714,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":888,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":714,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":714,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":888,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":714,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:28"},
{"history_id":"3445","user_id":"63","game_stage":"10","question":"(89-75)x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":169,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:30"},
{"history_id":"3446","user_id":"64","game_stage":"8","question":"48+128÷32","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":32}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":128}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":32}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:31"},
{"history_id":"3447","user_id":"65","game_stage":"9","question":"104x14+11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1456,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1467,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1456,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2600,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:34"},
{"history_id":"3448","user_id":"71","game_stage":"8","question":"71x7+128","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":497,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":625,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":497,\"numB\":128}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":497,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":625,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":497,\"numB\":128}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:35"},
{"history_id":"3449","user_id":"59","game_stage":"9","question":"296÷148-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":148}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":296,\"numB\":148}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:37"},
{"history_id":"3450","user_id":"87","game_stage":"7","question":"125x10÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1250,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1250,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:39"},
{"history_id":"3451","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"32x4-123","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":123}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":123}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:46"},
{"history_id":"3452","user_id":"79","game_stage":"7","question":"86x11x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":946,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":946,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":14190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":165}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:47"},
{"history_id":"3453","user_id":"78","game_stage":"10","question":"(129-80)x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:50"},
{"history_id":"3454","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"61x1-41","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":41}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":41}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:53"},
{"history_id":"3455","user_id":"63","game_stage":"10","question":"23-(94-86)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":0}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:55"},
{"history_id":"3456","user_id":"70","game_stage":"6","question":"5+139-110","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":139}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":110}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:43:57"},
{"history_id":"3457","user_id":"82","game_stage":"9","question":"278÷2-24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":139,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:04"},
{"history_id":"3458","user_id":"74","game_stage":"10","question":"55÷(22÷2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:06"},
{"history_id":"3459","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"192+54x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":864,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1056,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":864}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":246,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":246,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:07"},
{"history_id":"3460","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"374-39x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":374,\"numB\":351}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":315,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":374,\"numB\":39}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2815,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":315,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:15"},
{"history_id":"3461","user_id":"83","game_stage":"8","question":"70x8+70","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":630,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":560,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":630,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":560,\"numB\":70}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:15"},
{"history_id":"3462","user_id":"72","game_stage":"10","question":"(106+183)x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":183}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2023,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":289,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":283,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":183}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1981,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":283,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:15"},
{"history_id":"3463","user_id":"77","game_stage":"9","question":"106-138÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:17"},
{"history_id":"3464","user_id":"71","game_stage":"8","question":"27÷3-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":0}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:20"},
{"history_id":"3465","user_id":"64","game_stage":"8","question":"145÷29+106","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":106}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":106}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:22"},
{"history_id":"3466","user_id":"78","game_stage":"10","question":"115-(114-20)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":115,\"numB\":124}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:25"},
{"history_id":"3467","user_id":"67","game_stage":"9","question":"89+66x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":551,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":462}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":541,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":462}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:28"},
{"history_id":"3468","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"58-12÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:28"},
{"history_id":"3469","user_id":"63","game_stage":"10","question":"(71-13)x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:28"},
{"history_id":"3470","user_id":"80","game_stage":"10","question":"1089÷(197-98)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1089,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1089,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:32"},
{"history_id":"3471","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"96x13+172","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1248,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1248,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:34"},
{"history_id":"3472","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"46-38÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":38}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:40"},
{"history_id":"3473","user_id":"59","game_stage":"10","question":"33÷(165÷55)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":165}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01mis04","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:42"},
{"history_id":"3474","user_id":"65","game_stage":"9","question":"272+256÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":336,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":528,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":256}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":528,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:44"},
{"history_id":"3475","user_id":"68","game_stage":"9","question":"66+298÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":149}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":364,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":298}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":364,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:46"},
{"history_id":"3476","user_id":"64","game_stage":"8","question":"162÷54-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:47"},
{"history_id":"3477","user_id":"60","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c69\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u5272150\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u52722\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"9x(150+2)","userAns_obj":"(150+2)x9","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:51"},
{"history_id":"3478","user_id":"78","game_stage":"10","question":"43-(24-2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:51"},
{"history_id":"3479","user_id":"75","game_stage":"10","question":"3x(51+65)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":116}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:52"},
{"history_id":"3480","user_id":"74","game_stage":"10","question":"(2+103)÷35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":103}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":103}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:53"},
{"history_id":"3481","user_id":"72","game_stage":"10","question":"340÷(85-17)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":340,\"numB\":68}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":340,\"numB\":68}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:44:56"},
{"history_id":"3482","user_id":"77","game_stage":"9","question":"86+143÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:00"},
{"history_id":"3483","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"49x4-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:10"},
{"history_id":"3484","user_id":"64","game_stage":"8","question":"194÷97+162","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":162}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":194,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":162}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:11"},
{"history_id":"3485","user_id":"70","game_stage":"6","question":"20x7x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:15"},
{"history_id":"3486","user_id":"79","game_stage":"8","question":"5x7+169","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":169}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":169}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:17"},
{"history_id":"3487","user_id":"82","game_stage":"9","question":"100÷4-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:18"},
{"history_id":"3488","user_id":"87","game_stage":"8","question":"81÷9+192","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":192}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":192}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:20"},
{"history_id":"3489","user_id":"67","game_stage":"9","question":"201-12x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":120}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":201,\"numB\":120}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:25"},
{"history_id":"3490","user_id":"80","game_stage":"10","question":"1881÷(117+92)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1881,\"numB\":209}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1881,\"numB\":209}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:25"},
{"history_id":"3491","user_id":"86","game_stage":"10","question":"525÷(103-28)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":525,\"numB\":75}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":525,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:25"},
{"history_id":"3492","user_id":"63","game_stage":"10","question":"(104-46)x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":696,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:34"},
{"history_id":"3493","user_id":"75","game_stage":"10","question":"12÷(90÷30)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":30}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":30}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:38"},
{"history_id":"3494","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"270+144x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1872,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":2142,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":1872}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":414,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5382,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":414,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:41"},
{"history_id":"3495","user_id":"72","game_stage":"10","question":"(196-94)÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:42"},
{"history_id":"3496","user_id":"84","game_stage":"9","question":"91x14+43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1274,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1317,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1274,\"numB\":43}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1274,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1317,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1274,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:44"},
{"history_id":"3497","user_id":"85","game_stage":"8","question":"49x12-221","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":588,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":367,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":588,\"numB\":221}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":588,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":367,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":588,\"numB\":221}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:49"},
{"history_id":"3498","user_id":"59","game_stage":"10","question":"(157+129)÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":157,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":286,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":286,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":157,\"numB\":129}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":286,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:50"},
{"history_id":"3499","user_id":"65","game_stage":"9","question":"19x4+35","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":741,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:52"},
{"history_id":"3500","user_id":"71","game_stage":"8","question":"44x6-27","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":264,\"numB\":27}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2904,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2877,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2904,\"numB\":27}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:53"},
{"history_id":"3501","user_id":"68","game_stage":"9","question":"128+45x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":675,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":803,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":675}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2595,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:55"},
{"history_id":"3502","user_id":"83","game_stage":"9","question":"90x11+123","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":990,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":990,\"numB\":123}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":990,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":990,\"numB\":123}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:45:56"},
{"history_id":"3503","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"226÷113+294","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":294}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":294}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:02"},
{"history_id":"3504","user_id":"76","game_stage":"8","question":"173+9÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:02"},
{"history_id":"3505","user_id":"74","game_stage":"10","question":"517÷(188÷4)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":517,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":517,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:04"},
{"history_id":"3506","user_id":"87","game_stage":"8","question":"360-31x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":341,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":360,\"numB\":341}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":329,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":360,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3619,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":329,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:08"},
{"history_id":"3507","user_id":"80","game_stage":"10","question":"(185+21)x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2678,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2678,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:13"},
{"history_id":"3508","user_id":"75","game_stage":"10","question":"(139+50)÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:28"},
{"history_id":"3509","user_id":"84","game_stage":"9","question":"150÷75-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:33"},
{"history_id":"3510","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"83x11+70","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":913,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":983,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":913,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":891,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":961,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":891,\"numB\":70}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:36"},
{"history_id":"3511","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"271+4x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":271,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":271,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:42"},
{"history_id":"3512","user_id":"78","game_stage":"11","question":"12x(250-78)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2064,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":250,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2064,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:43"},
{"history_id":"3513","user_id":"86","game_stage":"10","question":"3x(14+40)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":54}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":54}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:46"},
{"history_id":"3514","user_id":"63","game_stage":"11","question":"341÷(155÷5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":341,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":341,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:47"},
{"history_id":"3515","user_id":"67","game_stage":"10","question":"98-(167-95)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:49"},
{"history_id":"3516","user_id":"87","game_stage":"8","question":"87x2-51","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":51}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":51}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:50"},
{"history_id":"3517","user_id":"75","game_stage":"10","question":"(66-65)x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":65}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:55"},
{"history_id":"3518","user_id":"59","game_stage":"10","question":"86-(94-37)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:46:57"},
{"history_id":"3519","user_id":"68","game_stage":"9","question":"86x14+133","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1337,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1204,\"numB\":133}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1224,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1357,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1224,\"numB\":133}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:03"},
{"history_id":"3520","user_id":"72","game_stage":"11","question":"390÷(145-15)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":390,\"numB\":130}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":130,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":390,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:07"},
{"history_id":"3521","user_id":"83","game_stage":"9","question":"62-175÷25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:08"},
{"history_id":"3522","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"55÷11+128","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":128}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":128}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:09"},
{"history_id":"3523","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"53x11+175","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":583,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":758,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":583,\"numB\":175}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":583,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":758,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":583,\"numB\":175}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:12"},
{"history_id":"3524","user_id":"79","game_stage":"8","question":"185÷37-2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:14"},
{"history_id":"3525","user_id":"77","game_stage":"10","question":"36-(95-69)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":26}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:15"},
{"history_id":"3526","user_id":"84","game_stage":"9","question":"138÷23+92","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":92}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":92}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:22"},
{"history_id":"3527","user_id":"67","game_stage":"10","question":"(148-58)÷18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:33"},
{"history_id":"3528","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"94÷2-3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:47:53"},
{"history_id":"3529","user_id":"82","game_stage":"10","question":"203÷(161+42)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":203}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":203,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":203}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:49:00"},
{"history_id":"3530","user_id":"72","game_stage":"11","question":"(208+55)÷263","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":263,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":263}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":263,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":208,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":263,\"numB\":263}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:51:48"},
{"history_id":"3531","user_id":"64","game_stage":"9","question":"93÷31+286","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":286}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":289,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":286}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:52:00"},
{"history_id":"3532","user_id":"83","game_stage":"9","question":"62x5+276","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":586,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":310,\"numB\":276}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":300,\"numB\":276}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 10:52:00"},
{"history_id":"3533","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"272÷8-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:02:19"},
{"history_id":"3534","user_id":"63","game_stage":"11","question":"(230÷23)÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":230,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:02:22"},
{"history_id":"3535","user_id":"83","game_stage":"9","question":"118x6-206","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":708,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":502,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":708,\"numB\":206}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":708,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":118,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":502,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":708,\"numB\":206}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:02:53"},
{"history_id":"3536","user_id":"63","game_stage":"11","question":"1422÷(55+182)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1422,\"numB\":237}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":237,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":182}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1422,\"numB\":237}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:02:58"},
{"history_id":"3537","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"72-253÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":253,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":253,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:03:02"},
{"history_id":"3538","user_id":"85","game_stage":"9","question":"206+146x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":292,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":498,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":292}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":146}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":704,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":352,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:03:19"},
{"history_id":"3539","user_id":"67","game_stage":"10","question":"28÷(184÷46)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:03:26"},
{"history_id":"3540","user_id":"78","game_stage":"11","question":"(119+14)x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":798,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":798,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:03:33"},
{"history_id":"3541","user_id":"78","game_stage":"11","question":"11-(26-24)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:03:59"},
{"history_id":"3542","user_id":"66","game_stage":"9","question":"180+60x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":780,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":780}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":780,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":780}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:04"},
{"history_id":"3543","user_id":"69","game_stage":"8","question":"51÷17+174","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:05"},
{"history_id":"3544","user_id":"72","game_stage":"11","question":"252-(205-35)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":170}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":170,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":170}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:08"},
{"history_id":"3545","user_id":"68","game_stage":"9","question":"106x6+80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":636,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":716,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":636,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":636,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":716,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":636,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:10"},
{"history_id":"3546","user_id":"59","game_stage":"11","question":"48÷(9÷3)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:10"},
{"history_id":"3547","user_id":"76","game_stage":"9","question":"169÷13+193","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":193}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":193}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:15"},
{"history_id":"3548","user_id":"79","game_stage":"8","question":"47x2-76","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":76}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":76}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:15"},
{"history_id":"3549","user_id":"85","game_stage":"9","question":"102x13+201","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1326,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1527,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1326,\"numB\":201}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1326,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1527,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1326,\"numB\":201}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:18"},
{"history_id":"3550","user_id":"77","game_stage":"10","question":"3440÷(163+181)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":181}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3440,\"numB\":344}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":344,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":181}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3440,\"numB\":344}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:26"},
{"history_id":"3551","user_id":"68","game_stage":"9","question":"146-224÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":112}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:49"},
{"history_id":"3552","user_id":"63","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c67\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u5272199\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u527262\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"7x(199+62)","userAns_obj":"(199x7)+62","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:51"},
{"history_id":"3553","user_id":"84","game_stage":"10","question":"22÷(160÷80)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:55"},
{"history_id":"3554","user_id":"83","game_stage":"10","question":"720÷(104-32)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":32}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":720,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":32}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":720,\"numB\":72}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:56"},
{"history_id":"3555","user_id":"86","game_stage":"10","question":"(74-54)÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:56"},
{"history_id":"3556","user_id":"65","game_stage":"11","question":"8x(217-93)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":93}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":992,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":124}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":93}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":992,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":124}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:57"},
{"history_id":"3557","user_id":"75","game_stage":"11","question":"12x(85-1)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1008,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":84}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1274,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":1275,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:04:58"},
{"history_id":"3558","user_id":"76","game_stage":"9","question":"156+111x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":1110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":267,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2670,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:10"},
{"history_id":"3559","user_id":"67","game_stage":"11","question":"13x(191-15)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":176}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":176,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":176}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:15"},
{"history_id":"3560","user_id":"77","game_stage":"10","question":"370÷(111÷3)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":370,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:17"},
{"history_id":"3561","user_id":"78","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c610\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527255\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u527275\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"10x(55+75)","userAns_obj":"(10x55)+75","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:24"},
{"history_id":"3562","user_id":"63","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86174\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8676\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e864\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"4x(174+76)","userAns_obj":"(174+76)x4","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:26"},
{"history_id":"3563","user_id":"66","game_stage":"10","question":"21÷(91÷13)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:26"},
{"history_id":"3564","user_id":"79","game_stage":"8","question":"165+18x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":381,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":216}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":18}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":183,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:26"},
{"history_id":"3565","user_id":"75","game_stage":"11","question":"317÷(100+217)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":317,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":217}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":317,\"numB\":317}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":317,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":217}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":317,\"numB\":317}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:26"},
{"history_id":"3566","user_id":"85","game_stage":"9","question":"147-13x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":670,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:27"},
{"history_id":"3567","user_id":"80","game_stage":"11","question":"3752÷(212+257)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":469,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":257}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3752,\"numB\":469}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":469,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":257}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3752,\"numB\":469}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:32"},
{"history_id":"3568","user_id":"68","game_stage":"9","question":"140÷28-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":28}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:36"},
{"history_id":"3569","user_id":"65","game_stage":"11","question":"(14÷7)÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:36"},
{"history_id":"3570","user_id":"67","game_stage":"11","question":"185-(256-121)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":135}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":121}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":135}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:42"},
{"history_id":"3571","user_id":"87","game_stage":"8","question":"73-9x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":448,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:44"},
{"history_id":"3572","user_id":"59","game_stage":"11","question":"(64÷16)÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:45"},
{"history_id":"3573","user_id":"78","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8642\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8653\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e8611\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"11x(42+53)","userAns_obj":"(42+53)x11","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:48"},
{"history_id":"3574","user_id":"72","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8698\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8617\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e8613\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"13x(98+17)","userAns_obj":"(98+17)x13","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:57"},
{"history_id":"3575","user_id":"69","game_stage":"9","question":"36x14+12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":504,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":516,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":504,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:58"},
{"history_id":"3576","user_id":"76","game_stage":"9","question":"28x15+158","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":578,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":158}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":578,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":158}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:05:59"},
{"history_id":"3577","user_id":"83","game_stage":"10","question":"(175-92)÷83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:04"},
{"history_id":"3578","user_id":"85","game_stage":"9","question":"72-174÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":102,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":102}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:14"},
{"history_id":"3579","user_id":"79","game_stage":"8","question":"149+13x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":52}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":149,\"numB\":52}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:16"},
{"history_id":"3580","user_id":"65","game_stage":"11","question":"(55+26)x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1296,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:25"},
{"history_id":"3581","user_id":"80","game_stage":"11","question":"(196-144)÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:27"},
{"history_id":"3582","user_id":"74","game_stage":"11","question":"2x(162+29)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":382,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":191}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":382,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":191}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:29"},
{"history_id":"3583","user_id":"67","game_stage":"11","question":"(34-10)x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:29"},
{"history_id":"3584","user_id":"68","game_stage":"9","question":"205+127x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":762,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":967,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":762}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":762,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":967,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":762}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:30"},
{"history_id":"3585","user_id":"84","game_stage":"10","question":"270÷(170-80)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":170,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":270,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:33"},
{"history_id":"3586","user_id":"66","game_stage":"10","question":"11x(106+57)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1793,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":163}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":106,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1793,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":163}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:33"},
{"history_id":"3587","user_id":"86","game_stage":"11","question":"944÷(85+33)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":944,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":944,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:37"},
{"history_id":"3588","user_id":"87","game_stage":"8","question":"36-160÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:41"},
{"history_id":"3589","user_id":"83","game_stage":"10","question":"(91+148)÷239","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":239,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":148}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":239}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":239,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":148}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":239,\"numB\":239}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:43"},
{"history_id":"3590","user_id":"69","game_stage":"9","question":"66÷33+18","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:44"},
{"history_id":"3591","user_id":"75","game_stage":"11","question":"(168-137)x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":403,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":343,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:56"},
{"history_id":"3592","user_id":"66","game_stage":"10","question":"12÷(52÷13)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:06:58"},
{"history_id":"3593","user_id":"76","game_stage":"9","question":"94x13-1115","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1222,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1222,\"numB\":1115}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1222,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1222,\"numB\":1115}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:07:14"},
{"history_id":"3594","user_id":"77","game_stage":"11","question":"218-(211-37)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":174}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":174}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:07:14"},
{"history_id":"3595","user_id":"86","game_stage":"11","question":"(142-141)x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:07:31"},
{"history_id":"3596","user_id":"69","game_stage":"9","question":"39x5+226","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":421,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":226}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":421,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":226}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:07:34"},
{"history_id":"3597","user_id":"84","game_stage":"10","question":"(73-67)x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:07:42"},
{"history_id":"3598","user_id":"75","game_stage":"11","question":"(197+144)x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":341,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3751,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":341,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":341,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3751,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":341,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:07:48"},
{"history_id":"3599","user_id":"67","game_stage":"11","question":"2016÷(168+120)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2016,\"numB\":288}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":120}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2016,\"numB\":288}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:07:54"},
{"history_id":"3600","user_id":"85","game_stage":"9","question":"248+9÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":248,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":248,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:13"},
{"history_id":"3601","user_id":"74","game_stage":"11","question":"(146-17)x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2064,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":129,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7464,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":129,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:13"},
{"history_id":"3602","user_id":"69","game_stage":"9","question":"128x1-94","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":134,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:22"},
{"history_id":"3603","user_id":"75","game_stage":"11","question":"(281+73)x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":354,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":354,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":354,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:28"},
{"history_id":"3604","user_id":"67","game_stage":"11","question":"10x(195-132)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":132}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":630,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":132}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":630,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:29"},
{"history_id":"3605","user_id":"76","game_stage":"9","question":"15-78÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:31"},
{"history_id":"3606","user_id":"86","game_stage":"11","question":"(212+98)x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":310,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2140,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":310,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:33"},
{"history_id":"3607","user_id":"77","game_stage":"11","question":"(219+228)x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":447,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":228}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":447,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":447,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":228}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":447,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:34"},
{"history_id":"3608","user_id":"66","game_stage":"11","question":"4÷(282÷141)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:39"},
{"history_id":"3609","user_id":"59","game_stage":"11","question":"1911÷(294-21)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":273,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1911,\"numB\":273}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":273,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1911,\"numB\":273}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:41"},
{"history_id":"3610","user_id":"68","game_stage":"10","question":"407÷(185÷5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":407,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":407,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:45"},
{"history_id":"3611","user_id":"74","game_stage":"11","question":"(217÷31)÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:46"},
{"history_id":"3612","user_id":"79","game_stage":"9","question":"75x15+221","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1125,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1346,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1125,\"numB\":221}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":221}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":17800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":236}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:47"},
{"history_id":"3613","user_id":"83","game_stage":"11","question":"221÷(52-35)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:55"},
{"history_id":"3614","user_id":"80","game_stage":"11","question":"2544÷(224+200)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":424,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":200}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2544,\"numB\":424}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":424,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":200}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2544,\"numB\":424}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:08:57"},
{"history_id":"3615","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"2099-146x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2044,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2099,\"numB\":2044}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2044,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2099,\"numB\":2044}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:01"},
{"history_id":"3616","user_id":"65","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c66\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u5272143\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272185\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"6x(143+185)","userAns_obj":"(185+143)x6","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:03"},
{"history_id":"3617","user_id":"87","game_stage":"9","question":"53+15÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:14"},
{"history_id":"3618","user_id":"85","game_stage":"9","question":"143÷13-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":143,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:23"},
{"history_id":"3619","user_id":"86","game_stage":"11","question":"7x(238+253)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":491,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":253}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3437,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":491}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":491,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":238,\"numB\":253}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3437,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":491}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:35"},
{"history_id":"3620","user_id":"62","game_stage":"9","question":"114-4x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":40}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:37"},
{"history_id":"3621","user_id":"77","game_stage":"11","question":"2050÷(255+155)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":410,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":155}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2050,\"numB\":410}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":410,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":155}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2050,\"numB\":410}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:39"},
{"history_id":"3622","user_id":"68","game_stage":"10","question":"(53-14)x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1881,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:41"},
{"history_id":"3623","user_id":"66","game_stage":"11","question":"(153-94)-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:09:48"},
{"history_id":"3624","user_id":"83","game_stage":"11","question":"(126+201)x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":327,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":201}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":654,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":327,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":327,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":201}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":658,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":327,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:02"},
{"history_id":"3625","user_id":"76","game_stage":"10","question":"4x(141-29)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":448,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":112}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":564,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":535,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":564,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:04"},
{"history_id":"3626","user_id":"79","game_stage":"9","question":"120+134x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1742,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1862,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":1742}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":274,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":134}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3562,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:04"},
{"history_id":"3627","user_id":"84","game_stage":"11","question":"47-(176-141)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:22"},
{"history_id":"3628","user_id":"75","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c62\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527216\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272115\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"2x(16+115)","userAns_obj":"(115+16)x2","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:27"},
{"history_id":"3629","user_id":"87","game_stage":"9","question":"283+123x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1390,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":283,\"numB\":1107}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":406,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":283,\"numB\":123}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3654,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":406,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:28"},
{"history_id":"3630","user_id":"66","game_stage":"11","question":"1365÷(299+156)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":156}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1365,\"numB\":455}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":455,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":156}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1365,\"numB\":455}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:29"},
{"history_id":"3631","user_id":"74","game_stage":"11","question":"1410÷(185-91)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1410,\"numB\":94}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":739,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1410,\"numB\":94}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:30"},
{"history_id":"3632","user_id":"68","game_stage":"10","question":"13x(165-5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":160}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":160,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":160}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:40"},
{"history_id":"3633","user_id":"85","game_stage":"9","question":"134-272÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":68}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":272,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":68}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:48"},
{"history_id":"3634","user_id":"71","game_stage":"8","question":"58÷2+193","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":222,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":193}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":193}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":444,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":195}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:10:54"},
{"history_id":"3635","user_id":"80","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8618\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86126\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e867\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"7x(18+126)","userAns_obj":"126+18x7","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:09"},
{"history_id":"3636","user_id":"69","game_stage":"9","question":"232+99x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":693,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":925,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":693}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":331,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2317,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":331,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:11"},
{"history_id":"3637","user_id":"84","game_stage":"11","question":"(172÷43)÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:14"},
{"history_id":"3638","user_id":"68","game_stage":"10","question":"25-(96-86)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:18"},
{"history_id":"3639","user_id":"59","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c612\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527237\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u527237\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"12x(37+37)","userAns_obj":"37+37x12","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:20"},
{"history_id":"3640","user_id":"71","game_stage":"8","question":"80x3+7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":247,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:22"},
{"history_id":"3641","user_id":"77","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8628\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8663\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e8613\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"13x(28+63)","userAns_obj":"28+63+13","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:25"},
{"history_id":"3642","user_id":"85","game_stage":"9","question":"70x12-328","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":840,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":512,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":840,\"numB\":328}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":328}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":316}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:42"},
{"history_id":"3643","user_id":"59","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u621011\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u5806168\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u5806161\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"11x(168+161)","userAns_obj":"(161+168)x11","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:51"},
{"history_id":"3644","user_id":"74","game_stage":"11","question":"266-(252-23)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":229}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":229,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":229}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:11:52"},
{"history_id":"3645","user_id":"82","game_stage":"10","question":"450÷(180÷4)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":450,\"numB\":45}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":450,\"numB\":45}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:12:17"},
{"history_id":"3646","user_id":"66","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u62109\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u5806141\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u5806104\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"9x(141+104)","userAns_obj":"(9x104)+141","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:12:39"},
{"history_id":"3647","user_id":"95","game_stage":"9","question":"44÷22+141","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":141}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":141}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:21:35"},
{"history_id":"3648","user_id":"88","game_stage":"9","question":"147+96÷6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:21:42"},
{"history_id":"3649","user_id":"98","game_stage":"7","question":"61+150+200","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":150}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":411,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":200}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":150}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":411,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":200}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:21:44"},
{"history_id":"3650","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"117+137+99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":254,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":353,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":654,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":137}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":753,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":654,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:05"},
{"history_id":"3651","user_id":"92","game_stage":"7","question":"135-70+72","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":72}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":135,\"numB\":0}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:09"},
{"history_id":"3652","user_id":"107","game_stage":"4","question":"193-14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:13"},
{"history_id":"3653","user_id":"110","game_stage":"8","question":"101+96x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":677,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":576}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":197,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:14"},
{"history_id":"3654","user_id":"105","game_stage":"8","question":"42÷7+73","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":73}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":73}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:18"},
{"history_id":"3655","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"145+70÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":70}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:18"},
{"history_id":"3656","user_id":"99","game_stage":"7","question":"57-9-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:21"},
{"history_id":"3657","user_id":"106","game_stage":"7","question":"152-135+224","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":135}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":224}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":135}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":224}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:27"},
{"history_id":"3658","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"169+97x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":266,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:31"},
{"history_id":"3659","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"65+40-85","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":85}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":40}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":85}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:35"},
{"history_id":"3660","user_id":"98","game_stage":"7","question":"294÷14x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":294,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:40"},
{"history_id":"3661","user_id":"107","game_stage":"4","question":"45÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:45"},
{"history_id":"3662","user_id":"91","game_stage":"7","question":"240+59-136","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":136}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":163,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":136}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:46"},
{"history_id":"3663","user_id":"100","game_stage":"8","question":"56+177÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":177}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2682,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:46"},
{"history_id":"3664","user_id":"110","game_stage":"8","question":"10+180÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:47"},
{"history_id":"3665","user_id":"92","game_stage":"7","question":"140+267+128","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":407,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":267}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":535,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":407,\"numB\":128}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":407,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":267}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":535,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":407,\"numB\":128}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:53"},
{"history_id":"3666","user_id":"116","game_stage":"8","question":"137+22÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":22}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:56"},
{"history_id":"3667","user_id":"112","game_stage":"6","question":"77-42-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:22:56"},
{"history_id":"3668","user_id":"109","game_stage":"7","question":"44+69+281","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":394,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":281}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":394,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":281}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:01"},
{"history_id":"3669","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"166÷2+10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":166,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:02"},
{"history_id":"3670","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"48+50","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":50}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":98,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":50}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:02"},
{"history_id":"3671","user_id":"105","game_stage":"8","question":"80x12-298","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":662,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":960,\"numB\":298}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":662,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":960,\"numB\":298}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:05"},
{"history_id":"3672","user_id":"110","game_stage":"8","question":"2x1-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:05"},
{"history_id":"3673","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"24+17x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":187}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":451,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:07"},
{"history_id":"3674","user_id":"103","game_stage":"9","question":"126+200÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":25,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:10"},
{"history_id":"3675","user_id":"113","game_stage":"6","question":"123+187-307","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":187}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":310,\"numB\":307}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":187}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":310,\"numB\":307}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:17"},
{"history_id":"3676","user_id":"88","game_stage":"9","question":"90÷3+147","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":147}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":147}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:19"},
{"history_id":"3677","user_id":"95","game_stage":"9","question":"25x12-70","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":300,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":300,\"numB\":70}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:23"},
{"history_id":"3678","user_id":"112","game_stage":"6","question":"2x2÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:24"},
{"history_id":"3679","user_id":"110","game_stage":"8","question":"35x1-23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:26"},
{"history_id":"3680","user_id":"116","game_stage":"8","question":"105+65x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":625,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":520}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":625,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":520}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:28"},
{"history_id":"3681","user_id":"100","game_stage":"8","question":"48+46x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":506,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":554,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":506}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":46}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1880,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:28"},
{"history_id":"3682","user_id":"105","game_stage":"8","question":"12÷6+118","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":118}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:29"},
{"history_id":"3683","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"372-26x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":372,\"numB\":312}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":346,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":372,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":346,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:30"},
{"history_id":"3684","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"27x4÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":108,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:32"},
{"history_id":"3685","user_id":"98","game_stage":"7","question":"299-19-189","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":91,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":189}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":81,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":189}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:34"},
{"history_id":"3686","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"47+234+223","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":234}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":504,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":223}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":281,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":234}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":504,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":281,\"numB\":223}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:36"},
{"history_id":"3687","user_id":"99","game_stage":"7","question":"231÷33÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":33}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:37"},
{"history_id":"3688","user_id":"90","game_stage":"8","question":"11x1+84","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":84}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":84}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:38"},
{"history_id":"3689","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"13+171÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":57}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":184,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":171}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:40"},
{"history_id":"3690","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"92-61","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:42"},
{"history_id":"3691","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"34x11+83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":457,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":374,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":34,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":467,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":374,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:43"},
{"history_id":"3692","user_id":"103","game_stage":"9","question":"120÷8-7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:45"},
{"history_id":"3693","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"112÷4+37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:49"},
{"history_id":"3694","user_id":"92","game_stage":"7","question":"42x10x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":420,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:50"},
{"history_id":"3695","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"117-67x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:23:58"},
{"history_id":"3696","user_id":"104","game_stage":"8","question":"130+171÷57","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":301,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":171}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":301,\"numB\":57}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:05"},
{"history_id":"3697","user_id":"90","game_stage":"8","question":"119÷7-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:06"},
{"history_id":"3698","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"1+91x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":819,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":820,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":819}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":92,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":828,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:13"},
{"history_id":"3699","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"6÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:14"},
{"history_id":"3700","user_id":"100","game_stage":"8","question":"148+10x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":218,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":70}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1106,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:15"},
{"history_id":"3701","user_id":"109","game_stage":"7","question":"78x14x15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1092,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1092,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1092,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1092,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:19"},
{"history_id":"3702","user_id":"98","game_stage":"7","question":"40+270-246","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":270}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":310,\"numB\":246}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":310,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":40,\"numB\":270}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":310,\"numB\":246}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:20"},
{"history_id":"3703","user_id":"103","game_stage":"9","question":"114-224÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":224,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:25"},
{"history_id":"3704","user_id":"116","game_stage":"8","question":"97-196÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:25"},
{"history_id":"3705","user_id":"107","game_stage":"6","question":"180-73-64","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":107,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:27"},
{"history_id":"3706","user_id":"90","game_stage":"8","question":"41-3x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:28"},
{"history_id":"3707","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"21+148÷74","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":74}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":961,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":148}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":961,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:33"},
{"history_id":"3708","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"68x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1111111111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:33"},
{"history_id":"3709","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"148÷37","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:34"},
{"history_id":"3710","user_id":"112","game_stage":"6","question":"144÷3÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:35"},
{"history_id":"3711","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"52x3-139","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":139}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":156,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":139}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:35"},
{"history_id":"3712","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"4-4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":0,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:37"},
{"history_id":"3713","user_id":"99","game_stage":"7","question":"26x10x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:39"},
{"history_id":"3714","user_id":"95","game_stage":"9","question":"225+220÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":220,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":55}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":220,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":55}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:39"},
{"history_id":"3715","user_id":"88","game_stage":"9","question":"11-235÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:48"},
{"history_id":"3716","user_id":"104","game_stage":"8","question":"9+72x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":585,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":576}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":881,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7048,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":881,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:52"},
{"history_id":"3717","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"134+130","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":264,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":130}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":164,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":130}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:52"},
{"history_id":"3718","user_id":"116","game_stage":"8","question":"133+54÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":18}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:54"},
{"history_id":"3719","user_id":"92","game_stage":"7","question":"126-62-16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:24:56"},
{"history_id":"3720","user_id":"109","game_stage":"7","question":"206÷103÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":103}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":103}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:01"},
{"history_id":"3721","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"176+121","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":121}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":16688686,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":121}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:10"},
{"history_id":"3722","user_id":"94","game_stage":"7","question":"8+58+78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":136}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:12"},
{"history_id":"3723","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"75x11+194","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":825,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1019,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":825,\"numB\":194}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":825,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1019,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":825,\"numB\":194}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:17"},
{"history_id":"3724","user_id":"113","game_stage":"6","question":"124÷31÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:23"},
{"history_id":"3725","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"19x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":95,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:29"},
{"history_id":"3726","user_id":"110","game_stage":"9","question":"158+130x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":418,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":260}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":418,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":260}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:30"},
{"history_id":"3727","user_id":"107","game_stage":"6","question":"116÷2÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:33"},
{"history_id":"3728","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"91÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:35"},
{"history_id":"3729","user_id":"105","game_stage":"9","question":"25x7+274","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":449,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":274}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":449,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":274}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:40"},
{"history_id":"3730","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"81-69","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":69}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":69}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:42"},
{"history_id":"3731","user_id":"103","game_stage":"10","question":"116÷(37+21)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:45"},
{"history_id":"3732","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"644-45x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":585,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":644,\"numB\":585}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":599,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":644,\"numB\":45}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7787,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":599,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:25:53"},
{"history_id":"3733","user_id":"95","game_stage":"10","question":"10x(152-88)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":640,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1520,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":152}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1448,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":1520,\"numB\":88}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:00"},
{"history_id":"3734","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"47x3-19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":19}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":19}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:02"},
{"history_id":"3735","user_id":"104","game_stage":"8","question":"188÷47+148","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":148}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":148}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:04"},
{"history_id":"3736","user_id":"113","game_stage":"6","question":"32x8x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:05"},
{"history_id":"3737","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"179-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":179,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:06"},
{"history_id":"3738","user_id":"98","game_stage":"8","question":"42+42x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":420,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":420}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":840,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:07"},
{"history_id":"3739","user_id":"107","game_stage":"6","question":"97x1÷97","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":97}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":97,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":97,\"numB\":97}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:07"},
{"history_id":"3740","user_id":"100","game_stage":"8","question":"23x7+134","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":161,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":134}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":141,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":141,\"numB\":134}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:08"},
{"history_id":"3741","user_id":"88","game_stage":"9","question":"728-51x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":714,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":728,\"numB\":714}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":714,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":728,\"numB\":714}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:10"},
{"history_id":"3742","user_id":"110","game_stage":"9","question":"127x3-269","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":381,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":381,\"numB\":269}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":381,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":381,\"numB\":269}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:12"},
{"history_id":"3743","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"75x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":525,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":525,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:15"},
{"history_id":"3744","user_id":"94","game_stage":"7","question":"131x16÷1048","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2096,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2096,\"numB\":1048}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2096,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2096,\"numB\":1048}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:20"},
{"history_id":"3745","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"70+53+145","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":145}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":123,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":268,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":145}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:20"},
{"history_id":"3746","user_id":"103","game_stage":"10","question":"10÷(62÷31)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:21"},
{"history_id":"3747","user_id":"116","game_stage":"9","question":"184÷8+230","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":230}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":253,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":230}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:24"},
{"history_id":"3748","user_id":"90","game_stage":"9","question":"27x6+299","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":461,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":299}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":461,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":299}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:30"},
{"history_id":"3749","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"74+29x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":290,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":364,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":290}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":103,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1030,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":103,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:30"},
{"history_id":"3750","user_id":"105","game_stage":"9","question":"199-11x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":188,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":199,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1444,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:32"},
{"history_id":"3751","user_id":"91","game_stage":"7","question":"68x7÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":476,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":476,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":476,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":476,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:32"},
{"history_id":"3752","user_id":"100","game_stage":"8","question":"155+48÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":24}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":24,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":179,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":24}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:36"},
{"history_id":"3753","user_id":"98","game_stage":"8","question":"49+36x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":265,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":216}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":510,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:43"},
{"history_id":"3754","user_id":"107","game_stage":"6","question":"120-68-12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":52,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":40,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:44"},
{"history_id":"3755","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"71+62÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":124,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:44"},
{"history_id":"3756","user_id":"92","game_stage":"8","question":"192+90x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":462,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":270}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":90}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":846,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:48"},
{"history_id":"3757","user_id":"103","game_stage":"10","question":"48÷(20÷5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:50"},
{"history_id":"3758","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"77x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":616,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":616,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:51"},
{"history_id":"3759","user_id":"109","game_stage":"8","question":"147+108÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":108,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":183,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":147,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:51"},
{"history_id":"3760","user_id":"111","game_stage":"8","question":"128÷64+157","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":157}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":157}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:52"},
{"history_id":"3761","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"26x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":302,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:54"},
{"history_id":"3762","user_id":"110","game_stage":"9","question":"12-8÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:55"},
{"history_id":"3763","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"78÷2+33","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":72,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":33}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":33}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:57"},
{"history_id":"3764","user_id":"113","game_stage":"6","question":"20x13÷10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:26:58"},
{"history_id":"3765","user_id":"94","game_stage":"7","question":"36+154-182","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":154}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":182}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":154}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":182}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:02"},
{"history_id":"3766","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"165÷15x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":165,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":99,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:06"},
{"history_id":"3767","user_id":"116","game_stage":"9","question":"72÷4-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:08"},
{"history_id":"3768","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"122+90x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":900,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1022,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":900}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":212,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":90}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:08"},
{"history_id":"3769","user_id":"100","game_stage":"8","question":"47x6-129","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":129}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":129}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:10"},
{"history_id":"3770","user_id":"104","game_stage":"8","question":"43x10-207","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":430,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":223,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":430,\"numB\":207}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":430,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":430,\"numB\":207}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:12"},
{"history_id":"3771","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"133x4÷14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":532,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":532,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":532,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1162,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":532,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:18"},
{"history_id":"3772","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"11x3+115","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":148,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":115}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":118,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":115}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":118}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:20"},
{"history_id":"3773","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"180÷20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:23"},
{"history_id":"3774","user_id":"98","game_stage":"8","question":"101+18x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:28"},
{"history_id":"3775","user_id":"100","game_stage":"8","question":"77÷11-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:30"},
{"history_id":"3776","user_id":"97","game_stage":"4","question":"98+22","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":22}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":98,\"numB\":22}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:31"},
{"history_id":"3777","user_id":"105","game_stage":"9","question":"877-52x16","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":832,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":877,\"numB\":832}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":832,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":877,\"numB\":832}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:33"},
{"history_id":"3778","user_id":"108","game_stage":"6","question":"161÷23x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":70,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:39"},
{"history_id":"3779","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"124÷2+64","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":64}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":64}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:41"},
{"history_id":"3780","user_id":"95","game_stage":"10","question":"885÷(197+98)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":885,\"numB\":295}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":295,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":197,\"numB\":98}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":885,\"numB\":295}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:45"},
{"history_id":"3781","user_id":"90","game_stage":"9","question":"47x11-80","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":517,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":437,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":517,\"numB\":80}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":517,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":437,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":517,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:47"},
{"history_id":"3782","user_id":"88","game_stage":"10","question":"10x(171-92)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":790,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":79}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":171,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":790,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":79}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:48"},
{"history_id":"3783","user_id":"109","game_stage":"8","question":"102+138÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":171,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":69}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":102,\"numB\":138}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":120,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:48"},
{"history_id":"3784","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"95+99","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":99}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":194,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":95,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:49"},
{"history_id":"3785","user_id":"92","game_stage":"8","question":"33+89x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1068,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":1068}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":89}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1464,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:27:59"},
{"history_id":"3786","user_id":"116","game_stage":"9","question":"161+21÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":161,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:00"},
{"history_id":"3787","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"78+96x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":96,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":270,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":192}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":348,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:10"},
{"history_id":"3788","user_id":"95","game_stage":"10","question":"4÷(89-88)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":88}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:10"},
{"history_id":"3789","user_id":"98","game_stage":"8","question":"15-76÷19","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":76,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:11"},
{"history_id":"3790","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"90x10+143","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":900,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1043,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":900,\"numB\":143}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":153,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":143}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":177,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":153}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:13"},
{"history_id":"3791","user_id":"103","game_stage":"11","question":"793÷(72-11)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":793,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":793,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:19"},
{"history_id":"3792","user_id":"106","game_stage":"7","question":"127x8÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1016,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1016,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1016,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1016,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:20"},
{"history_id":"3793","user_id":"105","game_stage":"9","question":"122÷2+227","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":227}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":288,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":227}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:22"},
{"history_id":"3794","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"67x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":201,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:25"},
{"history_id":"3795","user_id":"109","game_stage":"8","question":"13+87x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":87}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":87}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:26"},
{"history_id":"3796","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"27+15÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:30"},
{"history_id":"3797","user_id":"96","game_stage":"4","question":"77x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":616,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":616,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:31"},
{"history_id":"3798","user_id":"98","game_stage":"8","question":"21÷7+179","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":179}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":179}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:37"},
{"history_id":"3799","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"181+72÷8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:41"},
{"history_id":"3800","user_id":"112","game_stage":"7","question":"145-128+132","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":128}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":132}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":128}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":132}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:43"},
{"history_id":"3801","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"83x13÷13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1079,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":83,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1079,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1079,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":83,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8697,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1079,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:43"},
{"history_id":"3802","user_id":"94","game_stage":"8","question":"6x13+156","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":234,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":156}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":244,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":156}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:45"},
{"history_id":"3803","user_id":"88","game_stage":"10","question":"(88-1)x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":87,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:45"},
{"history_id":"3804","user_id":"107","game_stage":"7","question":"189+256-197","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":445,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":256}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":248,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":445,\"numB\":197}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":197}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:46"},
{"history_id":"3805","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"123÷41-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:48"},
{"history_id":"3806","user_id":"91","game_stage":"7","question":"252÷14x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":18,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:53"},
{"history_id":"3807","user_id":"104","game_stage":"8","question":"111+136÷34","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":115,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":111,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:28:57"},
{"history_id":"3808","user_id":"113","game_stage":"7","question":"177+66+137","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":380,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":137}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":243,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":470,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":243,\"numB\":137}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:02"},
{"history_id":"3809","user_id":"110","game_stage":"10","question":"100-(114-58)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":56}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":114,\"numB\":58}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":44,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":56}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:04"},
{"history_id":"3810","user_id":"114","game_stage":"4","question":"80x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":960,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:04"},
{"history_id":"3811","user_id":"95","game_stage":"10","question":"113-(120-15)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":105}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":105,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":120,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":105}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:06"},
{"history_id":"3812","user_id":"106","game_stage":"7","question":"269-83-14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":269,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":186,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":269,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":186,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:13"},
{"history_id":"3813","user_id":"109","game_stage":"8","question":"162÷81-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":80}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:15"},
{"history_id":"3814","user_id":"88","game_stage":"10","question":"24÷(159÷53)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":53}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:18"},
{"history_id":"3815","user_id":"90","game_stage":"9","question":"48-138÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:19"},
{"history_id":"3816","user_id":"116","game_stage":"9","question":"84+122x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1098,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":1098}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":41098,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":41182,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":41098}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:21"},
{"history_id":"3817","user_id":"104","game_stage":"8","question":"61-4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:22"},
{"history_id":"3818","user_id":"103","game_stage":"11","question":"(80+152)÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":152}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":152}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":232,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:24"},
{"history_id":"3819","user_id":"94","game_stage":"8","question":"117÷3+166","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":166}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":39,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":117,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":205,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":166}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:26"},
{"history_id":"3820","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"94x4-149","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":376,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":227,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":376,\"numB\":149}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":376,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":227,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":376,\"numB\":149}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:29"},
{"history_id":"3821","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"138÷6÷23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:30"},
{"history_id":"3822","user_id":"92","game_stage":"8","question":"74x13+62","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":962,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1024,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":962,\"numB\":62}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":62}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5550,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":75}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:31"},
{"history_id":"3823","user_id":"107","game_stage":"7","question":"265+297+195","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":562,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":265,\"numB\":297}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":757,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":562,\"numB\":195}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":562,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":265,\"numB\":297}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":757,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":562,\"numB\":195}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:39"},
{"history_id":"3824","user_id":"104","game_stage":"8","question":"38÷2-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":19,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:49"},
{"history_id":"3825","user_id":"93","game_stage":"8","question":"48÷24+136","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":136}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":138,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":136}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:50"},
{"history_id":"3826","user_id":"108","game_stage":"7","question":"267-141+83","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":209,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":83}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":126,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":267,\"numB\":141}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":309,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":83}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:51"},
{"history_id":"3827","user_id":"94","game_stage":"8","question":"31x7-117","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":100,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":117}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":107,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":217,\"numB\":117}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:57"},
{"history_id":"3828","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"130+89x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1287,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":1157}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":89}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2847,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":219,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:29:58"},
{"history_id":"3829","user_id":"100","game_stage":"9","question":"92x16+291","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1472,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1763,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1472,\"numB\":291}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":644,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":935,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":644,\"numB\":291}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:01"},
{"history_id":"3830","user_id":"112","game_stage":"7","question":"156÷26x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":156,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:02"},
{"history_id":"3831","user_id":"103","game_stage":"11","question":"545÷(247+298)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":545,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":298}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":545,\"numB\":545}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":545,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":298}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":545,\"numB\":545}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:05"},
{"history_id":"3832","user_id":"110","game_stage":"10","question":"12x(55+117)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":117}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2064,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":172}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":117}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":12,\"numB\":172}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis08","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:13"},
{"history_id":"3833","user_id":"116","game_stage":"9","question":"248+57x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":798,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1046,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":248,\"numB\":798}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":798,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1046,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":248,\"numB\":798}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:18"},
{"history_id":"3834","user_id":"113","game_stage":"7","question":"233-48-142","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":185,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":142}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":185,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":43,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":142}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:23"},
{"history_id":"3835","user_id":"91","game_stage":"8","question":"152+4÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":154,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:26"},
{"history_id":"3836","user_id":"90","game_stage":"10","question":"1x(138+124)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":262,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":124}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":262,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":262}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":262,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":138,\"numB\":124}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":262,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":262}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:28"},
{"history_id":"3837","user_id":"94","game_stage":"8","question":"65x4-116","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":116}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":260,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":116}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:30"},
{"history_id":"3838","user_id":"105","game_stage":"10","question":"13÷(104÷8)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":104,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:31"},
{"history_id":"3839","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"153+17x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":221}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":374,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":221}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:36"},
{"history_id":"3840","user_id":"95","game_stage":"11","question":"273÷(273÷13)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":21}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":213,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":273,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:36"},
{"history_id":"3841","user_id":"110","game_stage":"10","question":"74÷(169-95)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":74}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":169,\"numB\":95}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":74}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:40"},
{"history_id":"3842","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"74÷2+135","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":172,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":135}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":135}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":678,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":137}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:41"},
{"history_id":"3843","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"128÷64÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:45"},
{"history_id":"3844","user_id":"98","game_stage":"9","question":"26x1+59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":85,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":59}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":60,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":60}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:46"},
{"history_id":"3845","user_id":"111","game_stage":"9","question":"282+110x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":502,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":220}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":220,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":110,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":502,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":282,\"numB\":220}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:50"},
{"history_id":"3846","user_id":"109","game_stage":"8","question":"8÷4+149","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":149}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":149}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:51"},
{"history_id":"3847","user_id":"108","game_stage":"7","question":"142+171+294","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":313,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":171}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":607,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":313,\"numB\":294}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":323,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":142,\"numB\":171}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":617,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":323,\"numB\":294}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:53"},
{"history_id":"3848","user_id":"94","game_stage":"8","question":"15x6+186","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":186}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":15,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":90,\"numB\":186}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:30:56"},
{"history_id":"3849","user_id":"91","game_stage":"8","question":"45÷9-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:02"},
{"history_id":"3850","user_id":"105","game_stage":"10","question":"(62-51)÷11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":62,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:06"},
{"history_id":"3851","user_id":"100","game_stage":"9","question":"176÷2+264","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":264}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":73,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":340,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":73,\"numB\":264}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:08"},
{"history_id":"3852","user_id":"109","game_stage":"8","question":"100÷50-1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":1}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:09"},
{"history_id":"3853","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"94x6-151","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":564,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":413,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":564,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":56,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":151}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:17"},
{"history_id":"3854","user_id":"106","game_stage":"8","question":"56x12+161","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":672,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":833,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":672,\"numB\":161}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":672,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":56,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":813,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":672,\"numB\":161}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:19"},
{"history_id":"3855","user_id":"107","game_stage":"7","question":"182÷26x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":26}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":1}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":182,\"numB\":26}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:22"},
{"history_id":"3856","user_id":"97","game_stage":"6","question":"89-36+142","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":142}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":89,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":195,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":142}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:25"},
{"history_id":"3857","user_id":"90","game_stage":"10","question":"(112-55)x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":57,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":342,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:26"},
{"history_id":"3858","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"144+155÷31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":31}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":299,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":155}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":299,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:26"},
{"history_id":"3859","user_id":"110","game_stage":"10","question":"101-(144-54)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":90}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":90,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":144,\"numB\":54}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":90}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:28"},
{"history_id":"3860","user_id":"98","game_stage":"9","question":"218+288÷24","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":288,\"numB\":24}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":230,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:30"},
{"history_id":"3861","user_id":"114","game_stage":"6","question":"195+195-108","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":390,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":195}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":390,\"numB\":108}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":390,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":195}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":282,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":390,\"numB\":108}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:32"},
{"history_id":"3862","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"69÷3-17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:32"},
{"history_id":"3863","user_id":"95","game_stage":"11","question":"1208÷(233-82)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1208,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":82}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1208,\"numB\":151}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:35"},
{"history_id":"3864","user_id":"113","game_stage":"7","question":"192÷3÷4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":4}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":64,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:43"},
{"history_id":"3865","user_id":"93","game_stage":"9","question":"260+140x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":140,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1940,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":1680}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":400,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":140}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":4800,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":400,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:43"},
{"history_id":"3866","user_id":"108","game_stage":"7","question":"278+252-15","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":530,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":252}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":515,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":530,\"numB\":15}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":530,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":252}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":515,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":530,\"numB\":15}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:44"},
{"history_id":"3867","user_id":"92","game_stage":"8","question":"168÷6+168","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":168}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":168}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:44"},
{"history_id":"3868","user_id":"103","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c64\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527297\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272178\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"4x(97+178)","userAns_obj":"(97+178)x4","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:46"},
{"history_id":"3869","user_id":"111","game_stage":"9","question":"608-49x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":539,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":608,\"numB\":539}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":539,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":49,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":69,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":608,\"numB\":539}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:47"},
{"history_id":"3870","user_id":"90","game_stage":"10","question":"(63-52)x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":88,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:49"},
{"history_id":"3871","user_id":"116","game_stage":"10","question":"8x(152-8)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":144,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1152,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":144}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1216,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":152}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1208,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":1216,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:49"},
{"history_id":"3872","user_id":"109","game_stage":"8","question":"487-54x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":486,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":487,\"numB\":486}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":486,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":487,\"numB\":486}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:51"},
{"history_id":"3873","user_id":"88","game_stage":"11","question":"4740÷(81+235)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":235}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4740,\"numB\":316}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":81,\"numB\":235}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4740,\"numB\":316}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:53"},
{"history_id":"3874","user_id":"115","game_stage":"8","question":"61-4x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:31:55"},
{"history_id":"3875","user_id":"91","game_stage":"8","question":"139+134÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":67,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":134,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":206,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:03"},
{"history_id":"3876","user_id":"104","game_stage":"9","question":"297÷9+126","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":159,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":126}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":126}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":135}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:08"},
{"history_id":"3877","user_id":"98","game_stage":"9","question":"31-132÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":20,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":31,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:10"},
{"history_id":"3878","user_id":"107","game_stage":"7","question":"226+75-82","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":301,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":301,\"numB\":82}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":301,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":75}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":219,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":301,\"numB\":82}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:18"},
{"history_id":"3879","user_id":"96","game_stage":"6","question":"172+43+181","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":215,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":396,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":215,\"numB\":181}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":61111,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":43,\"numB\":181}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":61283,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":172,\"numB\":61111}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:22"},
{"history_id":"3880","user_id":"105","game_stage":"10","question":"159-(162-34)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":128}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":128}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:24"},
{"history_id":"3881","user_id":"106","game_stage":"8","question":"100+67x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":737,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":67,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":837,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":737}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":167,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":100,\"numB\":67}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1817,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":167,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:24"},
{"history_id":"3882","user_id":"92","game_stage":"8","question":"620-51x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":612,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":620,\"numB\":612}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":612,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":51,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":620,\"numB\":612}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:31"},
{"history_id":"3883","user_id":"94","game_stage":"9","question":"80+57x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":228,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":308,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":228}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":137,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":57}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":548,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:37"},
{"history_id":"3884","user_id":"108","game_stage":"7","question":"105÷3x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":35,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:37"},
{"history_id":"3885","user_id":"113","game_stage":"7","question":"202÷2x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":202,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1010,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":202,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1001,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:39"},
{"history_id":"3886","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"27x13+187","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":538,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":351,\"numB\":187}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":351,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":538,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":351,\"numB\":187}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:41"},
{"history_id":"3887","user_id":"112","game_stage":"7","question":"231+25-228","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":228}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":231,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":256,\"numB\":228}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:44"},
{"history_id":"3888","user_id":"88","game_stage":"11","question":"(255-30)x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":30}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":675,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":225,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":255,\"numB\":30}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":675,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":225,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:44"},
{"history_id":"3889","user_id":"104","game_stage":"9","question":"278+226÷113","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":113}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:45"},
{"history_id":"3890","user_id":"111","game_stage":"9","question":"44-17x1","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":44,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:48"},
{"history_id":"3891","user_id":"98","game_stage":"9","question":"4-86÷43","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":86,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":82,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":4,\"numB\":86}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":43}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis02mis04","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:49"},
{"history_id":"3892","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"274-81-104","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":104}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":193,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":274,\"numB\":81}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":104}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:56"},
{"history_id":"3893","user_id":"100","game_stage":"9","question":"206÷103+291","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":103}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":291}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":206,\"numB\":103}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":293,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":291}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:32:58"},
{"history_id":"3894","user_id":"95","game_stage":"11","question":"24÷(290÷145)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":145}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":290,\"numB\":145}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:01"},
{"history_id":"3895","user_id":"90","game_stage":"11","question":"333÷(185÷5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":333,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":333,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:12"},
{"history_id":"3896","user_id":"116","game_stage":"10","question":"1225÷(163+12)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1225,\"numB\":175}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1225,\"numB\":163}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":187,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":175,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:16"},
{"history_id":"3897","user_id":"94","game_stage":"9","question":"184÷92+171","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":171}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":184,\"numB\":92}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":171}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:16"},
{"history_id":"3898","user_id":"88","game_stage":"11","question":"(22+230)x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":230}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":504,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":252,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":230}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":504,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":252,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:19"},
{"history_id":"3899","user_id":"106","game_stage":"8","question":"3+68x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":748,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":751,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":748}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":748,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":68,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":751,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":748}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:25"},
{"history_id":"3900","user_id":"104","game_stage":"9","question":"237÷3-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":79,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":237,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":68,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:29"},
{"history_id":"3901","user_id":"113","game_stage":"7","question":"203+273+257","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":476,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":273}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":733,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":476,\"numB\":257}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":476,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":203,\"numB\":273}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":733,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":476,\"numB\":257}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:36"},
{"history_id":"3902","user_id":"114","game_stage":"6","question":"84x11÷28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":924,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":924,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":924,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":924,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:36"},
{"history_id":"3903","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"163+10÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":173,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":163,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":86,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:45"},
{"history_id":"3904","user_id":"90","game_stage":"11","question":"(195-6)x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1890,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1890,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:47"},
{"history_id":"3905","user_id":"115","game_stage":"7","question":"128+184-200","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":200}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":184}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":200}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:49"},
{"history_id":"3906","user_id":"97","game_stage":"6","question":"63÷21x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":63,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:51"},
{"history_id":"3907","user_id":"107","game_stage":"8","question":"126+6x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":66,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":192,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":132,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1452,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:52"},
{"history_id":"3908","user_id":"94","game_stage":"9","question":"226÷2-105","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":105}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":113,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":105}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:53"},
{"history_id":"3909","user_id":"100","game_stage":"9","question":"58-91÷7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":7}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":0}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:56"},
{"history_id":"3910","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"653-55x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":605,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":48,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":653,\"numB\":605}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":598,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":653,\"numB\":55}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6578,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":598,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:59"},
{"history_id":"3911","user_id":"116","game_stage":"10","question":"93-(128-50)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":78,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":50}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:33:59"},
{"history_id":"3912","user_id":"95","game_stage":"11","question":"(293-72)÷17","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":293,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":17}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":221,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":293,\"numB\":72}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":221,\"numB\":17}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:01"},
{"history_id":"3913","user_id":"110","game_stage":"11","question":"6x(36+144)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":180}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":36,\"numB\":144}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1080,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":180}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:04"},
{"history_id":"3914","user_id":"105","game_stage":"11","question":"48-(87-52)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":35}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":35}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:08"},
{"history_id":"3915","user_id":"104","game_stage":"9","question":"119x6+135","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":714,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":849,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":714,\"numB\":135}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":714,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":119,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":849,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":714,\"numB\":135}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:09"},
{"history_id":"3916","user_id":"98","game_stage":"10","question":"3x(28+91)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":357,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":119}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":119,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":91}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":357,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":119}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:11"},
{"history_id":"3917","user_id":"96","game_stage":"6","question":"79+48+31","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":127,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":79,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":158,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":31}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:14"},
{"history_id":"3918","user_id":"111","game_stage":"10","question":"37÷(74÷2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":37}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":37}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:19"},
{"history_id":"3919","user_id":"106","game_stage":"8","question":"24x10-169","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":169}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":240,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":24,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":169}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:20"},
{"history_id":"3920","user_id":"109","game_stage":"9","question":"70÷35+78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":78}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":78}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:21"},
{"history_id":"3921","user_id":"92","game_stage":"8","question":"228-55x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":165}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":165,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":228,\"numB\":165}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:26"},
{"history_id":"3922","user_id":"107","game_stage":"8","question":"21+29x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":166,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":145}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":50,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":21,\"numB\":29}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":250,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:30"},
{"history_id":"3923","user_id":"108","game_stage":"7","question":"271+49-305","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":271,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":320,\"numB\":305}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":271,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":320,\"numB\":305}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:33"},
{"history_id":"3924","user_id":"93","game_stage":"9","question":"162+72÷12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":168,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:34"},
{"history_id":"3925","user_id":"100","game_stage":"9","question":"373-33x9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":373,\"numB\":297}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":33,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":373,\"numB\":297}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:35"},
{"history_id":"3926","user_id":"94","game_stage":"9","question":"93x1-39","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":39}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":93,\"numB\":39}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:38"},
{"history_id":"3927","user_id":"113","game_stage":"7","question":"72x6÷144","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":432,\"numB\":144}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":432,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":432,\"numB\":144}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:39"},
{"history_id":"3928","user_id":"91","game_stage":"9","question":"122x3+229","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":366,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":595,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":366,\"numB\":229}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":366,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":122,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":595,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":366,\"numB\":229}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:44"},
{"history_id":"3929","user_id":"95","game_stage":"11","question":"(46+295)x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":341,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":295}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1023,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":341,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":314,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":295}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":942,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":314,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:44"},
{"history_id":"3930","user_id":"97","game_stage":"6","question":"27÷3÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":27,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:50"},
{"history_id":"3931","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"133+78x12","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":936,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":78,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1069,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":936}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":133,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2532,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":12}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:50"},
{"history_id":"3932","user_id":"115","game_stage":"7","question":"218÷2÷109","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":109,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":109}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":218,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":109}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:51"},
{"history_id":"3933","user_id":"90","game_stage":"11","question":"(205-43)÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":9}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":162,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":205,\"numB\":43}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":162,\"numB\":9}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:52"},
{"history_id":"3934","user_id":"106","game_stage":"8","question":"105+45÷9","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":45,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":105,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:34:56"},
{"history_id":"3935","user_id":"110","game_stage":"11","question":"(260-34)-91","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":91}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":91}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:03"},
{"history_id":"3936","user_id":"116","game_stage":"10","question":"13x(181-77)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1352,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":104}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":181,\"numB\":77}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":452,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":104}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:03"},
{"history_id":"3937","user_id":"107","game_stage":"8","question":"132+26÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":145,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":132,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:06"},
{"history_id":"3938","user_id":"108","game_stage":"7","question":"88÷8x5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":88,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:08"},
{"history_id":"3939","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"116x16x10","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1856,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1856,\"numB\":10}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1856,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":16}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":18560,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1856,\"numB\":10}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:08"},
{"history_id":"3940","user_id":"93","game_stage":"9","question":"66÷3-11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":66,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:10"},
{"history_id":"3941","user_id":"111","game_stage":"10","question":"(82-36)x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":82,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":276,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":46,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:12"},
{"history_id":"3942","user_id":"114","game_stage":"6","question":"187÷17x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":11,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":34,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":17,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":187,\"numB\":34}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis03","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:17"},
{"history_id":"3943","user_id":"88","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8663\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8693\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e869\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"9x(63+93)","userAns_obj":"(63+93)x9","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:18"},
{"history_id":"3944","user_id":"97","game_stage":"6","question":"9÷3÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:18"},
{"history_id":"3945","user_id":"96","game_stage":"6","question":"159÷3÷53","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":53}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":372378327,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":159,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":728272772,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":372378327,\"numB\":53}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:21"},
{"history_id":"3946","user_id":"92","game_stage":"8","question":"130÷2+167","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":167}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":65,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":130,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":232,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":167}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:27"},
{"history_id":"3947","user_id":"105","game_stage":"11","question":"(297-108)-113","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":113}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":189,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":76,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":189,\"numB\":113}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:32"},
{"history_id":"3948","user_id":"109","game_stage":"9","question":"75-2x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":59,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":75,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:34"},
{"history_id":"3949","user_id":"107","game_stage":"8","question":"10x8-63","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":80,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:35"},
{"history_id":"3950","user_id":"98","game_stage":"10","question":"(131-6)x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1375,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":125,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1375,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:36"},
{"history_id":"3951","user_id":"100","game_stage":"9","question":"235÷47+30","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":30}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":235,\"numB\":47}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":35,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":30}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:37"},
{"history_id":"3952","user_id":"115","game_stage":"7","question":"125÷25÷5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":125,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:38"},
{"history_id":"3953","user_id":"108","game_stage":"7","question":"123÷41x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":123,\"numB\":41}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":33,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:43"},
{"history_id":"3954","user_id":"101","game_stage":"8","question":"185÷37+180","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":185,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":180}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":217,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":37,\"numB\":180}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":123456789,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":217}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:43"},
{"history_id":"3955","user_id":"94","game_stage":"10","question":"2350÷(136+99)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":235,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":136,\"numB\":99}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2350,\"numB\":235}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2350,\"numB\":136}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":104,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":5,\"numB\":99}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:47"},
{"history_id":"3956","user_id":"104","game_stage":"10","question":"1165÷(39+194)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1165,\"numB\":233}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":39,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1165,\"numB\":233}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:35:53"},
{"history_id":"3957","user_id":"111","game_stage":"10","question":"70-(50-34)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":34}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":70,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:00"},
{"history_id":"3958","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"297+119+120","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":416,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":119}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":536,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":416,\"numB\":120}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":316,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":119}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":436,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":316,\"numB\":120}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:02"},
{"history_id":"3959","user_id":"112","game_stage":"8","question":"65x9+186","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":585,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":771,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":585,\"numB\":186}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":765,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":951,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":765,\"numB\":186}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:03"},
{"history_id":"3960","user_id":"91","game_stage":"9","question":"99x3-154","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":154}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":297,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":143,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":297,\"numB\":154}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:04"},
{"history_id":"3961","user_id":"113","game_stage":"8","question":"57+94x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1222,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":13}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":1279,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":1222}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":57,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1963,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":151,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:08"},
{"history_id":"3962","user_id":"93","game_stage":"9","question":"899-61x14","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":854,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":899,\"numB\":854}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":854,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":14}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":45,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":899,\"numB\":854}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:08"},
{"history_id":"3963","user_id":"105","game_stage":"11","question":"139-(188-111)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":77}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":77,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":188,\"numB\":111}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":62,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":139,\"numB\":77}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:11"},
{"history_id":"3964","user_id":"110","game_stage":"11","question":"3825÷(72+183)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":183}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3825,\"numB\":255}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":255,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":72,\"numB\":183}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":13,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3825,\"numB\":255}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:15"},
{"history_id":"3965","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"23x1+23","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":23}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":23,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":1}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":46,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":23,\"numB\":23}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:20"},
{"history_id":"3966","user_id":"107","game_stage":"8","question":"146÷73+28","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":73}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":30,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:23"},
{"history_id":"3967","user_id":"94","game_stage":"10","question":"211-(185-5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":180}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":26,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":211,\"numB\":185}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":21,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:25"},
{"history_id":"3968","user_id":"108","game_stage":"7","question":"137-36+254","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":355,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":254}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":101,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":137,\"numB\":36}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":355,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":101,\"numB\":254}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:27"},
{"history_id":"3969","user_id":"114","game_stage":"6","question":"148÷2÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":74,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":148,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:30"},
{"history_id":"3970","user_id":"115","game_stage":"7","question":"155-108-6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":47,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":155,\"numB\":108}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":41,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":47,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:32"},
{"history_id":"3971","user_id":"98","game_stage":"10","question":"(29+25)÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":54,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":25}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:34"},
{"history_id":"3972","user_id":"109","game_stage":"9","question":"185+244÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":244,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":307,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":122}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":122,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":244,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":307,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":185,\"numB\":122}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:36"},
{"history_id":"3973","user_id":"116","game_stage":"10","question":"2x(91-80)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":91,\"numB\":80}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":22,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":2,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:37"},
{"history_id":"3974","user_id":"95","game_stage":"11","question":"176÷(85-69)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":176,\"numB\":16}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:40"},
{"history_id":"3975","user_id":"90","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c613\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527288\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272141\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"13x(88+141)","userAns_obj":"(13x88)+141","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:43"},
{"history_id":"3976","user_id":"104","game_stage":"10","question":"744÷(112-19)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":744,\"numB\":93}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":93,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":19}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":744,\"numB\":93}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:46"},
{"history_id":"3977","user_id":"110","game_stage":"11","question":"(247-51)÷98","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":98}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":196,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":247,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":196,\"numB\":98}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:48"},
{"history_id":"3978","user_id":"89","game_stage":"7","question":"53+173-208","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":173}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":208}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":226,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":173}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":226,\"numB\":208}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:48"},
{"history_id":"3979","user_id":"112","game_stage":"8","question":"127+64x4","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":256,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":383,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":256}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":191,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":127,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":724,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":191,\"numB\":4}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:50"},
{"history_id":"3980","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"87÷3-20","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":20}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":87,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":20}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:36:52"},
{"history_id":"3981","user_id":"100","game_stage":"10","question":"366÷(158-97)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":366,\"numB\":61}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":61,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":158,\"numB\":97}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":366,\"numB\":61}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:37:05"},
{"history_id":"3982","user_id":"90","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86197\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86167\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e8611\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"11x(197+167)","userAns_obj":"(197+167)x11","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:37:13"},
{"history_id":"3983","user_id":"113","game_stage":"8","question":"77+177÷59","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":177,\"numB\":59}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":80,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":254,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":77,\"numB\":177}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":254,\"numB\":59}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:37:15"},
{"history_id":"3984","user_id":"94","game_stage":"10","question":"42-(52-21)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":31,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":52,\"numB\":21}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":31}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":52}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":21}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"mis01mis04","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:37:18"},
{"history_id":"3985","user_id":"99","game_stage":"8","question":"131+10x11","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":110}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":110,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":10,\"numB\":11}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":241,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":110}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:37:32"},
{"history_id":"3986","user_id":"113","game_stage":"8","question":"42x2+167","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":167}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":42,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":251,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":84,\"numB\":167}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:38:31"},
{"history_id":"3987","user_id":"112","game_stage":"8","question":"26x12+127","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":439,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":127}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":312,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":26,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":439,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":312,\"numB\":127}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:39:41"},
{"history_id":"3988","user_id":"113","game_stage":"8","question":"249-69x3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":207,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":207}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":180,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":249,\"numB\":69}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":540,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":180,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:41:02"},
{"history_id":"3989","user_id":"93","game_stage":"10","question":"8x(193-42)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":151}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":151,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":193,\"numB\":42}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1208,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":151}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:48:45"},
{"history_id":"3990","user_id":"93","game_stage":"10","question":"19-(61-49)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":12,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":12}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":61,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":17,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":19,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:49:42"},
{"history_id":"3991","user_id":"93","game_stage":"10","question":"(74-66)÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":74,\"numB\":66}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":8,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:50:23"},
{"history_id":"3992","user_id":"91","game_stage":"9","question":"50x4-65","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":65}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":50,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":135,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":65}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:50:26"},
{"history_id":"3993","user_id":"93","game_stage":"10","question":"85-(152-94)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":58,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":152,\"numB\":94}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":27,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":85,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:51:20"},
{"history_id":"3994","user_id":"111","game_stage":"11","question":"259-(278-68)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":210}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":210,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":278,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":49,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":210}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:51:39"},
{"history_id":"3995","user_id":"95","game_stage":"11","question":"(173+216)÷389","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":389,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":216}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":389,\"numB\":389}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":389,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":216}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":389,\"numB\":389}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:51:53"},
{"history_id":"3996","user_id":"91","game_stage":"10","question":"13x(126+49)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":175}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":175,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":126,\"numB\":49}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2275,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":13,\"numB\":175}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:52:34"},
{"history_id":"3997","user_id":"95","game_stage":"11","question":"16x(41-5)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":36}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":41,\"numB\":5}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":576,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":36}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:52:43"},
{"history_id":"3998","user_id":"93","game_stage":"11","question":"30÷(260÷130)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":130}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":260,\"numB\":130}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":15,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":30,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:52:43"},
{"history_id":"3999","user_id":"107","game_stage":"9","question":"29x6+205","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":174,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":6}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":379,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":174,\"numB\":205}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":211,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":205}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":6119,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":211}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:11"},
{"history_id":"4000","user_id":"116","game_stage":"10","question":"(22+109)x7","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":917,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":7}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":131,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":22,\"numB\":109}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":917,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":131,\"numB\":7}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:17"},
{"history_id":"4001","user_id":"100","game_stage":"10","question":"(146+145)x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":291,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":145}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3783,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":291,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":291,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":146,\"numB\":145}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":8730,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":291,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:18"},
{"history_id":"4002","user_id":"104","game_stage":"10","question":"(92-63)÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":63}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":92,\"numB\":63}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":0,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:19"},
{"history_id":"4003","user_id":"111","game_stage":"11","question":"(192÷64)÷3","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":192,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":42,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":128,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis09","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:34"},
{"history_id":"4004","user_id":"91","game_stage":"10","question":"55÷(99÷9)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":99,\"numB\":9}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":55,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":55,\"numB\":11}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:41"},
{"history_id":"4005","user_id":"93","game_stage":"11","question":"(214-64)÷25","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":25}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":214,\"numB\":64}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":6,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":25}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:46"},
{"history_id":"4006","user_id":"92","game_stage":"9","question":"69÷23+154","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":154}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":69,\"numB\":23}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":157,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":3,\"numB\":154}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:48"},
{"history_id":"4007","user_id":"104","game_stage":"10","question":"64-(113-85)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":28}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":113,\"numB\":85}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":36,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":64,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:53:56"},
{"history_id":"4008","user_id":"111","game_stage":"11","question":"(58÷2)÷29","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":29,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":58,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":29}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:06"},
{"history_id":"4009","user_id":"89","game_stage":"8","question":"150+48x8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":384,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":48,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":534,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":384}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":198,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":150,\"numB\":48}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1584,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":198,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis02","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:12"},
{"history_id":"4010","user_id":"98","game_stage":"11","question":"1x(233-83)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":150}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":233,\"numB\":83}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":150,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1,\"numB\":150}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:21"},
{"history_id":"4011","user_id":"95","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u62106\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u580645\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u580670\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"6x(45+70)","userAns_obj":"(45+70)x6","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:38"},
{"history_id":"4012","user_id":"91","game_stage":"10","question":"(178+12)÷38","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":38}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":190,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":178,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":190,\"numB\":38}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:39"},
{"history_id":"4013","user_id":"93","game_stage":"11","question":"6x(124-61)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":378,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":63}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":124,\"numB\":61}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":378,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6,\"numB\":63}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:43"},
{"history_id":"4014","user_id":"107","game_stage":"9","question":"59x10+254","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":590,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":844,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":590,\"numB\":254}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":590,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":10}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":844,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":590,\"numB\":254}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:44"},
{"history_id":"4015","user_id":"94","game_stage":"10","question":"1024÷(145-17)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":128,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1024,\"numB\":128}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":28,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":145,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":37,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":1024,\"numB\":28}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:47"},
{"history_id":"4016","user_id":"92","game_stage":"9","question":"32÷2-5","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":11,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":5}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":32,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":1,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":5}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:53"},
{"history_id":"4017","user_id":"110","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c68\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527266\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u527223\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"8x(66+23)","userAns_obj":"66+23","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:54:54"},
{"history_id":"4018","user_id":"100","game_stage":"10","question":"(168+68)x13","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3068,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":13}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":236,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":168,\"numB\":68}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":3068,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":236,\"numB\":13}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:00"},
{"history_id":"4019","user_id":"116","game_stage":"10","question":"(59+35)÷47","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":94,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":59,\"numB\":35}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":94,\"numB\":47}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:07"},
{"history_id":"4020","user_id":"111","game_stage":"11","question":"14x(195+233)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":428,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":233}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5992,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":428}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":428,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":195,\"numB\":233}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":5992,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":14,\"numB\":428}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:13"},
{"history_id":"4021","user_id":"104","game_stage":"11","question":"173-(116-27)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":89}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":89,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":27}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":84,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":173,\"numB\":89}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:22"},
{"history_id":"4022","user_id":"100","game_stage":"10","question":"(20+96)÷58","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":58}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":116,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":96}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":2,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":116,\"numB\":58}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:27"},
{"history_id":"4023","user_id":"110","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86134\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e8639\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e8613\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"13x(134+39)","userAns_obj":"(134+39)x13","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:29"},
{"history_id":"4024","user_id":"89","game_stage":"8","question":"153÷17+66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":9,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":75,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":9,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":38,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":153,\"numB\":17}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":204,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":38,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:32"},
{"history_id":"4025","user_id":"98","game_stage":"11","question":"(54+244)÷2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":244}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":298,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":54,\"numB\":244}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":149,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":298,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:37"},
{"history_id":"4026","user_id":"91","game_stage":"10","question":"(65+194)x2","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":259,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":518,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":2}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":259,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":65,\"numB\":194}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":518,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":2}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:44"},
{"history_id":"4027","user_id":"106","game_stage":"9","question":"109+234÷78","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":3}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":3,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":234,\"numB\":78}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":112,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":109,\"numB\":3}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:50"},
{"history_id":"4028","user_id":"107","game_stage":"9","question":"212÷4-49","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":49}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":53,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":212,\"numB\":4}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":4,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":53,\"numB\":49}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:55:54"},
{"history_id":"4029","user_id":"92","game_stage":"9","question":"25x12-67","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":300,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":233,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":300,\"numB\":67}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":200,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":25,\"numB\":12}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":133,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":200,\"numB\":67}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:56:16"},
{"history_id":"4030","user_id":"105","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c68\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u527265\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u527287\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"8x(65+87)","userAns_obj":"(65+87)x8","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:56:16"},
{"history_id":"4031","user_id":"112","game_stage":"8","question":"60x8-66","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":414,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":480,\"numB\":66}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":480,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":60,\"numB\":8}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":414,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":480,\"numB\":66}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:56:18"},
{"history_id":"4032","user_id":"104","game_stage":"11","question":"(29+251)x6","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":251}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1680,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":6}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":2,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":280,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":29,\"numB\":251}{\"index\":5,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":2280,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":280,\"numB\":6}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:56:18"},
{"history_id":"4033","user_id":"115","game_stage":"9","question":"259÷37+206","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":213,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":206}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":7,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":259,\"numB\":37}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":213,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":7,\"numB\":206}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:56:19"},
{"history_id":"4034","user_id":"94","game_stage":"10","question":"112÷(28÷2)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":14}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":28,\"numB\":2}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":8,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":112,\"numB\":14}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:56:34"},
{"history_id":"4035","user_id":"107","game_stage":"9","question":"213÷3-8","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":63,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":8}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":213,\"numB\":3}{\"index\":3,\"operators\":45,\"partAns\":3,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":71,\"numB\":8}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:56:43"},
{"history_id":"4036","user_id":"98","game_stage":"11","question":"6860÷(266+224)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":490,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":224}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6860,\"numB\":490}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":490,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":266,\"numB\":224}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":14,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":6860,\"numB\":490}","isCorrect":"True","misconception":"","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:56:49"},
{"history_id":"4037","user_id":"98","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6574\u7406\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u7684\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u7e3d\u5171\u5206\u62109\u5806\uff0c\u6bcf\u5806\u5167\u5404\u653e\u7f6e\u5927\u7684\u8349\u5806153\u500b\uff0c\u5c0f\u7684\u8349\u580623\u500b\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u5230\u591a\u5c11\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"9x(153+23)","userAns_obj":"23","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"\u4e0d\u540c\u7684\u904b\u7b97\u7b26\u865f\u6709\u4e0d\u540c","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:58:18"},
{"history_id":"4038","user_id":"98","game_stage":"12","question":"\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u6e96\u5099\u51fa\u9580\u53bb\u6536\u5272\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u6c7a\u5b9a\u63a1\u96c6A\u8f2a\uff0c\u6bcf\u8f2a\u90fd\u5148\u5728\u5bb6\u9580\u53e3\u6536\u5272B\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7136\u5f8c\u5728\u6c60\u5858\u65c1\u908a\u6536\u5272C\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4eca\u5929\u7e3d\u5171\u6536\u5272\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"\u6536\u5272$+","userAns_obj":"\u8f2a$x","isCorrect":"\u7e3d\u5171$+\r","misconception":"9x(153+23)","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:58:19"},
{"history_id":"4039","user_id":"98","game_stage":"12","question":"\ufeff\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u8d70\u5728\u8def\u4e0a\u770b\u5230\u4e00\u4e9b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u4ed6\u6bcf\u4e00\u6b21\u90fd\u5728\u7b2c\u4e00\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86B\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u7b2c\u4e8c\u500b\u5730\u65b9\u8490\u96c6\u4e86C\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff0c\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de\u8dd1\u4e86A\u6b21\uff0c\u8acb\u554f\u8c6c\u5927\u54e5\u7e3d\u5171\u8490\u96c6\u4e86\u5e7e\u500b\u8349\u5806\uff1f","correctAns_obj":"\u8490\u96c6$+","userAns_obj":"\u4f86\u4f86\u56de\u56de$x","isCorrect":"\u7e3d\u5171$+\r","misconception":"9x(153+23)","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:58:19"},
{"history_id":"4040","user_id":"91","game_stage":"11","question":"160÷(240÷15)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":16,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":10,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":16}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":18,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":240,\"numB\":15}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":247,\"partAns\":5,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":160,\"numB\":18}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis05","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:58:35"},
{"history_id":"4041","user_id":"91","game_stage":"11","question":"16x(20+51)","correctAns_obj":"{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":71,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":20,\"numB\":51}{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":1136,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":71}","userAns_obj":"{\"index\":1,\"operators\":120,\"partAns\":320,\"isInBracket\":false,\"numA\":16,\"numB\":20}{\"index\":4,\"operators\":43,\"partAns\":371,\"isInBracket\":true,\"numA\":320,\"numB\":51}","isCorrect":"False","misconception":"mis01","upload_time":"2018-06-28 11:59:15"}]
